<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<configurable>
  <sku>SVYK110GR</sku>
  <i18n_name>ROZIE CROPPED  MICRO GEOMETRIC PRINT</i18n_name>
  <i18n_name_de>ROZIE CROPPED  MICRO GEOMETRIC PRINT</i18n_name_de>
  <i18n_name_nl>ROZIE CROPPED  MICRO GEOMETRIC PRINT</i18n_name_nl>
  <i18n_name_fr>ROZIE CROPPED  MICRO GEOMETRIC PRINT</i18n_name_fr>
  <i18n_name_it>ROZIE CROPPED  MICRO GEOMETRIC PRINT</i18n_name_it>
  <i18n_name_es>ROZIE CROPPED  MICRO GEOMETRIC PRINT</i18n_name_es>
  <product_start_date>2012-10-28</product_start_date>
  <product_end_date>2019-10-02</product_end_date>
  <i18n_description>The Rozie Cropped Micro Geometric Print is A very expensive brand’s new and leg-lengthening High Waist Slim fit, seen here channelling the geometric and bespoke denim trends. The Rozie has a slim, straight leg that combines with a feminine high waist to give a sleek, sophisticated and beautifully leg-lengthening silhouette. The signature squiggle on the back pocket enhances the striking 7FAM identity. Just enough stretch means making your fashion mark is effortlessly comfortable. Shape up to the graphic denim trend in this high-fashion and feminine cropped style.</i18n_description>
  <i18n_description_de>Rozie Cropped Micro Geometric Print heißt der neue Fit von A very expensive brand, der sichtbar beinestreckend wirkt und die neuesten geometrischen und originellen Trends für maßgeschneiderten Denim aufnimmt. Die Rozie hat einen geraden und schlanken Beinschnitt, der zur hohen, femininen Leibhöhe passt und für eine gerade und raffinierte, wunderschön beinstreckende Linie sorgt. Das gestickte Logo auf dem Backpocket unterstreicht die starke Persönlichkeit von 7FAM. Mit dem richtigen Stretchanteil geben Sie den Stil an, ohne auf Ihren Komfort zu verzichten. Valorisieren Sie den grafischen Denim-Trend mit diesem femininen High Fashion Cropped-Modell.</i18n_description_de>
  <i18n_description_nl>De Rozie Cropped Micro Geometric Print is A very expensive brand’s nieuwe High Waist Slim fit, die het been langer doet lijken en in het teken van geometrisch denim staat. De Rozie heeft een strakke, recht uitlopende pijp en een hoge taille en zorgt zo voor een slank en geraffineerd silhouet.  Het logo op de achterzak verhoogt de verrassende 7FAM identiteit. Net genoeg stretch geeft dit model enorm draagcomfort. Stort je in de grafische denimtrend met deze high-fashion, vrouwelijke cropped jeans.</i18n_description_nl>
  <i18n_description_fr>Le Rozie Cropped version Micro Geometric Print est le nouveau jean slim taille haute de A very expensive brand. Ce modèle qui allonge visuellement la jambe est ici présenté dans une version surfant sur la vague des denims géométriques et sur mesure. Les jambes slim et droites du Rozie s'associent à une taille haute féminine pour créer une silhouette épurée, sophistiquée et allongeant joliment la jambe.  Le logo emblématique sur la poche arrière accentue encore l'identité résolument 7FAM de ce modèle. Et avec juste ce qu'il faut de stretch, marquer la mode de votre empreinte devient tout simplement hyperconfortable. Adoptez la tendance des denims graphiques dans ce pantalon court très mode et féminin.</i18n_description_fr>
  <i18n_description_it>Il Rozie Cropped Micro Geometric Print è il nuovo fit di A very expensive brand che allunga visibilmente la gamba e riassume in sé le ultimissime tendenze geometriche e del denim su misura. Il Rozie ha gamba dritta e asciutta che si coniuga con una vita alta e femminile, per donare una linea dritta e sofisticata, con un bellissimo effetto slanciato della gamba. Il logo ricamato sulla tasca posteriore sottolinea la spiccata personalità di 7FAM. Con la giusta percentuale di stretch potrete lasciare un’impronta di stile senza rinunciare al comfort. Valorizzate la tendenza del denim grafico con questo modello cropped femminile e di alta moda.</i18n_description_it>
  <i18n_description_es>The Rozie Cropped Micro Geometric Print is A very expensive brand’s new and leg-lengthening High Waist Slim fit, seen here channelling the geometric and bespoke denim trends. The Rozie has a slim, straight leg that combines with a feminine high waist to give a sleek, sophisticated and beautifully leg-lengthening silhouette. The signature squiggle on the back pocket enhances the striking 7FAM identity. Just enough stretch means making your fashion mark is effortlessly comfortable. Shape up to the graphic denim trend in this high-fashion and feminine cropped style.</i18n_description_es>
  <i18n_short_description>ROZIE CROPPED  MICRO GEOMETRIC PRINT</i18n_short_description>
  <i18n_short_description_de>ROZIE CROPPED  MICRO GEOMETRIC PRINT</i18n_short_description_de>
  <i18n_short_description_nl>ROZIE CROPPED  MICRO GEOMETRIC PRINT</i18n_short_description_nl>
  <i18n_short_description_fr>ROZIE CROPPED  MICRO GEOMETRIC PRINT</i18n_short_description_fr>
  <i18n_short_description_it>ROZIE CROPPED  MICRO GEOMETRIC PRINT</i18n_short_description_it>
  <i18n_short_description_es>ROZIE CROPPED  MICRO GEOMETRIC PRINT</i18n_short_description_es>
  <i18n_product_details>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Measurements based on Size 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Approx. inseam: 29in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rise: Front: 8in Back: 12 1/2in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leg opening: 10 1/2in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Measurements may vary based on size, fabric and wash&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;62% Cotton, 38% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A very expensive brand's signature squiggle back pocket&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zip fly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;High waist&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Made in Europe using original and handcrafted finishing techniques</i18n_product_details>
  <i18n_product_details_de>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Maße basieren auf Größe 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Beinlänge ca. 74cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leibhöhe: Vorne: 20cm Hinten: 32cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fussweite: 26.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Die Maße können je nach Größe, Material und Waschung variieren&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;62% Baumwolle, 38% SpandexDie Signature Squiggle Backpocket von A very expensive brand&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Reisverschlussleiste&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hohe Leibhöhe&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Made in Europe unter Verwendung von Original-und Handarbeit Veredelungstechniken&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_de>
  <i18n_product_details_nl>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Afmetingen gebaseerd op maat 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Binnenbeenlengte ca. 74cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Kruisnaad: Voor: 20cm Achter: 32cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zoomwijdte: 26.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Afmetingen kunnen variëren op basis van maat, stof en wassing&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;62% Katoen, 38% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A very expensive brand's signature squiggle achterzak&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ritssluiting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hoge taille&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gemaakt in Europa met behulp van originele en ambachtelijke afwerkingstechnieken&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_nl>
  <i18n_product_details_fr>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mesures sur la base de la taille 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Inseam: sur  74cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fourche: Avant: 20cm Arriere: 32cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ouverture des jambes: 26.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Les mesures peuvent varier en fonction de la taille, du tissu et du lavage&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;62% Coton, 38% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A very expensive brand's squiggle poche&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fermeture Zip&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hohe Leibhöhe&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fabriqué en Europe avec des techniques de finitions artisanales&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_fr>
  <i18n_product_details_it>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Misure basate sulla taglia 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lunghezza dal cavallo alla caviglia: circa  74cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lunghezza dal cavallo alla vita:  Davanti: 20cm Dietro: 32cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Apertura gamba: 26.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Le misure possono variare in base alla taglia, al tessuto e al lavaggio&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;62% Cotone, 38% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tasca dietro: A very expensive brand's squiggle&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cerniera lampo&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vita allta&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Realizzato in Europa utilizzando tecniche di finitura artigianali &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_it>
  <i18n_product_details_es>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Medidas basadas en la Talla 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tiro aproximado: 29in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tiro: Frontal: 8in Trasero: 12 1/2in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Abertura de la pierna: 10 1/2in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Las medidas pueden variar dependiendo de la talla, material y teñido&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;62% Algodón, 38% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zip fly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cintura alta&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fabricado en Europa utilizando técnicas de acabado originales y artesanas.</i18n_product_details_es>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit>The Rozie is our sexy high waisted slim fit, featuring the A very expensive brand signature squiggle. The modern overall slim silhouette, combined with the leg-lengthening inseam, provides a sleek and sophisticated look. This fit is  also offered in a cropped version, which is perfect for the spring season and to be worn with flat summer sandals.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_de>Rozie ist unsere sexy High-Waist Slim Fit mit dekoriertem A very expensive brand Logo. Die in der ganzen Länge eng anliegende Jeans und die beinstreckende Naht an der Innenbeinlänge sorgen für einen garantiert anspruchsvollen und verführerischen Look. Es gibt sie auch in der Cropped-Variante: Ein perfekter Frühlingslook zum Tragen mit flachen Sommersandalen.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_de>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_nl>De Rozie is onze sexy slim fit met hoge taille en de A very expensive brand signature squiggle. Het moderne slanke silhouet zorgt in combinatie met de pijpen die het been langer doen lijken voor een chique, geraffineerde look. Er is ook een kortere uitvoering van het model verkrijgbaar dat perfect is voor het lenteseizoen en met platte sandalen wordt gedragen.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_nl>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_fr>Le Rozie est notre jean slim à taille haute. Très sexy, vous y retrouverez le logo emblématique de A very expensive brand. Sa silhouette moderne, slim de haut en bas, s'associe à une longueur qui allonge visuellement la jambe pour vous faire un look épuré et sophistiqué. Cette coupe est également disponible en version courte, idéale pour porter au printemps ou avec des sandales plates estivales.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_fr>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_it>Rozie è il nostro slim fit, sexy a vita alta con logo decorato A very expensive brand. La vestibilità attillata su tutta la lunghezza e la cucitura interna che slancia la gamba regalano un look sofisticato e seducente. E' disponibile anche in versione cropped, perfetta per la primavera e da indossare con sandali piatti estivi.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_it>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_es>The Rozie is our sexy high waisted slim fit, featuring the A very expensive brand signature squiggle. The modern overall slim silhouette, combined with the leg-lengthening inseam, provides a sleek and sophisticated look. This fit is  also offered in a cropped version, which is perfect for the spring season and to be worn with flat summer sandals.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_es>
  <price>240</price>
  <price_uk>220</price_uk>
  <price_de>240</price_de>
  <price_be>240</price_be>
  <price_nl>240</price_nl>
  <price_fr>240</price_fr>
  <price_it>240</price_it>
  <price_pan_en>240</price_pan_en>
  <price_pan_es>240</price_pan_es>
  <price_pan_fr>240</price_pan_fr>
  <price_pan_de>240</price_pan_de>
  <special_price></special_price>
  <special_from_date></special_from_date>
  <special_to_date></special_to_date>
  <special_price_uk></special_price_uk>
  <special_from_date_uk></special_from_date_uk>
  <special_to_date_uk></special_to_date_uk>
  <special_price_de></special_price_de>
  <special_from_date_de></special_from_date_de>
  <special_to_date_de></special_to_date_de>
  <special_price_nl></special_price_nl>
  <special_from_date_nl></special_from_date_nl>
  <special_to_date_nl></special_to_date_nl>
  <special_price_be></special_price_be>
  <special_from_date_be></special_from_date_be>
  <special_to_date_be></special_to_date_be>
  <special_price_fr></special_price_fr>
  <special_from_date_fr></special_from_date_fr>
  <special_to_date_fr></special_to_date_fr>
  <special_price_it></special_price_it>
  <special_from_date_it></special_from_date_it>
  <special_to_date_it></special_to_date_it>
  <special_price_pan_en></special_price_pan_en>
  <special_from_date_pan_en></special_from_date_pan_en>
  <special_to_date_pan_en></special_to_date_pan_en>
  <special_price_pan_es></special_price_pan_es>
  <special_from_date_pan_es></special_from_date_pan_es>
  <special_to_date_pan_es></special_to_date_pan_es>
  <special_price_pan_fr></special_price_pan_fr>
  <special_from_date_pan_fr></special_from_date_pan_fr>
  <special_to_date_pan_fr></special_to_date_pan_fr>
  <special_price_pan_de></special_price_pan_de>
  <special_from_date_pan_de></special_from_date_pan_de>
  <special_to_date_pan_de></special_to_date_pan_de>
  <news_from_date>2012-10-28</news_from_date>
  <image_front>SVYK110GR_front.jpg</image_front>
  <image_back>SVYK110GR_back.jpg</image_back>
  <image_pocket>SVYK110GR_pocket.jpg</image_pocket>
  <image_wash>SVYK110GR_wash.jpg</image_wash>
  <small_image></small_image>
  <thumbnail></thumbnail>
  <url_key></url_key>
  <color></color>
  <bubble_new_collection></bubble_new_collection>
  <bubble_sale></bubble_sale>
  <bubble_best_seller></bubble_best_seller>
  <bubble_limited_edition></bubble_limited_edition>
  <gender>Women</gender>
  <fit_group>STRAIGHT</fit_group>
  <fit_code>ROZIE</fit_code>
  <wash_group>DARK WASH</wash_group>
  <enable_special_area>No</enable_special_area>
  <special_area_static_block_id></special_area_static_block_id>
  <delivery_return_static_block_id>product_tab_delivery_return</delivery_return_static_block_id>
  <status>Disabled</status>
  <visibility>Nowhere</visibility>
  <super_attributes>size</super_attributes>
  <website>base</website>
  <category_ids></category_ids>
  <main_cat_seo></main_cat_seo>
  <details_care></details_care>
</configurable>
