<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<configurable>
  <sku>SMY33A0AC</sku>
  <i18n_name>AUSTYN WITH OFF REGISTER SQUIGGLE CALIFORNIA DUSK</i18n_name>
  <i18n_name_de>AUSTYN WITH OFF REGISTER SQUIGGLE CALIFORNIA DUSK</i18n_name_de>
  <i18n_name_nl>AUSTYN WITH OFF REGISTER SQUIGGLE CALIFORNIA DUSK</i18n_name_nl>
  <i18n_name_fr>AUSTYN WITH OFF REGISTER SQUIGGLE CALIFORNIA DUSK</i18n_name_fr>
  <i18n_name_it>AUSTYN WITH OFF REGISTER SQUIGGLE CALIFORNIA DUSK</i18n_name_it>
  <i18n_name_es>AUSTYN WITH OFF REGISTER SQUIGGLE CALIFORNIA DUSK</i18n_name_es>
  <product_start_date>2012-04-01</product_start_date>
  <product_end_date>2017-05-02</product_end_date>
  <i18n_description>The Austyn Off Register Squiggle California Dusk is A very expensive brand’s relaxed straight leg jean for men in a dark blue, worn-look denim with a distinctively modern cast. A more relaxed version of our Standard, this fit is roomier through the hip and thigh with a true-to-size waist and a straight leg shape. A very expensive brand’s California Dusk wash is stonewashed with a unique brown/orange tint visible inside the garment. 3D whiskers, chevrons and starbursts create distinctive highs and lows while grinding on pockets and bottom hem add to the well worn look. Classic orange and yellow stitching along with brass hardware complete this authentic wash. Kick back in this easy-going men’s jean that refuses to compromise your fashion credentials.</i18n_description>
  <i18n_description_de>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Die Austyn Off Register Squiggle California Dusk ist A very expensive brands lässige Straight Leg für Herren in einem dunkelblauen Worn-in-Denim mit echt modernem Schimmer&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;legere Version unseres Standard-Modells&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;etwas weiter geschnitten an Hüfte und Oberschenkeln&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;mit passgenauer Leibhöhe und geradem Bein&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A very expensive brands California Dusk Wash mit Stonewash und von innen sichtbarem, einzigartigem Braun-/Orangeton&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sitzfalten, Chevrons und Starbursts in 3D erzeugen einmalige Höhen und Tiefen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;die abgeriebenen Stellen an den Taschen und dem unteren Saum sorgen für einen coolen Used-Look&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;klassische orangefarbene und gelbe Nähte sowie Messingverzierungen runden diese authentische Waschung ab&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;entspannen Sie sich mit dieser lässigen Herrenjeans, mit der Sie keine Fashionpoints einbüßen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_description_de>
  <i18n_description_nl>De Austyn Off Register Squiggle California Dusk is de vlotte mannenjeans met rechte pijpen van A very expensive brand in donkerblauwe, afgedragen denim met een bijzonder moderne kleur. Dit model is een relaxtere uitvoering van onze Standard, is ruimer rond de heupen en dijen en heeft een maatzuivere taille en rechte pijpen. De California Dusk-wassing van 7FAM is gestonewashed met een unieke bruin/oranje tint die ook aan de binnenkant zichtbaar is. 3D-strepen, kepers en sterren creëren een mooi contrast tussen donker en licht en schuurvlekken op de zakken en de onderzoom zorgen voor een mooie afgedragen look. De klassieke oranje en gele stiksels en de koperen knopen passen mooi bij de authentieke wassing. Relax in deze ongedwongen mannenjeans met hoog fashiongehalte.</i18n_description_nl>
  <i18n_description_fr>Le jean Austyn version California Dusk avec logo relooké associe la coupe droite décontractée de A very expensive brand pour homme à un denim bleu foncé à l’aspect usé ultra-moderne. Plus casual que le modèle Standard, il est élargi sur les hanches et les cuisses mais conserve une taille parfaitement ajustée et un tombé bien droit. Le lavage California Dusk est délavé et arbore une teinte brun orangé unique, visible sur le revers. Les whiskers en relief, les marques chevrons et les effets d’usure en étoile créent un effet dégradé, complétés par des marques de vieillissement sur les poches et l’ourlet inférieur qui viennent parfaire le look usé de l’ensemble. Des surpiqûres classiques orange et jaunes et des détails cuivrés apportent la touche finale à ce lavage qui respire l’authenticité. Craquez pour ce modèle masculin à la fois décontracté et très tendance.</i18n_description_fr>
  <i18n_description_it>Voglia di un look moderno? Austyn Off Register Squiggle California Dusk di A very expensive brand è un confortevole jeans da uomo a gamba dritta in un denim blu scuro dall’aria vissuta. Più easy rispetto al modello Standard, questo pantalone ha una vita normale ed è più ampio su fianchi e cosce. Il lavaggio stone washed California Dusk consente di ottenere un’esclusiva tinta marrone/arancio visibile nella parte interna. I baffi in 3D, le striature e gli effetti starburst creano esclusivi giochi di colore, mentre le abrasioni sulle tasche e sull’orlo rafforzano l’aspetto used. Le classiche cuciture giallo/arancio e i dettagli in ottone completano questo denim autentico. Cercate un modello easy senza compromessi in fatto di moda? Austyn Off Register Squiggle California Dusk fa al caso vostro.</i18n_description_it>
  <i18n_description_es>The Austyn Off Register Squiggle California Dusk is A very expensive brand’s relaxed straight leg jean for men in a dark blue, worn-look denim with a distinctively modern cast. A more relaxed version of our Standard, this fit is roomier through the hip and thigh with a true-to-size waist and a straight leg shape. A very expensive brand’s California Dusk wash is stonewashed with a unique brown/orange tint visible inside the garment. 3D whiskers, chevrons and starbursts create distinctive highs and lows while grinding on pockets and bottom hem add to the well worn look. Classic orange and yellow stitching along with brass hardware complete this authentic wash. Kick back in this easy-going men’s jean that refuses to compromise your fashion credentials.</i18n_description_es>
  <i18n_short_description>AUSTYN WITH OFF REGISTER SQUIGGLE CALIFORNIA DUSK</i18n_short_description>
  <i18n_short_description_de>AUSTYN WITH OFF REGISTER SQUIGGLE CALIFORNIA DUSK</i18n_short_description_de>
  <i18n_short_description_nl>AUSTYN WITH OFF REGISTER SQUIGGLE CALIFORNIA DUSK</i18n_short_description_nl>
  <i18n_short_description_fr>AUSTYN WITH OFF REGISTER SQUIGGLE CALIFORNIA DUSK</i18n_short_description_fr>
  <i18n_short_description_it>AUSTYN WITH OFF REGISTER SQUIGGLE CALIFORNIA DUSK</i18n_short_description_it>
  <i18n_short_description_es>AUSTYN WITH OFF REGISTER SQUIGGLE CALIFORNIA DUSK</i18n_short_description_es>
  <i18n_product_details>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Approx. inseam: 33 1/2in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rise: Front: 8 3/4in Back: 14 1/4in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leg opening: 18in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;100% Cotton &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A very expensive brand's signature squiggle back pocket&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zip fly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details>
  <i18n_product_details_de>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Beinlänge ca.  85cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leibhöhe: Vorne: 22cm Hinten: 36cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fussweite: 46cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;100% Baumwolle &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Die Signature Squiggle Backpocket von A very expensive brand&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Reisverschlussleiste&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_de>
  <i18n_product_details_nl>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Binnenbeenlengte ca.  85cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Kruisnaad: Voor: 22cm Achter: 36cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zoomwijdte: 46cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;100% Katoen &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A very expensive brand's signature squiggle achterzak&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ritssluiting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_nl>
  <i18n_product_details_fr>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Inseam: sur  85cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fourche: Avant: 22cm Arrière: 36cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ouverture des jambes: 46cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;100% Coton &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A very expensive brand's squiggle poche&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fermeture Zip&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_fr>
  <i18n_product_details_it>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lunghezza dal cavallo alla caviglia: circa  85cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lunghezza dal cavallo alla vita: Davanti: 22cm Dietro: 36cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Apertura gamba: 46cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;100% Cotone &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tasca Dietro: A very expensive brand's squiggle&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cerniera lampo&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_it>
  <i18n_product_details_es>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tiro aproximado: 33 1/2in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tiro: Frontal: 8 3/4in Trasero: 14 1/4in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Abertura de la pierna: 18in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;100% Algodón &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zip fly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_es>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit>The Austyn is our relaxed straight leg jean. A more relaxed version of our Standard, this fit is roomier through the hip and thigh with a true-to-size waist and a straight leg shape. The Austyn features a zip fly and is offered in a variety of back pockets and stitching designs.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_de>Austyn ist unsere legere Straight Leg Jeans. Gerade geschnitten, aber im Gegensatz zu unserem Modell Standard etwas lockerer an Hüfte und Oberschenkeln geschnitten. Mit Reissverschluss und in verschiedenen Taschendesigns erhältlich.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_de>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_nl>De Austyn is onze relaxed straightleg-jeans. Deze fit is ruimer aan heup en dij, met een true-to-size middel en met rechte pijp. De Austyn heeft een ritssluiting en is verkrijgbaar met allerhande designs op de achterzakken en met verschillende stiksels.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_nl>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_fr>L’Austyn est un jean droit très confortable. Encore plus décontractée que notre jean Standard, cette coupe est plus ample au niveau des hanches et des cuisses, ajustée à la taille et droite sur les jambes. Dotée d’une fermeture zippée, elle est proposée avec divers types de poches arrière et de surpiqûres.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_fr>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_it>Austyn è un jeans confortevole a gamba dritta. Più easy rispetto al modello Standard, questo pantalone ha una vita normale ed è più ampio su fianchi e cosce. Austyn si distingue per la chiusura a zip e offre un’ampia varietà di cuciture e tasche posteriori.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_it>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_es>The Austyn is our relaxed straight leg jean. A more relaxed version of our Standard, this fit is roomier through the hip and thigh with a true-to-size waist and a straight leg shape. The Austyn features a zip fly and is offered in a variety of back pockets and stitching designs.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_es>
  <price>219</price>
  <price_uk>200</price_uk>
  <price_de>219</price_de>
  <price_be>219</price_be>
  <price_nl>219</price_nl>
  <price_fr>153</price_fr>
  <price_it>219</price_it>
  <price_pan_en>219</price_pan_en>
  <price_pan_es>219</price_pan_es>
  <price_pan_fr>219</price_pan_fr>
  <price_pan_de>219</price_pan_de>
  <special_price></special_price>
  <special_from_date></special_from_date>
  <special_to_date></special_to_date>
  <special_price_uk></special_price_uk>
  <special_from_date_uk></special_from_date_uk>
  <special_to_date_uk></special_to_date_uk>
  <special_price_de></special_price_de>
  <special_from_date_de></special_from_date_de>
  <special_to_date_de></special_to_date_de>
  <special_price_nl></special_price_nl>
  <special_from_date_nl></special_from_date_nl>
  <special_to_date_nl></special_to_date_nl>
  <special_price_be></special_price_be>
  <special_from_date_be></special_from_date_be>
  <special_to_date_be></special_to_date_be>
  <special_price_fr></special_price_fr>
  <special_from_date_fr></special_from_date_fr>
  <special_to_date_fr></special_to_date_fr>
  <special_price_it></special_price_it>
  <special_from_date_it></special_from_date_it>
  <special_to_date_it></special_to_date_it>
  <special_price_pan_en></special_price_pan_en>
  <special_from_date_pan_en></special_from_date_pan_en>
  <special_to_date_pan_en></special_to_date_pan_en>
  <special_price_pan_es></special_price_pan_es>
  <special_from_date_pan_es></special_from_date_pan_es>
  <special_to_date_pan_es></special_to_date_pan_es>
  <special_price_pan_fr></special_price_pan_fr>
  <special_from_date_pan_fr></special_from_date_pan_fr>
  <special_to_date_pan_fr></special_to_date_pan_fr>
  <special_price_pan_de></special_price_pan_de>
  <special_from_date_pan_de></special_from_date_pan_de>
  <special_to_date_pan_de></special_to_date_pan_de>
  <news_from_date>2012-04-01</news_from_date>
  <image_front>SMY33A0AC_front.jpg</image_front>
  <image_back>SMY33A0AC_back.jpg</image_back>
  <image_pocket>SMY33A0AC_pocket.jpg</image_pocket>
  <image_wash>SMY33A0AC_wash.jpg</image_wash>
  <small_image></small_image>
  <thumbnail></thumbnail>
  <url_key></url_key>
  <color></color>
  <bubble_new_collection></bubble_new_collection>
  <bubble_sale></bubble_sale>
  <bubble_best_seller></bubble_best_seller>
  <bubble_limited_edition></bubble_limited_edition>
  <gender>Men</gender>
  <fit_group>STRAIGHT</fit_group>
  <fit_code>AUSTYN</fit_code>
  <wash_group>DARK WASH</wash_group>
  <enable_special_area>No</enable_special_area>
  <special_area_static_block_id></special_area_static_block_id>
  <delivery_return_static_block_id>product_tab_delivery_return</delivery_return_static_block_id>
  <status>Disabled</status>
  <visibility>Nowhere</visibility>
  <super_attributes>size</super_attributes>
  <website>base</website>
  <category_ids></category_ids>
  <main_cat_seo></main_cat_seo>
  <details_care></details_care>
</configurable>
