<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<configurable>
  <sku>SL6J63SEY</sku>
  <i18n_name>KAYLIE SEALBAY</i18n_name>
  <i18n_name_de>KAYLIE SEALBAY</i18n_name_de>
  <i18n_name_nl>KAYLIE SEALBAY</i18n_name_nl>
  <i18n_name_fr>KAYLIE SEALBAY</i18n_name_fr>
  <i18n_name_it>KAYLIE SEALBAY</i18n_name_it>
  <i18n_name_es>KAYLIE SEALBAY</i18n_name_es>
  <product_start_date>2012-01-01</product_start_date>
  <product_end_date>2017-05-01</product_end_date>
  <i18n_description>The Kaylie Sealbay jean for women is a sexy, slim fit bootcut in a fabulous clean white wash. A very expensive brand’s Kaylie has a classic rise that fits and flatters every body type. Hugging the body through the hip and thigh, this fit continues to be slim through the knee and breaks at the calf into a bootcut leg opening, creating a dramatic, leg-lengthening silhouette. Fused with this look-at-me white denim with contrast black labels, this is a seductive women’s jean. The simplicity of this denim is all the more enticing thanks to an amazingly soft handfeel. Team it with statement wedges and strut into cocktail hour.</i18n_description>
  <i18n_description_de>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;die Kaylie Sealbay Damenjeans ist eine sexy, Slim-Fit Bootcut in einer fantastisch-makellosen weißen Waschung&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;die Kaylie von A very expensive brand hat eine klassische Leibhöhe, die einfach jede Körperform perfekt in Szene setzt&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;umschmeichelt den Körper an Hüfte und Oberschenkeln&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;der Fit ist bis über das Knie schmal geschnitten und geht ab der Wade in einen Bootcut über&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;für eine atemberaubende, beinstreckende Silhouette&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;plus auffälliges weißes Denim und schwarze Kontrastlabels = eine absolut verführerische Damenjeans&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;weniger ist mehr: dieses Denim ist schlicht umwerfend und wunderschön weich&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;mit auffälligen Wedges sind Sie startklar für einen stylishen Aperitif&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_description_de>
  <i18n_description_nl>De Kaylie Sealbay vrouwenjeans is een sexy, slim fit bootcut met een fantastisch strakke witte wassing. De Kaylie van A very expensive brand heeft een klassieke heuplijn die elk lichaamstype eer aandoet en altijd goed zit. De Kaylie sluit nauw aan op heup en dij, blijft slank tot over de knieën en waaiert vanaf de kuit uit aan de onderpijpen, wat zorgt voor een opvallend silhouet dat de lengte van de benen benadrukt. Deze aantrekkelijke witte denim heeft contrasterende zwarte labels, wat het tot een uitdagende vrouwenjeans maakt. De eenvoud van deze denim wordt nog aantrekkelijker door de heerlijk zachte stof. Combineer hem met sleehakken en je hebt de ideale outfit voor het cocktailuurtje.</i18n_description_nl>
  <i18n_description_fr>Avec le Kaylie version Sealbay, 7FAM vous propose un modèle bootcut slim sexy dans un lavage blanc éclatant. Le Kaylie repose sur la taille naturelle pour mettre en valeur toutes les silhouettes. Sa coupe, serrée au niveau des hanches et des cuisses, est encore slim jusqu’aux genoux puis finit en bootcut à partir du mollet pour des jambes interminables. Dans cette version en denim blanc irrésistible agrémenté d’étiquettes noires en contraste, c’est le jean sexy pour femme par excellence. Difficile de se passer de ce tissu simple et incroyablement doux au toucher. À porter avec des semelles compensées tendance pour une tenue de cocktail toute trouvée !</i18n_description_fr>
  <i18n_description_it>Il jeans da donna Kaylie Sealbay è un bootcut sexy e aderente in un favoloso lavaggio bianco dalle linee pulite. Dalla vita classica, Kaylie di A very expensive brand sta bene proprio a tutte. Aderente attorno a fianchi, cosce e ginocchia, questo modello si allarga all'altezza del polpaccio come un bootcut, dando l'impressione di avere gambe più lunghe. Con le etichette nere in contrasto con il denim bianco, i jeans Kaylie Sealbay attirano tutti gli sguardi. Straordinariamente morbido al tatto, questo denim semplice, ma attraente, può essere abbinato a un paio di zeppe alte per un happy hour da vere protagoniste.</i18n_description_it>
  <i18n_description_es>The Kaylie Sealbay jean for women is a sexy, slim fit bootcut in a fabulous clean white wash. A very expensive brand’s Kaylie has a classic rise that fits and flatters every body type. Hugging the body through the hip and thigh, this fit continues to be slim through the knee and breaks at the calf into a bootcut leg opening, creating a dramatic, leg-lengthening silhouette. Fused with this look-at-me white denim with contrast black labels, this is a seductive women’s jean. The simplicity of this denim is all the more enticing thanks to an amazingly soft handfeel. Team it with statement wedges and strut into cocktail hour.</i18n_description_es>
  <i18n_short_description>KAYLIE SEALBAY</i18n_short_description>
  <i18n_short_description_de>KAYLIE SEALBAY</i18n_short_description_de>
  <i18n_short_description_nl>KAYLIE SEALBAY</i18n_short_description_nl>
  <i18n_short_description_fr>KAYLIE SEALBAY</i18n_short_description_fr>
  <i18n_short_description_it>KAYLIE SEALBAY</i18n_short_description_it>
  <i18n_short_description_es>KAYLIE SEALBAY</i18n_short_description_es>
  <i18n_product_details>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Approx. inseam: 35in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rise: Front: 6 7/8in Back: 11 1/2in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leg opening: 19 1/2in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Cotton 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A very expensive brand's signature squiggle back pocket&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zip Fly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Made in Europe using original and handcrafted finishing techniques&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details>
  <i18n_product_details_de>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Beinlänge ca. : 89cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leibhöhe: Vorne: 17.5cm Hinten: 29cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fussweite: 49.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Baumwolle 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Die Signature Squiggle Backpocket von A very expensive brand&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Reisverschlussleiste&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Made in Europe unter Verwendung von Original-und Handarbeit Veredelungstechniken&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_de>
  <i18n_product_details_nl>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Binnenbeenlengte ca. : 89cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Kruisnaad: Voor: 17.5cm Achter: 29cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zoomwijdte: 49.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Katoen 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A very expensive brand's signature squiggle achterzak&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ritssluiting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gemaakt in Europa met behulp van originele en ambachtelijke afwerkingstechnieken&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_nl>
  <i18n_product_details_fr>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Inseam: sur 89cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fourche: Avant: 17.5cm Arriere: 29cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ouverture des jambes: 49.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Coton 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A very expensive brand's squiggle poche&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fermeture Zip&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fabriqué en Europe avec des techniques de finitions artisanales&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_fr>
  <i18n_product_details_it>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lunghezza dal cavallo alla caviglia: circa 89cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lunghezza dal cavallo alla vita: Davanti: 17.5cm Dietro: 29cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Apertura gamba: 49.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Cotone 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tasca Dietro: A very expensive brand's squiggle&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cerniera lampo&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Realizzato in Europa utilizzando tecniche di finitura artigianali&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_it>
  <i18n_product_details_es>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tiro aproximado: 35in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tiro: Frontal: 6 7/8in Trasero: 11 1/2in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Abertura de la pierna: 19 1/2in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Algodón 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cremallera&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fabricado en Europa utilizando técnicas de acabado originales y artesanas.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_es>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit>The Kaylie is A very expensive brand’s sexy, new slim fit boot designed to flatter every body type and give the appearance of mile-long legs. This 5-pocket jean featuresa classic rise and hugs the body through the hip, thigh,and knee. It breaks at the calf into a bootcut leg opening,creating a dramatic silhouette that lengthens the leg andlooks modern and fresh. The Kaylie features the 7 For AllMankind signature squiggle.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_de>Die Kaylie ist A very expensive brands neuer sexy Slim-Fit Bootcut, der jede Figur von ihrer besten Seite zeigt und endlos lange Beine zaubert. Diese 5-Pocket Jeans hat eine klassische Leibhöhe und umschmeichelt Hüfte, Oberschenkel und Knie. Ab der Wade geht der Schnitt in einen Bootcut über und kreiert eine atemberaubende, beinstreckende Silhouette mit einem frischen, modernen Look. Die Kaylie hat das original A very expensive brand Signature Squiggle.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_de>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_nl>De Kaylie is de sexy nieuwe slim fit bootcut van A very expensive brand, ontworpen om elk lichaamstype eer aan te doen en je benen eindeloos te laten lijken. Deze jeans met 5 zakken heeft een klassieke heuplijn en sluit nauw aan op de heup, dij en knie. Het model waaiert vanaf de kuit uit aan de onderpijpen, wat zorgt voor een opvallend silhouet dat de lengte van de benen benadrukt en modern en fris oogt. De Kaylie is voorzien van de A very expensive brand signature squiggle.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_nl>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_fr>Le Kaylie est le nouveau jean slim boot très sexy de A very expensive brand, idéal pour avantager toutes les silhouettes en donnant l’impression de jambes interminables. Ce jean 5 poches reposant sur la taille naturelle moule parfaitement les hanches, les cuisses et les genoux puis se termine en bootcut à partir du mollet pour allonger les jambes. Résultat : une silhouette impeccable empreinte de fraîcheur et de modernité. Les poches arrière du Kaylie sont ornées du logo brodé A very expensive brand.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_fr>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_it>Kaylie è un nuovo bootcut sexy e aderente, creato da A very expensive brand per esaltare le forme e dare l’impressione di avere gambe chilometriche. Questi jeans a cinque tasche dalla vita classica avvolgono fianchi, cosce e ginocchia. All’altezza del polpaccio si allargano come un bootcut, creando una splendida silhouette che dà l’impressione di avere gambe più lunghe, per un look moderno e innovativo. Naturalmente, anche sul modello Kaylie spicca il logo ricamato di A very expensive brand.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_it>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_es>The Kaylie is A very expensive brand’s sexy, new slim fit boot designed to flatter every body type and give the appearance of mile-long legs. This 5-pocket jean featuresa classic rise and hugs the body through the hip, thigh,and knee. It breaks at the calf into a bootcut leg opening,creating a dramatic silhouette that lengthens the leg andlooks modern and fresh. The Kaylie features the 7 For AllMankind signature squiggle.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_es>
  <price>219</price>
  <price_uk>200</price_uk>
  <price_de>219</price_de>
  <price_be>219</price_be>
  <price_nl>219</price_nl>
  <price_fr>76</price_fr>
  <price_it>219</price_it>
  <price_pan_en>219</price_pan_en>
  <price_pan_es>219</price_pan_es>
  <price_pan_fr>219</price_pan_fr>
  <price_pan_de>219</price_pan_de>
  <special_price></special_price>
  <special_from_date></special_from_date>
  <special_to_date></special_to_date>
  <special_price_uk></special_price_uk>
  <special_from_date_uk></special_from_date_uk>
  <special_to_date_uk></special_to_date_uk>
  <special_price_de></special_price_de>
  <special_from_date_de></special_from_date_de>
  <special_to_date_de></special_to_date_de>
  <special_price_nl></special_price_nl>
  <special_from_date_nl></special_from_date_nl>
  <special_to_date_nl></special_to_date_nl>
  <special_price_be></special_price_be>
  <special_from_date_be></special_from_date_be>
  <special_to_date_be></special_to_date_be>
  <special_price_fr></special_price_fr>
  <special_from_date_fr></special_from_date_fr>
  <special_to_date_fr></special_to_date_fr>
  <special_price_it></special_price_it>
  <special_from_date_it></special_from_date_it>
  <special_to_date_it></special_to_date_it>
  <special_price_pan_en></special_price_pan_en>
  <special_from_date_pan_en></special_from_date_pan_en>
  <special_to_date_pan_en></special_to_date_pan_en>
  <special_price_pan_es></special_price_pan_es>
  <special_from_date_pan_es></special_from_date_pan_es>
  <special_to_date_pan_es></special_to_date_pan_es>
  <special_price_pan_fr></special_price_pan_fr>
  <special_from_date_pan_fr></special_from_date_pan_fr>
  <special_to_date_pan_fr></special_to_date_pan_fr>
  <special_price_pan_de></special_price_pan_de>
  <special_from_date_pan_de></special_from_date_pan_de>
  <special_to_date_pan_de></special_to_date_pan_de>
  <news_from_date>2012-01-01</news_from_date>
  <image_front>SL6J63SEY_front.jpg</image_front>
  <image_back>SL6J63SEY_back.jpg</image_back>
  <image_pocket>SL6J63SEY_pocket.jpg</image_pocket>
  <image_wash>SL6J63SEY_wash.jpg</image_wash>
  <small_image></small_image>
  <thumbnail></thumbnail>
  <url_key></url_key>
  <color></color>
  <bubble_new_collection></bubble_new_collection>
  <bubble_sale></bubble_sale>
  <bubble_best_seller></bubble_best_seller>
  <bubble_limited_edition></bubble_limited_edition>
  <gender>Women</gender>
  <fit_group>TROUSER &amp; WIDE LEG</fit_group>
  <fit_code>KAYLIE</fit_code>
  <wash_group>light wash</wash_group>
  <enable_special_area>No</enable_special_area>
  <special_area_static_block_id></special_area_static_block_id>
  <delivery_return_static_block_id>product_tab_delivery_return</delivery_return_static_block_id>
  <status>Disabled</status>
  <visibility>Nowhere</visibility>
  <super_attributes>size</super_attributes>
  <website>base</website>
  <category_ids></category_ids>
  <main_cat_seo></main_cat_seo>
  <details_care></details_care>
</configurable>
