<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<configurable>
  <sku>SWTK15CGR</sku>
  <i18n_name>THE SKINNY WITH CRYSTALS ALL OVER GEOMETRIC GREY DENIM GREY</i18n_name>
  <i18n_name_de>THE SKINNY WITH CRYSTALS ALL OVER GEOMETRIC GREY DENIM GREY</i18n_name_de>
  <i18n_name_nl>THE SKINNY WITH CRYSTALS ALL OVER GEOMETRIC GREY DENIM GREY</i18n_name_nl>
  <i18n_name_fr>THE SKINNY WITH CRYSTALS ALL OVER GEOMETRIC GREY DENIM GREY</i18n_name_fr>
  <i18n_name_it>THE SKINNY WITH CRYSTALS ALL OVER GEOMETRIC GREY DENIM GREY</i18n_name_it>
  <i18n_name_es>THE SKINNY WITH CRYSTALS ALL OVER GEOMETRIC GREY DENIM GREY</i18n_name_es>
  <product_start_date>2012-10-28</product_start_date>
  <product_end_date>2019-10-02</product_end_date>
  <i18n_description>The Skinny with Crystals all over Geometric Grey Denim Grey is A very expensive brand’s body-sculpting women’s jean to make an impossible-to-miss geometric trend statement. The Skinny is a second-skin, super-stretch fit characterised by its minimal detailing, clean pockets, comfortable straight rise and a slim, sexy, fitted silhouette top to bottom. The length hits just below the ankle to maintain a clean line with no stacking. This provocative, street-savvy fit has head-turning power in this bespoke denim. The directional design is part of 7FAM’s collection inspired by city textures and geometrics. The lasered geometric print is overcoated, giving a cityscape sheen while the perfect amount of stretch makes this ultra-cool jean heavenly to wear. So, how to power your style with a meteoric mix of cool graphics, slick silhouettes and hi-tech fabrics? Team it with a longline or oversize buttoned up shirt, pull on your fiercest ankle boots and make a memorable edgy statement at cocktails.</i18n_description>
  <i18n_description_de>Die Skinny with Crystals all over Geometric Grey Denim Grey ist eine figurbetonende Damenjeans und eine absolut originelle Weise, den unverzichtbaren Trend der geometrischen Druckmuster zu interpretieren.  Diese Skinny von A very expensive brand formt die Silhouette mit ihrem Super-Stretch-Gewebe fast wie eine zweite Haut und besitzt minimalistische Details, sauber geschnittene Taschen, eine gerade und bequeme Leibhöhe und eine durchweg enganliegende, sexy und schlanke Linie.  Die Länge reicht knapp unter den Knöchel und sorgt für eine absolut saubere Linie. Dieser provokante Fit mit metropolitanem Charakter ist in diesem maßgeschneiderten Denim ein wahrer Blickfang.  Das ganz besondere Design gehört zur Kollektion von 7FAM, die sich an den metropolitanen Geometrien und Konsistenzen inspiriert. Der geometrische Laserdruck ist superbeschichtet, mit metropolitan wirkenden Reflexen, während das richtige Ausmaß an Stretch für einen sublimen Tragkomfort dieser prestigereichen Damenjeans sorgt.  Wie könnten Sie je einen besseren Stil haben als mit dieser funkelnden Mischung aus cooler Grafik, lockeren Linien und Hightech-Geweben?  Tragen Sie sie mit einer geknöpften langen oder Oversize-Bluse und Stiefeletten, dann bleibt Ihr Glam auf der Cocktailparty nicht unbemerkt.</i18n_description_de>
  <i18n_description_nl>De Skinny with Crystals all over Geometric Grey Denim Grey is A very expensive brand’s nauwsluitende vrouwenjeans waarmee je gevoel voor geometrie niet onopgemerkt gaat. De Skinny is een superstretch model dat aansluit als een tweede huid, met minimale details, sobere zakken en een comfortabele rechte heuplijn, en van top tot teen voor een slank en sexy silhouet zorgt. De jeans valt tot net onder de enkel voor een simpele lijn zonder kreukels. Het verleidelijke, streetwise model in een denim dat voor jou gemaakt lijkt, doet hoofden draaien. Het toonaangevende design maakt deel uit van 7FAM’s collectie die is geïnspireerd op stedelijke texturen en geometrische vormen. De gelaserde geometrische print krijgt door een coating een cityscape glans terwijl het perfecte stretchgehalte deze supercoole jeans enorm comfortabel maakt. En hoe draag je deze meteorische mix van grafische elementen, coole silhouetten en hightech stoffen? Met een lange of oversized bloes en stoere zul je menige cocktailparty opluisteren!</i18n_description_nl>
  <i18n_description_fr>Le Skinny version Crystals all over Geometric Grey Denim Grey de A very expensive brand est un jean femme qui épousera votre silhouette et vous fera un look géométrique tendance qui ne passera pas inaperçu. Le Skinny possède une coupe ultra-stretch seconde peau très flatteuse pour votre silhouette qui se distingue par ses détails minimalistes, ses poches nettes, sa taille droite et confortable et sa silhouette slim sexy et ajustée sur toute sa longueur. La longueur de jambe tombe juste en dessous de la cheville, pour un jean qui reste parfaitement clean et droit. Le denim sur mesure de cette coupe provocante et ultratendance a le pouvoir de faire tourner les têtes !  Ce modèle très mode fait partie de la collection imaginée par 7FAM pour s'inspirer des textures et formes géométriques urbaines. L'imprimé géométrique réalisé au laser est recouvert d'une enduction offrant un moiré résolument urbain, tandis que son élasticité justement dosée fait de ce jean femme ultracool une merveille à porter. Alors, envie de propulser votre style vers les étoiles à coups de graphismes cool, silhouettes épurées et matières high tech ? Associez-le à une chemise boutonnée longue ou oversize, enfilez vos boots les plus sauvages et affichez un look affirmé et pointu sur vos cocktails.</i18n_description_fr>
  <i18n_description_it>Lo Skinny with Crystals all over Geometric Grey Denim Grey è un jeans da donna che modella il fisico e interpreta in modo assolutamente originale  l’irrinunciabile tendenza delle stampe geometriche.  Lo Skinny di A very expensive brand modella la silhouette con il suo super-stretch, quasi una seconda pelle; è caratterizzato da dettagli minimal, tasche di linea pulita, vita dritta e confortevole e una linea  aderente, sexy e asciutta dall’alto in basso.  La lunghezza appena sotto la caviglia regala una linea decisamente pulita e senza arricciature. Questo fit provocante, declinato in questo denim su misura di carattere metropolitano è sicuramente capace di attrarre gli sguardi.  Il design originale fa parte della collezione di 7FAM ispirata a geometrie e texture metropolitani. La stampa geometrica laserata è super spalmata e manda riflessi di gusto urban, mentre la giusta percentuale di stretch regala a questo prestigioso jeans una vestibilità sublime.  Quale stile migliore di questo sfolgorante mix di grafica cool, linee sciolte e tessuti high tech?  Unitelo a una camicia di linea lunga oppure oversize, e infilateci dei tronchetti e il vostro fascino non passerà inosservato durante l' happy hour.</i18n_description_it>
  <i18n_description_es>The Skinny with Crystals all over Geometric Grey Denim Grey is A very expensive brand’s body-sculpting women’s jean to make an impossible-to-miss geometric trend statement. The Skinny is a second-skin, super-stretch fit characterised by its minimal detailing, clean pockets, comfortable straight rise and a slim, sexy, fitted silhouette top to bottom. The length hits just below the ankle to maintain a clean line with no stacking. This provocative, street-savvy fit has head-turning power in this bespoke denim. The directional design is part of 7FAM’s collection inspired by city textures and geometrics. The lasered geometric print is overcoated, giving a cityscape sheen while the perfect amount of stretch makes this ultra-cool jean heavenly to wear. So, how to power your style with a meteoric mix of cool graphics, slick silhouettes and hi-tech fabrics? Team it with a longline or oversize buttoned up shirt, pull on your fiercest ankle boots and make a memorable edgy statement at cocktails.</i18n_description_es>
  <i18n_short_description>THE SKINNY WITH CRYSTALS ALL OVER GEOMETRIC GREY DENIM GREY</i18n_short_description>
  <i18n_short_description_de>THE SKINNY WITH CRYSTALS ALL OVER GEOMETRIC GREY DENIM GREY</i18n_short_description_de>
  <i18n_short_description_nl>THE SKINNY WITH CRYSTALS ALL OVER GEOMETRIC GREY DENIM GREY</i18n_short_description_nl>
  <i18n_short_description_fr>THE SKINNY WITH CRYSTALS ALL OVER GEOMETRIC GREY DENIM GREY</i18n_short_description_fr>
  <i18n_short_description_it>THE SKINNY WITH CRYSTALS ALL OVER GEOMETRIC GREY DENIM GREY</i18n_short_description_it>
  <i18n_short_description_es>THE SKINNY WITH CRYSTALS ALL OVER GEOMETRIC GREY DENIM GREY</i18n_short_description_es>
  <i18n_product_details>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Measurements based on Size 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Approx. inseam: 30in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rise: Front: 7in Back: 11 1/2in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leg opening: 10 1/2in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Measurements may vary based on size, fabric and wash&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;88% Cotton, 10% Polyester, 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Clean pocket&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zip fly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Medium waist&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Made in Europe using original and handcrafted finishing techniques</i18n_product_details>
  <i18n_product_details_de>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Maße basieren auf Größe 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Beinlänge ca. 76cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leibhöhe: Vorne: 18cm Hinten: 29cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fussweite: 26.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Die Maße können je nach Größe, Material und Waschung variieren&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;88% Baumwolle, 10% Polyester, 2% SpandexClean Pocket&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Reisverschlussleiste&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Normale Leibhöhe&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Made in Europe unter Verwendung von Original-und Handarbeit Veredelungstechniken&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_de>
  <i18n_product_details_nl>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Afmetingen gebaseerd op maat 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Binnenbeenlengte ca. 76cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Kruisnaad: Voor: 18cm Achter: 29cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zoomwijdte: 26.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Afmetingen kunnen variëren op basis van maat, stof en wassing&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;88% Katoen, 10% Polyester, 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Achterzak zonder squiggle&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ritssluiting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Medium taille&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gemaakt in Europa met behulp van originele en ambachtelijke afwerkingstechnieken&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_nl>
  <i18n_product_details_fr>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mesures sur la base de la taille 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Inseam: sur  76cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fourche: Avant: 18cm Arriere: 29cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ouverture des jambes: 26.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Les mesures peuvent varier en fonction de la taille, du tissu et du lavage&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;88% Coton, 10% Polyester, 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Clean poche&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fermeture Zip&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Taille classique&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fabriqué en Europe avec des techniques de finitions artisanales&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_fr>
  <i18n_product_details_it>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Misure basate sulla taglia 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lunghezza dal cavallo alla caviglia: circa  76cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lunghezza dal cavallo alla vita:  Davanti: 18cm Dietro: 29cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Apertura gamba: 26.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Le misure possono variare in base alla taglia, al tessuto e al lavaggio&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;88% Cotone, 10% Poliestere, 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tasca dietro: liscia&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cerniera lampo&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vita normale&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Realizzato in Europa utilizzando tecniche di finitura artigianali &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_it>
  <i18n_product_details_es>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Medidas basadas en la Talla 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tiro aproximado: 30in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tiro: Frontal: 7in Trasero: 11 1/2in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Abertura de la pierna: 10 1/2in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Las medidas pueden variar dependiendo de la talla, material y teñido&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;88% Algodón, 10% Poliéster, 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Blosillo sin squiggle&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zip fly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cintura media&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fabricado en Europa utilizando técnicas de acabado originales y artesanas.</i18n_product_details_es>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit>Characterised by its minimal detailing, The Skinny has a comfortable rise with a slim, sexy, and fitted silhouette top to bottom. The length hits at the ankle to maintain a clean line with no stacking.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_de>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimalistische Verzierungen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;die Skinny hat eine bequeme Leibhöhe und eine durchweg schmale, sexy und eng anliegende Silhouette&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;endet kurz über dem Knöchel und garantiert einen cleanen Look mit schmaler Silhouette&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_de>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_nl>De Skinny wordt gekenmerkt door minimale details en heeft een comfortabele heuplijn met een slank, sexy en aansluitend silhouet van top tot teen. De lengte gaat mooi tot de enkel voor een pure lijn zonder kreuken.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_nl>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_fr>Orné de détails raffinés, le Skinny est confortable à la taille avec une coupe plus ajustée très sexy qui épouse à merveille l’ensemble de la silhouette. Son tombé bien ajusté jusqu’à la cheville lui confère une ligne impeccable et sans plis.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_fr>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_it>Il modello Skinny, con dettagli minimal e vita confortevole, disegna una figura sexy e sottile da capo a piedi! L’orlo arriva alla caviglia per un taglio deciso senza arricciature.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_it>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_es>Characterised by its minimal detailing, The Skinny has a comfortable rise with a slim, sexy, and fitted silhouette top to bottom. The length hits at the ankle to maintain a clean line with no stacking.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_es>
  <price>400</price>
  <price_uk>360</price_uk>
  <price_de>400</price_de>
  <price_be>400</price_be>
  <price_nl>400</price_nl>
  <price_fr>400</price_fr>
  <price_it>400</price_it>
  <price_pan_en>400</price_pan_en>
  <price_pan_es>400</price_pan_es>
  <price_pan_fr>400</price_pan_fr>
  <price_pan_de>400</price_pan_de>
  <special_price></special_price>
  <special_from_date></special_from_date>
  <special_to_date></special_to_date>
  <special_price_uk></special_price_uk>
  <special_from_date_uk></special_from_date_uk>
  <special_to_date_uk></special_to_date_uk>
  <special_price_de></special_price_de>
  <special_from_date_de></special_from_date_de>
  <special_to_date_de></special_to_date_de>
  <special_price_nl></special_price_nl>
  <special_from_date_nl></special_from_date_nl>
  <special_to_date_nl></special_to_date_nl>
  <special_price_be></special_price_be>
  <special_from_date_be></special_from_date_be>
  <special_to_date_be></special_to_date_be>
  <special_price_fr></special_price_fr>
  <special_from_date_fr></special_from_date_fr>
  <special_to_date_fr></special_to_date_fr>
  <special_price_it></special_price_it>
  <special_from_date_it></special_from_date_it>
  <special_to_date_it></special_to_date_it>
  <special_price_pan_en></special_price_pan_en>
  <special_from_date_pan_en></special_from_date_pan_en>
  <special_to_date_pan_en></special_to_date_pan_en>
  <special_price_pan_es></special_price_pan_es>
  <special_from_date_pan_es></special_from_date_pan_es>
  <special_to_date_pan_es></special_to_date_pan_es>
  <special_price_pan_fr></special_price_pan_fr>
  <special_from_date_pan_fr></special_from_date_pan_fr>
  <special_to_date_pan_fr></special_to_date_pan_fr>
  <special_price_pan_de></special_price_pan_de>
  <special_from_date_pan_de></special_from_date_pan_de>
  <special_to_date_pan_de></special_to_date_pan_de>
  <news_from_date>2012-10-28</news_from_date>
  <image_front>SWTK15CGR_front.jpg</image_front>
  <image_back>SWTK15CGR_back.jpg</image_back>
  <image_pocket>SWTK15CGR_pocket.jpg</image_pocket>
  <image_wash>SWTK15CGR_wash.jpg</image_wash>
  <small_image></small_image>
  <thumbnail></thumbnail>
  <url_key></url_key>
  <color></color>
  <bubble_new_collection></bubble_new_collection>
  <bubble_sale></bubble_sale>
  <bubble_best_seller></bubble_best_seller>
  <bubble_limited_edition></bubble_limited_edition>
  <gender>Women</gender>
  <fit_group>SKINNY</fit_group>
  <fit_code>THE SKINNY</fit_code>
  <wash_group>MEDIUM WASH</wash_group>
  <enable_special_area>No</enable_special_area>
  <special_area_static_block_id></special_area_static_block_id>
  <delivery_return_static_block_id>product_tab_delivery_return</delivery_return_static_block_id>
  <status>Disabled</status>
  <visibility>Nowhere</visibility>
  <super_attributes>Size</super_attributes>
  <website>base</website>
  <category_ids></category_ids>
  <main_cat_seo></main_cat_seo>
  <details_care></details_care>
</configurable>
