<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<configurable>
  <sku>SWTM700BL</sku>
  <i18n_name>THE SKINNY HIGH SHINE GUMMY BLACK</i18n_name>
  <i18n_name_de>THE SKINNY HIGH SHINE GUMMY BLACK</i18n_name_de>
  <i18n_name_nl>THE SKINNY HIGH SHINE GUMMY BLACK</i18n_name_nl>
  <i18n_name_fr>THE SKINNY HIGH SHINE GUMMY BLACK</i18n_name_fr>
  <i18n_name_it>THE SKINNY HIGH SHINE GUMMY BLACK</i18n_name_it>
  <i18n_name_es>THE SKINNY HIGH SHINE GUMMY BLACK</i18n_name_es>
  <product_start_date>2012-09-28</product_start_date>
  <product_end_date>2018-10-02</product_end_date>
  <i18n_description>The Skinny High Shine Gummy Black is an unashamedly sexy women’s skinny to parade your passion for the luxe leather trend. A very expensive brand’s The Skinny is a body-sculpting, super-stretch fit set apart by its minimal detailing, clean pockets and slim and sexy, fitted silhouette top to bottom. It has a comfortable rise while the length hits just below the ankle to maintain a clean line with no stacking. This provocative fit is the ultimate backdrop to showcase 7FAM’s High Shine Gummy, a show-stoppingly sexy, leather-look fabric that delivers amazing comfort and stretch thanks to the lightweight, high-performance construction. Choose this High Shine Black to work a multitude of high-fashion looks: create clean lines with a mannish collar on a white shirt or go Goth glamour with fierce heels and a flamboyant tone on top.</i18n_description>
  <i18n_description_de>Die Skinny High Shine Gummy Black ist eine unverschämt sexy Skinny für Damen, mit der Sie Ihre Leidenschaft für den Luxus-Ledertrend zur Schau stellen können. Die Skinny von A very expensive brand hat einen figurformenden Effekt mit Super-Stretch und besticht durch das minimalistische Design der Details, klare Linien der Taschen und eine von oben bis unten schmale, sexy und figurbetonte Silhouette. Sie hat eine bequeme Leibhöhe, die Beine enden direkt unter dem Knöchel, damit die klare Linie nicht durch Falten am Saum gebrochen wird. Die provozierende Passform ist der ultimative Schaukasten für das High Shine Gummy von 7FAM, ein atemberaubendes Gewebe im Lederlook, das aufgrund seines leichten, hoch leistungsfähigen Aufbaus überwältigenden Tragekomfort in Stretch-Qualität bietet. Mit dem High Shine Black können Sie modetechnisch auf vielen Parketts tanzen: Schaffen Sie klaren Linien mit einem weißen Shirt mit maskulinem Kragen oder setzen Sie mit schwindelerregenden Absätzen und einem Eye-Catcher-Farbton im Oberteil echte Goth-Glamour Akzente.</i18n_description_de>
  <i18n_description_nl>De Skinny High Shine Gummy Black is een uitgesproken sexy skinny voor vrouwen waarmee je je passie voor de luxe leather trend tentoonspreidt. A very expensive brand's The Skinny is een nauwsluitend superstretch model met minimale details , sobere zakken en een sexy en strak silhouet. Het model heeft een comfortabele heuplijn en valt tot net onder de enkel voor een simpele lijn zonder kreukels. Dit uitdagende model is de perfecte basis voor 7FAM's High Shine Gummy, een spectaculair sexy leerachtig materiaal dat enorme comfort en stretch biedt dankzij zijn lichtgewicht, hoogwaardige samenstelling. Kies voor deze High Shine Black waarmee je een veelheid aan supertrendy looks krijgt: ga voor simpel met een wit mannenshirt of voor glamour Goth met hoge hakken en flamboyante top.</i18n_description_nl>
  <i18n_description_fr>Le Skinny High Shine Gummy Noir est un skinny femme effronté et sexy qui exprime votre passion pour la nouvelle tendance du luxe, le cuir. Le Skinny A very expensive brand sculpte votre corps grâce à son matériau super-stretch et se distingue par des finitions minimalistes, des poches nettes et une silhouette mince et sexy sur toute la longueur. Sa taille basse est très confortable, et sa longueur juste sous la cheville garantit une ligne nette et fluide. Cette coupe provocante est la dernière interprétation du High Shine Gummy 7FAM, un tissu aspect cuir d'un sexy éblouissant, qui offre un confort et une élasticité exceptionnels grâce à sa grande légèreté et à sa construction d'avant-garde. Utilisez le High Shine Black pour créer une multitude de looks très mode, net avec une chemise blanche au col masculin, ou glamour gothique avec des talons agressifs et un haut à la couleur flamboyante.</i18n_description_fr>
  <i18n_description_it>Lo Skinny High Shine Gummy Black è uno skinny audacemente sexy da donna che rivela  la tua passione per la nuova tendenza del lusso - i capi in pelle. Lo Skinny di A very expensive brand scolpisce il fisico con il suo fit super-stretch e si distingue per i  dettagli  minimal, le tasche di taglio pulito e la linea slim, sexy e attillata in tutta la lunghezza. Ha una vita confortevole mentre la lunghezza, appena sotto la caviglia, regala una linea essenziale ed impeccabile. Questo fit provocante è ideale per esibire gli High Shine Gummy di 7FAM,  quintessenza di  femminilità, realizzato in tessuto effetto pelle, di comfort e stretch sorprendenti grazie alla leggerezza e alla costruzione performante. Questo High Shine Black è così versatile da prestarsi a svariati look glam: diventa essenziale con un collo maschile su camicia bianca oppure alternativo se abbinato a tacco vertiginoso e tonalità sgargianti.</i18n_description_it>
  <i18n_description_es>The Skinny High Shine Gummy Black is an unashamedly sexy women’s skinny to parade your passion for the luxe leather trend. A very expensive brand’s The Skinny is a body-sculpting, super-stretch fit set apart by its minimal detailing, clean pockets and slim and sexy, fitted silhouette top to bottom. It has a comfortable rise while the length hits just below the ankle to maintain a clean line with no stacking. This provocative fit is the ultimate backdrop to showcase 7FAM’s High Shine Gummy, a show-stoppingly sexy, leather-look fabric that delivers amazing comfort and stretch thanks to the lightweight, high-performance construction. Choose this High Shine Black to work a multitude of high-fashion looks: create clean lines with a mannish collar on a white shirt or go Goth glamour with fierce heels and a flamboyant tone on top.</i18n_description_es>
  <i18n_short_description>THE SKINNY HIGH SHINE GUMMY BLACK</i18n_short_description>
  <i18n_short_description_de>THE SKINNY HIGH SHINE GUMMY BLACK</i18n_short_description_de>
  <i18n_short_description_nl>THE SKINNY HIGH SHINE GUMMY BLACK</i18n_short_description_nl>
  <i18n_short_description_fr>THE SKINNY HIGH SHINE GUMMY BLACK</i18n_short_description_fr>
  <i18n_short_description_it>THE SKINNY HIGH SHINE GUMMY BLACK</i18n_short_description_it>
  <i18n_short_description_es>THE SKINNY HIGH SHINE GUMMY BLACK</i18n_short_description_es>
  <i18n_product_details>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Approx. inseam: 30in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rise: Front: 6 3/4in Back: 11 1/4in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leg opening: 10in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Cotton, 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A very expensive brand's signature squiggle back pocket&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zip fly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Made in Europe using original and handcrafted finishing techniques&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details>
  <i18n_product_details_de>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Beinlänge ca. 76cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leibhöhe: Vorne: 17cm Hinten: 28.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fussweite: 25.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Baumwolle, 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Die Signature Squiggle Backpocket von A very expensive brand&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Reisverschlussleiste&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Made in Europe unter Verwendung von Original-und Handarbeit Veredelungstechniken&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_de>
  <i18n_product_details_nl>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Binnenbeenlengte ca. 76cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Kruisnaad: Voor: 17cm Achter: 28.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zoomwijdte: 25.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Katoen, 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A very expensive brand's signature squiggle achterzak&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ritssluiting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gemaakt in Europa met behulp van originele en ambachtelijke afwerkingstechnieken&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_nl>
  <i18n_product_details_fr>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Inseam: sur 76cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fourche: Avant: 17cm Arrière: 28.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ouverture des jambes: 25.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Coton, 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A very expensive brand's squiggle poche&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fermeture Zip&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fabriqué en Europe avec des techniques de finitions artisanales&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_fr>
  <i18n_product_details_it>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lunghezza dal cavallo alla caviglia: circa 76cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lunghezza dal cavallo alla vita: Davanti: 17cm Dietro: 28.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Apertura gamba: 25.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Cotone, 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tasca dietro: A very expensive brand's squiggle&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cerniera lampo&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Realizzato in Europa utilizzando tecniche di finitura artigianali  &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_it>
  <i18n_product_details_es>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tiro aproximado: 30in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tiro: Frontal: 6 3/4in Trasero: 11 1/4in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Abertura de la pierna: 10in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Algodón, 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zip fly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fabricado en Europa utilizando técnicas de acabado originales y artesanas.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_es>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit>Characterised by its minimal detailing, The Skinny has a comfortable rise with a slim, sexy, and fitted silhouette top to bottom. The length hits at the ankle to maintain a clean line with no stacking.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_de>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimalistische Verzierungen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;die Skinny hat eine bequeme Leibhöhe und eine durchweg schmale, sexy und eng anliegende Silhouette&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;endet kurz über dem Knöchel und garantiert einen cleanen Look mit schmaler Silhouette&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_de>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_nl>De Skinny wordt gekenmerkt door minimale details en heeft een comfortabele heuplijn met een slank, sexy en aansluitend silhouet van top tot teen. De lengte gaat mooi tot de enkel voor een pure lijn zonder kreuken.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_nl>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_fr>Orné de détails raffinés, le Skinny est confortable à la taille avec une coupe plus ajustée très sexy qui épouse à merveille l’ensemble de la silhouette. Son tombé bien ajusté jusqu’à la cheville lui confère une ligne impeccable et sans plis.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_fr>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_it>Il modello Skinny, con dettagli minimal e vita confortevole, disegna una figura sexy e sottile da capo a piedi! L’orlo arriva alla caviglia per un taglio deciso senza arricciature.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_it>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_es>Characterised by its minimal detailing, The Skinny has a comfortable rise with a slim, sexy, and fitted silhouette top to bottom. The length hits at the ankle to maintain a clean line with no stacking.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_es>
  <price>240</price>
  <price_uk>220</price_uk>
  <price_de>240</price_de>
  <price_be>240</price_be>
  <price_nl>240</price_nl>
  <price_fr>240</price_fr>
  <price_it>240</price_it>
  <price_pan_en>240</price_pan_en>
  <price_pan_es>240</price_pan_es>
  <price_pan_fr>240</price_pan_fr>
  <price_pan_de>240</price_pan_de>
  <special_price></special_price>
  <special_from_date></special_from_date>
  <special_to_date></special_to_date>
  <special_price_uk></special_price_uk>
  <special_from_date_uk></special_from_date_uk>
  <special_to_date_uk></special_to_date_uk>
  <special_price_de></special_price_de>
  <special_from_date_de></special_from_date_de>
  <special_to_date_de></special_to_date_de>
  <special_price_nl></special_price_nl>
  <special_from_date_nl></special_from_date_nl>
  <special_to_date_nl></special_to_date_nl>
  <special_price_be></special_price_be>
  <special_from_date_be></special_from_date_be>
  <special_to_date_be></special_to_date_be>
  <special_price_fr></special_price_fr>
  <special_from_date_fr></special_from_date_fr>
  <special_to_date_fr></special_to_date_fr>
  <special_price_it></special_price_it>
  <special_from_date_it></special_from_date_it>
  <special_to_date_it></special_to_date_it>
  <special_price_pan_en></special_price_pan_en>
  <special_from_date_pan_en></special_from_date_pan_en>
  <special_to_date_pan_en></special_to_date_pan_en>
  <special_price_pan_es></special_price_pan_es>
  <special_from_date_pan_es></special_from_date_pan_es>
  <special_to_date_pan_es></special_to_date_pan_es>
  <special_price_pan_fr></special_price_pan_fr>
  <special_from_date_pan_fr></special_from_date_pan_fr>
  <special_to_date_pan_fr></special_to_date_pan_fr>
  <special_price_pan_de></special_price_pan_de>
  <special_from_date_pan_de></special_from_date_pan_de>
  <special_to_date_pan_de></special_to_date_pan_de>
  <news_from_date>2012-09-28</news_from_date>
  <image_front>SWTM700BL_front.jpg</image_front>
  <image_back>SWTM700BL_back.jpg</image_back>
  <image_pocket>SWTM700BL_pocket.jpg</image_pocket>
  <image_wash>SWTM700BL_wash.jpg</image_wash>
  <small_image></small_image>
  <thumbnail></thumbnail>
  <url_key></url_key>
  <color></color>
  <bubble_new_collection></bubble_new_collection>
  <bubble_sale></bubble_sale>
  <bubble_best_seller></bubble_best_seller>
  <bubble_limited_edition></bubble_limited_edition>
  <gender>Women</gender>
  <fit_group>SKINNY</fit_group>
  <fit_code>THE SKINNY</fit_code>
  <wash_group>Dark Wash</wash_group>
  <enable_special_area>No</enable_special_area>
  <special_area_static_block_id></special_area_static_block_id>
  <delivery_return_static_block_id>product_tab_delivery_return</delivery_return_static_block_id>
  <status>Disabled</status>
  <visibility>Nowhere</visibility>
  <super_attributes>size</super_attributes>
  <website>base</website>
  <category_ids></category_ids>
  <main_cat_seo></main_cat_seo>
  <details_care></details_care>
</configurable>
