<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<configurable>
  <sku>SNYJ650SQ</sku>
  <i18n_name>DAMION SILKY OAK</i18n_name>
  <i18n_name_de>DAMION SILKY OAK</i18n_name_de>
  <i18n_name_nl>DAMION SILKY OAK</i18n_name_nl>
  <i18n_name_fr>DAMION SILKY OAK</i18n_name_fr>
  <i18n_name_it>DAMION SILKY OAK</i18n_name_it>
  <i18n_name_es>DAMION SILKY OAK</i18n_name_es>
  <product_start_date>2012-04-01</product_start_date>
  <product_end_date>2017-05-02</product_end_date>
  <i18n_description>The Damion Silky Oak is your go-to men’s jean for sexy scruffy style. The new Damion is a superstrech, skinny fit loaded with youthful street fashion attitude. The fit is an updated and modern version of our true skinny fit for men. This more masculine skinny fit features a welt pocket instead of a coin pocket and a clean back pocket. 7FAM’s Silky oak wash begins as a black denim and is washed down to achieve an authentic vintage grey look, enhanced by the extreme, high contrast 3D whiskers. An exceptionally soft hand feel and high durability make this stretch denim the perfect partner for the skinny fit Damion. Add this well worn, beaten up look jean to your weekend wardrobe to nail carefree cool.</i18n_description>
  <i18n_description_de>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Die Damion Silky Oak ist eine Musthave-Jeans für den sexy Undone-Look&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Superstretch-Jeans mit engem Schnitt und jugendlicher Streetfashion-Attitüde&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;aktualisierte und moderne Version unserer originalen Skinny Fit für Herren&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;diese maskulinere Skinny Fit kommt mit Paspeltasche statt Coin Pocket und schlichter Back Pocket&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;7FAMs Silky Oak Wash startet als schwarzer Denim und wäscht sich zu einem authentischen grauen Vintage-Look aus&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;extreme 3D-Sitzfalten bieten starke Kontraste&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;der ungewöhnlich weiche Griff und die hohe Strapazierfähigkeit machen diesen Stretch-Denim zum perfekten Partner für die Skinny Fit Damion&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;diese abgetragene, abgeriebene Jeans bringt unbekümmerte Coolness in Ihre Wochenend-Garderobe&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_description_de>
  <i18n_description_nl>De Damion Silky Oak is jouw favoriete mannenjeans voor een sexy, nonchalante stijl. De nieuwe Damion is een superstretch, skinny fit boordevol jeugdige streetcool. Dit model is een nieuwe en moderne versie van onze skinny fit voor mannen. Deze mannelijkere skinny fit heeft een afgeboorde zak in plaats van een muntzak en een sobere achterzak. De Silky oak-wassing van 7FAM begint als een zwarte denim die afgewassen wordt tot een authentieke vintage grijze look met extreme, contrasterende 3D-strepen. Deze stretch denim voelt bijzonder zacht aan, is zeer duurzaam en is dus de perfecte partner voor de skinny fit Damion. Voeg deze afgedragen jeans met ruige look toe aan je weekendgarderobe voor zorgeloze cool.</i18n_description_nl>
  <i18n_description_fr>Avec le Damion version Silky Oak pour homme, offrez-vous un jean au style sexy et audacieux. Le nouveau Damion se distingue par sa coupe skinny ultra-stretch très jeune et branchée, une version revisitée et moderne de la coupe skinny originale de 7FAM. Ce modèle skinny plus masculin arbore une poche arrière clean, ainsi qu’une poche passepoilée qui remplace la poche monnaie. Le lavage Silky Oak est élaboré à partir d’un denim noir délavé pour obtenir un effet grisé vintage, agrémenté de whiskers en relief très contrastés. Sa texture incroyablement douce et très résistante en fait un denim stretch parfait pour la coupe skinny du Damion. Rafraîchissez votre garde-robe détente avec ce modèle à l’aspect usé pour un look décontracté qui respire l’insouciance.</i18n_description_fr>
  <i18n_description_it>Damion Silky Oak è un jeans da uomo indispensabile per uno stile sexy e un po’ trasandato. Uno skinny ultra stretch ideale per un look “da strada” giovane e fashion. Una versione moderna e up-to-date dell’originale skinny da uomo. Decisamente più maschile, si distingue per la tasca a filetto che sostituisce quella portamonete e per la tasca posteriore dalle linee pulite. Con il lavaggio Silky Oak, il denim nero viene scolorito per ottenere una tinta grigia dall’autentico sapore vintage, sottolineato da eccezionali baffi in 3D a elevato contrasto. Resistente e incredibilmente morbido al tatto, questo denim stretch è davvero perfetto. Per un look spensierato, aggiungete questo jeans vissuto al vostro guardaroba del week-end.</i18n_description_it>
  <i18n_description_es>The Damion Silky Oak is your go-to men’s jean for sexy scruffy style. The new Damion is a superstrech, skinny fit loaded with youthful street fashion attitude. The fit is an updated and modern version of our true skinny fit for men. This more masculine skinny fit features a welt pocket instead of a coin pocket and a clean back pocket. 7FAM’s Silky oak wash begins as a black denim and is washed down to achieve an authentic vintage grey look, enhanced by the extreme, high contrast 3D whiskers. An exceptionally soft hand feel and high durability make this stretch denim the perfect partner for the skinny fit Damion. Add this well worn, beaten up look jean to your weekend wardrobe to nail carefree cool.</i18n_description_es>
  <i18n_short_description>DAMION SILKY OAK</i18n_short_description>
  <i18n_short_description_de>DAMION SILKY OAK</i18n_short_description_de>
  <i18n_short_description_nl>DAMION SILKY OAK</i18n_short_description_nl>
  <i18n_short_description_fr>DAMION SILKY OAK</i18n_short_description_fr>
  <i18n_short_description_it>DAMION SILKY OAK</i18n_short_description_it>
  <i18n_short_description_es>DAMION SILKY OAK</i18n_short_description_es>
  <i18n_product_details>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Approx. inseam: 33 1/2in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rise: Front: 8in Back: 13in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leg opening: 13 1/2in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Cotton 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Clean pocket&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zip fly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Made in Europe using original and handcrafted finishing techniques&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details>
  <i18n_product_details_de>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Beinlänge ca.  85cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leibhöhe: Vorne: 20cm Hinten: 33cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fussweite: 34cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Baumwolle 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Clean Pocket&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Reisverschlussleiste&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Made in Europe unter Verwendung von Original-und Handarbeit Veredelungstechniken&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_de>
  <i18n_product_details_nl>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Binnenbeenlengte ca.  85cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Kruisnaad: Voor: 20cm Achter: 33cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zoomwijdte: 34cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Katoen 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Achterzak zonder squiggle&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ritssluiting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gemaakt in Europa met behulp van originele en ambachtelijke afwerkingstechnieken&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_nl>
  <i18n_product_details_fr>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Inseam: sur  85cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fourche: Avant: 20cm Arrière: 33cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ouverture des jambes: 34cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Coton 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Clean poche&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fermeture Zip&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fabriqué en Europe avec des techniques de finitions artisanales&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_fr>
  <i18n_product_details_it>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lunghezza dal cavallo alla caviglia: circa  85cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lunghezza dal cavallo alla vita: Davanti: 20cm Dietro: 33cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Apertura gamba: 34cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Cotone 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tasca Dietro: liscia&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cerniera lampo&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Realizzato in Europa utilizzando tecniche di finitura artigianali&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_it>
  <i18n_product_details_es>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tiro aproximado: 33 1/2in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tiro: Frontal: 8in Trasero: 13in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Abertura de la pierna: 13 1/2in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Algodón 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Blosillo sin squiggle&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zip fly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fabricado en Europa utilizando técnicas de acabado originales y artesanas.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_es>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit>The Damion is an updated and modern masculine version of A very expensive brand's true skinny fit for men. It features a welt pocket in place of a coin pocket and a clean back pocket when realized in our super stretch "masculine look" fabrics.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_de>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Die Damion ist eine aktualisierte, moderne maskuline Version des Men Skinny Fit von A very expensive brand&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leistentasche statt Münztasche und schlichte Gesäßtasche bei unseren superstretchigen Stoffen im Masculine Look&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_de>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_nl>De Damion is een vernieuwde en moderne versie van de echte skinny fit voor mannen van A very expensive brand. Deze jeans heeft een afgeboorde zak in plaats van een muntzak en een eenvoudige achterzak uitgevoerd in onze superstretch, mannelijk ogende stoffen.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_nl>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_fr>Le Damion est une version fraîche et moderne de la coupe skinny originale de A very expensive brand pour homme. Il se démarque par sa poche arrière clean et sa poche passepoilée qui remplace la poche monnaie, le tout décliné dans un tissu ultra-stretch au look résolument masculin.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_fr>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_it>Damion è una versione moderna e up-to-date dell’originale skinny da uomo di A very expensive brand. Si distingue per la tasca a filetto che sostituisce quella portamonete, per la tasca posteriore dalle linee pulite e per i tessuti ultra stretch dal look maschile.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_it>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_es>The Damion is an updated and modern masculine version of A very expensive brand's true skinny fit for men. It features a welt pocket in place of a coin pocket and a clean back pocket when realized in our super stretch "masculine look" fabrics.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_es>
  <price>249</price>
  <price_uk>225</price_uk>
  <price_de>249</price_de>
  <price_be>249</price_be>
  <price_nl>249</price_nl>
  <price_fr>85.26</price_fr>
  <price_it>249</price_it>
  <price_pan_en>249</price_pan_en>
  <price_pan_es>249</price_pan_es>
  <price_pan_fr>249</price_pan_fr>
  <price_pan_de>249</price_pan_de>
  <special_price></special_price>
  <special_from_date></special_from_date>
  <special_to_date></special_to_date>
  <special_price_uk></special_price_uk>
  <special_from_date_uk></special_from_date_uk>
  <special_to_date_uk></special_to_date_uk>
  <special_price_de></special_price_de>
  <special_from_date_de></special_from_date_de>
  <special_to_date_de></special_to_date_de>
  <special_price_nl></special_price_nl>
  <special_from_date_nl></special_from_date_nl>
  <special_to_date_nl></special_to_date_nl>
  <special_price_be></special_price_be>
  <special_from_date_be></special_from_date_be>
  <special_to_date_be></special_to_date_be>
  <special_price_fr></special_price_fr>
  <special_from_date_fr></special_from_date_fr>
  <special_to_date_fr></special_to_date_fr>
  <special_price_it></special_price_it>
  <special_from_date_it></special_from_date_it>
  <special_to_date_it></special_to_date_it>
  <special_price_pan_en></special_price_pan_en>
  <special_from_date_pan_en></special_from_date_pan_en>
  <special_to_date_pan_en></special_to_date_pan_en>
  <special_price_pan_es></special_price_pan_es>
  <special_from_date_pan_es></special_from_date_pan_es>
  <special_to_date_pan_es></special_to_date_pan_es>
  <special_price_pan_fr></special_price_pan_fr>
  <special_from_date_pan_fr></special_from_date_pan_fr>
  <special_to_date_pan_fr></special_to_date_pan_fr>
  <special_price_pan_de></special_price_pan_de>
  <special_from_date_pan_de></special_from_date_pan_de>
  <special_to_date_pan_de></special_to_date_pan_de>
  <news_from_date>2012-04-01</news_from_date>
  <image_front>SNYJ650SQ_front.jpg</image_front>
  <image_back>SNYJ650SQ_back.jpg</image_back>
  <image_pocket>SNYJ650SQ_pocket.jpg</image_pocket>
  <image_wash>SNYJ650SQ_wash.jpg</image_wash>
  <small_image></small_image>
  <thumbnail></thumbnail>
  <url_key></url_key>
  <color></color>
  <bubble_new_collection></bubble_new_collection>
  <bubble_sale></bubble_sale>
  <bubble_best_seller></bubble_best_seller>
  <bubble_limited_edition></bubble_limited_edition>
  <gender>Men</gender>
  <fit_group>SLIM FIT</fit_group>
  <fit_code>DAMION</fit_code>
  <wash_group>DARK WASH</wash_group>
  <enable_special_area>No</enable_special_area>
  <special_area_static_block_id></special_area_static_block_id>
  <delivery_return_static_block_id>product_tab_delivery_return</delivery_return_static_block_id>
  <status>Disabled</status>
  <visibility>Nowhere</visibility>
  <super_attributes>size</super_attributes>
  <website>base</website>
  <category_ids></category_ids>
  <main_cat_seo></main_cat_seo>
  <details_care></details_care>
</configurable>
