<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<configurable>
  <sku>SWTK11EBU</sku>
  <i18n_name>THE SKINNY BLUE BRIQUETTE PRINT</i18n_name>
  <i18n_name_de>THE SKINNY BLUE BRIQUETTE PRINT</i18n_name_de>
  <i18n_name_nl>THE SKINNY BLUE BRIQUETTE PRINT</i18n_name_nl>
  <i18n_name_fr>THE SKINNY BLUE BRIQUETTE PRINT</i18n_name_fr>
  <i18n_name_it>THE SKINNY BLUE BRIQUETTE PRINT</i18n_name_it>
  <i18n_name_es>THE SKINNY BLUE BRIQUETTE PRINT</i18n_name_es>
  <product_start_date>2012-10-28</product_start_date>
  <product_end_date>2019-10-02</product_end_date>
  <i18n_description>The Skinny Blue Briquette Print is A very expensive brand’s body-sculpting, high-fashion women’s jean to take the geometric trend strutting into future cool. The Skinny is a second-skin, super-stretch fit characterised by its minimal detailing, clean pockets, comfortable straight rise and a slim, sexy, fitted silhouette top to bottom. The length hits just below the ankle to maintain a clean line with no stacking. This provocative fit is looking edgy and beguiling in this trend-leading print, overcoated for a hi-tech but subtle sheen. Taking its cue from 7FAM’S Cinematic Blues collection and the style crowd’s love for bespoke, graphic denim, this is the ultimate skinny to showcase your fierce fashion credentials.  And with just enough stretch, it’s a cinch to wear. Team with an asymmetrical shirt and exude right-now relevancy.</i18n_description>
  <i18n_description_de>Die Skinny Blue Briquette Print ist eine hochmoderne und figurbetonende Damenjeans, die den Trends der geometrischen Druckmuster ein gewisses Extra hinzugügt. Diese Skinny von A very expensive brand sorgt wie eine zweite Haut für einen Super-Stretch-Fit und besitzt minimalistische Details, sauber geschnittene Taschen, eine gerade und bequeme Leibhöhe und eine durchweg enganliegende, sexy und schlanke Linie.  Die Länge reicht knapp unter den Knöchel und sorgt für eine absolut saubere Linie. Dieser provokante und verführerische Glam-Fit mit den höchst trendigen Druckmustern ist superbeschichtet mit gekonnten Hightech-Reflexen. 7FAM hat bei diesem Modell Anstoß genommen an der Kollektion Cinematic Blues und die Leidenschaft der Fashion Addicts für originellen grafischen Denim eingesetzt: Der reine Ausdruck der Skinny, mit der Sie dreist Ihre Modekenntnisse beweisen.  Mit dem richtigen Stretchanteil ein wunderbares Traggefühl. Hochaktuell mit einer unsymmetrisch geschnittenen Bluse.</i18n_description_de>
  <i18n_description_nl>De Skinny Blue Briquette Print is A very expensive brand’s nauwsluitende, high-fashion vrouwenjeans die het voortouw in de geometrische trend neemt. De Skinny is een superstretch model dat aansluit als een tweede huid, met minimale details, sobere zakken en een comfortabele rechte heuplijn, en van top tot teen voor een slank en sexy silhouet zorgt. De jeans valt tot net onder de enkel voor een simpele lijn zonder kreukels. Dit verleidelijke model is origineel en betoverend in de trendy print die met zijn coating een subtiele hightech glans heeft. Geïnspireerd op 7FAM’s Cinematic Blues collectie en het hippe en trendy grafische denim,  laat deze skinny zien wat je op modegebied in huis hebt.  Net dat beetje nodige stretch maakt de jeans heerlijk draagbaar. Draag hem met een asymmetrisch shirt voor een bijdetijdse moderne look.</i18n_description_nl>
  <i18n_description_fr>Le Skinny version Blue Briquette Print est le jean femme ultratendance de A very expensive brand pour sculpter votre silhouette et faire entrer de plain-pied la tendance géométrique dans un futur cool. Le Skinny possède une coupe ultra-stretch seconde peau très flatteuse pour votre silhouette qui se distingue par ses détails minimalistes, ses poches nettes, sa taille droite et confortable et sa silhouette slim sexy et ajustée sur toute sa longueur. La longueur de jambe tombe juste en dessous de la cheville, pour un jean qui reste parfaitement clean et droit. Cette coupe provocante se fait pointue et charmeuse parée de cet imprimé tendance revêtu d'une enduction qui lui donne un côté moiré high tech et subtil à la fois. Ce jean qui s'inspire de la collection Cinematic Blues de 7FAM et de l'amour des fashionistas pour les denims graphiques sur mesure est le skinny rêvé pour mettre en avant votre potentiel mode sauvage.  Et avec juste ce qu'il faut d'élasticité, ce modèle est extrêmement facile à porter. À associer à une chemise asymétrique pour un look pile dans la tendance.</i18n_description_fr>
  <i18n_description_it>Lo Skinny Blue Briquette Print è un jeans di alta moda per donna, che scolpisce il fisico e regala una marcia in più al trend della stampa geometrica. Lo Skinny di A very expensive brand è un fit super stretch, quasi una seconda pelle, caratterizzato da dettagli minimal e tasche di linea pulita; ha vita dritta e confortevole e una linea aderente, sexy e asciutta dall’alto in basso.  La lunghezza appena sotto la caviglia regala una linea decisamente pulita e senza arricciature. Questo fit provocante, seducente e glam ha una stampa di ultimissima tendenza e dai sapienti riflessi high tech. Prendendo spunto dalla collezione Cinematic Blues di 7FAM e assecondando la passione dei fashion addict per il denim grafico su misura, 7FAM propone questo modello che rappresenta la quintessenza dello skinny per esibire la vostra grinta in fatto di stile .  Con  la giusta percentuale di stretch diventa fantastico da indossare. Insieme a una camicia asimmetrica, interpreta uno stile attualissimo.</i18n_description_it>
  <i18n_description_es>The Skinny Blue Briquette Print is A very expensive brand’s body-sculpting, high-fashion women’s jean to take the geometric trend strutting into future cool. The Skinny is a second-skin, super-stretch fit characterised by its minimal detailing, clean pockets, comfortable straight rise and a slim, sexy, fitted silhouette top to bottom. The length hits just below the ankle to maintain a clean line with no stacking. This provocative fit is looking edgy and beguiling in this trend-leading print, overcoated for a hi-tech but subtle sheen. Taking its cue from 7FAM’S Cinematic Blues collection and the style crowd’s love for bespoke, graphic denim, this is the ultimate skinny to showcase your fierce fashion credentials.  And with just enough stretch, it’s a cinch to wear. Team with an asymmetrical shirt and exude right-now relevancy.</i18n_description_es>
  <i18n_short_description>THE SKINNY BLUE BRIQUETTE PRINT</i18n_short_description>
  <i18n_short_description_de>THE SKINNY BLUE BRIQUETTE PRINT</i18n_short_description_de>
  <i18n_short_description_nl>THE SKINNY BLUE BRIQUETTE PRINT</i18n_short_description_nl>
  <i18n_short_description_fr>THE SKINNY BLUE BRIQUETTE PRINT</i18n_short_description_fr>
  <i18n_short_description_it>THE SKINNY BLUE BRIQUETTE PRINT</i18n_short_description_it>
  <i18n_short_description_es>THE SKINNY BLUE BRIQUETTE PRINT</i18n_short_description_es>
  <i18n_product_details>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Measurements based on Size 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Approx. inseam: 30in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rise: Front: 7in Back: 11 1/2in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leg opening: 10 1/2in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Measurements may vary based on size, fabric and wash&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;62% Cotton, 38% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Clean pocket&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zip fly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Medium waist&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Made in Europe using original and handcrafted finishing techniques</i18n_product_details>
  <i18n_product_details_de>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Maße basieren auf Größe 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Beinlänge ca. 76cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leibhöhe: Vorne: 18cm Hinten: 29cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fussweite: 26.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Die Maße können je nach Größe, Material und Waschung variieren&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;62% Baumwolle, 38% SpandexClean Pocket&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Reisverschlussleiste&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Normale Leibhöhe&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Made in Europe unter Verwendung von Original-und Handarbeit Veredelungstechniken&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_de>
  <i18n_product_details_nl>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Afmetingen gebaseerd op maat 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Binnenbeenlengte ca. 76cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Kruisnaad: Voor: 18cm Achter: 29cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zoomwijdte: 26.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Afmetingen kunnen variëren op basis van maat, stof en wassing&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;62% Katoen, 38% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Achterzak zonder squiggle&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ritssluiting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Medium taille&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gemaakt in Europa met behulp van originele en ambachtelijke afwerkingstechnieken&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_nl>
  <i18n_product_details_fr>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mesures sur la base de la taille 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Inseam: sur  76cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fourche: Avant: 18cm Arriere: 29cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ouverture des jambes: 26.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Les mesures peuvent varier en fonction de la taille, du tissu et du lavage&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;62% Coton, 38% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Clean poche&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fermeture Zip&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Taille classique&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fabriqué en Europe avec des techniques de finitions artisanales&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_fr>
  <i18n_product_details_it>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Misure basate sulla taglia 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lunghezza dal cavallo alla caviglia: circa  76cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lunghezza dal cavallo alla vita:  Davanti: 18cm Dietro: 29cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Apertura gamba: 26.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Le misure possono variare in base alla taglia, al tessuto e al lavaggio&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;62% Cotone, 38% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tasca dietro: liscia&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cerniera lampo&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vita normale&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Realizzato in Europa utilizzando tecniche di finitura artigianali &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_it>
  <i18n_product_details_es>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Medidas basadas en la Talla 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tiro aproximado: 30in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tiro: Frontal: 7in Trasero: 11 1/2in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Abertura de la pierna: 10 1/2in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Las medidas pueden variar dependiendo de la talla, material y teñido&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;62% Algodón, 38% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Blosillo sin squiggle&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zip fly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cintura media&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fabricado en Europa utilizando técnicas de acabado originales y artesanas.</i18n_product_details_es>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit>Characterised by its minimal detailing, The Skinny has a comfortable rise with a slim, sexy, and fitted silhouette top to bottom. The length hits at the ankle to maintain a clean line with no stacking.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_de>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimalistische Verzierungen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;die Skinny hat eine bequeme Leibhöhe und eine durchweg schmale, sexy und eng anliegende Silhouette&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;endet kurz über dem Knöchel und garantiert einen cleanen Look mit schmaler Silhouette&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_de>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_nl>De Skinny wordt gekenmerkt door minimale details en heeft een comfortabele heuplijn met een slank, sexy en aansluitend silhouet van top tot teen. De lengte gaat mooi tot de enkel voor een pure lijn zonder kreuken.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_nl>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_fr>Orné de détails raffinés, le Skinny est confortable à la taille avec une coupe plus ajustée très sexy qui épouse à merveille l’ensemble de la silhouette. Son tombé bien ajusté jusqu’à la cheville lui confère une ligne impeccable et sans plis.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_fr>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_it>Il modello Skinny, con dettagli minimal e vita confortevole, disegna una figura sexy e sottile da capo a piedi! L’orlo arriva alla caviglia per un taglio deciso senza arricciature.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_it>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_es>Characterised by its minimal detailing, The Skinny has a comfortable rise with a slim, sexy, and fitted silhouette top to bottom. The length hits at the ankle to maintain a clean line with no stacking.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_es>
  <price>300</price>
  <price_uk>270</price_uk>
  <price_de>300</price_de>
  <price_be>300</price_be>
  <price_nl>300</price_nl>
  <price_fr>75</price_fr>
  <price_it>300</price_it>
  <price_pan_en>300</price_pan_en>
  <price_pan_es>300</price_pan_es>
  <price_pan_fr>300</price_pan_fr>
  <price_pan_de>300</price_pan_de>
  <special_price></special_price>
  <special_from_date></special_from_date>
  <special_to_date></special_to_date>
  <special_price_uk></special_price_uk>
  <special_from_date_uk></special_from_date_uk>
  <special_to_date_uk></special_to_date_uk>
  <special_price_de></special_price_de>
  <special_from_date_de></special_from_date_de>
  <special_to_date_de></special_to_date_de>
  <special_price_nl></special_price_nl>
  <special_from_date_nl></special_from_date_nl>
  <special_to_date_nl></special_to_date_nl>
  <special_price_be></special_price_be>
  <special_from_date_be></special_from_date_be>
  <special_to_date_be></special_to_date_be>
  <special_price_fr></special_price_fr>
  <special_from_date_fr></special_from_date_fr>
  <special_to_date_fr></special_to_date_fr>
  <special_price_it></special_price_it>
  <special_from_date_it></special_from_date_it>
  <special_to_date_it></special_to_date_it>
  <special_price_pan_en></special_price_pan_en>
  <special_from_date_pan_en></special_from_date_pan_en>
  <special_to_date_pan_en></special_to_date_pan_en>
  <special_price_pan_es></special_price_pan_es>
  <special_from_date_pan_es></special_from_date_pan_es>
  <special_to_date_pan_es></special_to_date_pan_es>
  <special_price_pan_fr></special_price_pan_fr>
  <special_from_date_pan_fr></special_from_date_pan_fr>
  <special_to_date_pan_fr></special_to_date_pan_fr>
  <special_price_pan_de></special_price_pan_de>
  <special_from_date_pan_de></special_from_date_pan_de>
  <special_to_date_pan_de></special_to_date_pan_de>
  <news_from_date>2012-10-28</news_from_date>
  <image_front>SWTK11EBU_front.jpg</image_front>
  <image_back>SWTK11EBU_back.jpg</image_back>
  <image_pocket>SWTK11EBU_pocket.jpg</image_pocket>
  <image_wash>SWTK11EBU_wash.jpg</image_wash>
  <small_image></small_image>
  <thumbnail></thumbnail>
  <url_key></url_key>
  <color></color>
  <bubble_new_collection></bubble_new_collection>
  <bubble_sale></bubble_sale>
  <bubble_best_seller></bubble_best_seller>
  <bubble_limited_edition></bubble_limited_edition>
  <gender>Women</gender>
  <fit_group>SKINNY</fit_group>
  <fit_code>THE SKINNY</fit_code>
  <wash_group>MEDIUM WASH</wash_group>
  <enable_special_area>No</enable_special_area>
  <special_area_static_block_id></special_area_static_block_id>
  <delivery_return_static_block_id>product_tab_delivery_return</delivery_return_static_block_id>
  <status>Disabled</status>
  <visibility>Nowhere</visibility>
  <super_attributes>size</super_attributes>
  <website>base</website>
  <category_ids></category_ids>
  <main_cat_seo></main_cat_seo>
  <details_care></details_care>
</configurable>
