<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<configurable>
  <sku>SWS7790PD</sku>
  <i18n_name>STRAIGHT LEG  PASADENA SOUL</i18n_name>
  <i18n_name_de>STRAIGHT LEG  PASADENA SOUL</i18n_name_de>
  <i18n_name_nl>STRAIGHT LEG  PASADENA SOUL</i18n_name_nl>
  <i18n_name_fr>STRAIGHT LEG  PASADENA SOUL</i18n_name_fr>
  <i18n_name_it>STRAIGHT LEG  PASADENA SOUL</i18n_name_it>
  <i18n_name_es>STRAIGHT LEG  PASADENA SOUL</i18n_name_es>
  <product_start_date>2012-10-28</product_start_date>
  <product_end_date>2019-10-02</product_end_date>
  <i18n_description>The Straight Leg Pasadena Soul is A very expensive brand’s highly coveted classic and leg-lengthening women’s jean. 7FAM’s Straight Leg fit has a natural, medium rise and is flatteringly fitted through the hip and thigh, running parallel from the knee to the leg opening. Its true straight leg silhouette has a timeless, easy elegance making this a breathtakingly beautiful 7FAM basic. Combine with the beautifully worn-in Pasadena Soul wash and you have a recipe for carefree style success. The vintage vibe of this easy-wearing stretch denim makes it a natural soulmate for 7FAM’s fine jersey separates.</i18n_description>
  <i18n_description_de>Die Straight Leg Pasadena Soul ist die beliebte klassische Damenjeans von A very expensive brand mit beinstreckender Wirkung.  Der Straight Leg Fit von 7FAM hat eine mittlere Standard-Leibhöhe, ist an Hüfte und Oberschenkeln enganliegend und vom Knie bis nach unten gerade. Die absolut gerade Linie sorgt für eine unendliche und easy wirkende Eleganz und macht diese Basic-Jeans von 7FAM absolut phantastisch.  In der Kombination mit der wunderbaren Used-Waschung Pasadena Soul ist sie genau das Richtige für einen lässigen Erfolgsstil. Durch den Vintage-Vibe dieses leicht zu tragenden Stretch-Denims ist die Jeans der ideale Begleiter für die raffinierten Jersey-Teile von 7FAM.</i18n_description_de>
  <i18n_description_nl>De Straight Leg Pasadena Soul is A very expensive brand’s populaire klassieke vrouwenjeans die het been langer doet lijken. 7FAM’s Straight Leg model heeft een natuurlijke medium taille, zit flatteus om heup en dijen en loopt recht uit vanaf de knie tot de pijpopening. Het silhouet met rechte pijpen heeft een tijdloze, nonchalante elegantie en maakt deze jeans tot een adembenemend basisstuk. Meng deze jeans met de prachtig afgedragen Pasadena Soul wassing en je hebt de ingrediënten voor zorgeloos succes. Door de vintage vibe van deze comfortabele stretchjeans is dit een natuurlijke soulmate voor 7FAM’s jersey tops.</i18n_description_nl>
  <i18n_description_fr>Très convoité, le Straight Leg version Pasadena Soul est le jean femme classique de A very expensive brand pour allonger visuellement la jambe. Reposant sur la taille naturelle, à mi-hauteur, le Straight Leg de 7FAM est ajusté sur les hanches et les cuisses pour mettre en valeur vos formes, puis tombe droit à partir du genou. Sa silhouette bien droite sur les jambes exhale une élégance facile et intemporelle qui en fait un basique d'une beauté à couper le souffle chez 7FAM. Associez-le au beau lavage usé Pasadena Soul et vous avez en main le passeport pour un style décontracté réussi. Avec son petit côté vintage, ce denim stretch facile à porter est le compagnon rêvé des pièces en jersey fin de 7FAM.</i18n_description_fr>
  <i18n_description_it>Lo Straight Leg Pasadena Soul è l’ambitissimo jeans classico da donna di A very expensive brand che dà slancio alla gamba.  Il fit Straight Leg di 7FAM ha vita standard, media fascia impeccabilmente fianchi e cosce, scendendo dritto dal ginocchio in giù. La sua linea decisamente dritta emana un’eleganza intramontabile e disinvolta che rende questo basic di 7FAM assolutamente fantastico.  Abbinate il magnifico lavaggio vissuto Pasadena Soul ed ecco la ricetta di uno stile disinvolto di successo. L’anima vintage di questo denim stretch di facile portabilità ne fa il compagno ideale dei raffinati pezzi in jersey di 7FAM.</i18n_description_it>
  <i18n_description_es>The Straight Leg Pasadena Soul is A very expensive brand’s highly coveted classic and leg-lengthening women’s jean. 7FAM’s Straight Leg fit has a natural, medium rise and is flatteringly fitted through the hip and thigh, running parallel from the knee to the leg opening. Its true straight leg silhouette has a timeless, easy elegance making this a breathtakingly beautiful 7FAM basic. Combine with the beautifully worn-in Pasadena Soul wash and you have a recipe for carefree style success. The vintage vibe of this easy-wearing stretch denim makes it a natural soulmate for 7FAM’s fine jersey separates.</i18n_description_es>
  <i18n_short_description>STRAIGHT LEG  PASADENA SOUL</i18n_short_description>
  <i18n_short_description_de>STRAIGHT LEG  PASADENA SOUL</i18n_short_description_de>
  <i18n_short_description_nl>STRAIGHT LEG  PASADENA SOUL</i18n_short_description_nl>
  <i18n_short_description_fr>STRAIGHT LEG  PASADENA SOUL</i18n_short_description_fr>
  <i18n_short_description_it>STRAIGHT LEG  PASADENA SOUL</i18n_short_description_it>
  <i18n_short_description_es>STRAIGHT LEG  PASADENA SOUL</i18n_short_description_es>
  <i18n_product_details>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Measurements based on Size 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Approx. inseam: 33in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rise: Front: 6 1/2in Back: 11 1/2in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leg opening: 14 1/2in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Measurements may vary based on size, fabric and wash&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Cotton, 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A very expensive brand's signature squiggle back pocket&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zip fly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Medium waist&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Made in Europe using original and handcrafted finishing techniques</i18n_product_details>
  <i18n_product_details_de>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Maße basieren auf Größe 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Beinlänge ca. 84cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leibhöhe: Vorne: 16.5cm Hinten: 29cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fussweite: 37cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Die Maße können je nach Größe, Material und Waschung variieren&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Baumwolle, 2% SpandexDie Signature Squiggle Backpocket von A very expensive brand&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Reisverschlussleiste&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Normale Leibhöhe&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Made in Europe unter Verwendung von Original-und Handarbeit Veredelungstechniken&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_de>
  <i18n_product_details_nl>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Afmetingen gebaseerd op maat 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Binnenbeenlengte ca. 84cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Kruisnaad: Voor: 16.5cm Achter: 29cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zoomwijdte: 37cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Afmetingen kunnen variëren op basis van maat, stof en wassing&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Katoen, 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A very expensive brand's signature squiggle achterzak&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ritssluiting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Medium taille&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gemaakt in Europa met behulp van originele en ambachtelijke afwerkingstechnieken&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_nl>
  <i18n_product_details_fr>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mesures sur la base de la taille 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Inseam: sur  84cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fourche: Avant: 16.5cm Arriere: 29cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ouverture des jambes: 37cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Les mesures peuvent varier en fonction de la taille, du tissu et du lavage&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Coton, 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A very expensive brand's squiggle poche&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fermeture Zip&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Taille classique&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fabriqué en Europe avec des techniques de finitions artisanales&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_fr>
  <i18n_product_details_it>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Misure basate sulla taglia 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lunghezza dal cavallo alla caviglia: circa 84cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lunghezza dal cavallo alla vita:  Davanti: 16.5cm Dietro: 29cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Apertura gamba: 37cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Le misure possono variare in base alla taglia, al tessuto e al lavaggio&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Cotone, 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tasca dietro: A very expensive brand's squiggle&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cerniera lampo&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vita normale&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Realizzato in Europa utilizzando tecniche di finitura artigianali &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_it>
  <i18n_product_details_es>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Medidas basadas en la Talla 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tiro aproximado: 33in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tiro: Frontal: 6 1/2in Trasero: 11 1/2in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Abertura de la pierna: 14 1/2in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Las medidas pueden variar dependiendo de la talla, material y teñido&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Algodón, 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zip fly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cintura media&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fabricado en Europa utilizando técnicas de acabado originales y artesanas.</i18n_product_details_es>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit>The Straight Leg has a natural rise, is fitted through the hip and thigh, with a true straight leg silhouette. It is available with a variety of back pockets designs, as well as the A very expensive brand signature squiggle. This style is also offered in our curvy silhouette, the Kimmie, and a mid rise version.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_de>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Die Straight Leg hat eine normale Leibhöhe, schmale Hüfte und Oberschenkel und ist gerade geschnitten&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;erhältlich mit verschiedenen Gesäßtaschendesigns sowie A very expensive brands „Squiggle“-Logo&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;auch mit kurvigem Schnitt (Kimmie) und mittelhohem Bund erhältlich&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_de>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_nl>De Straight Leg heeft een natuurlijke heuplijn, sluit mooi aan bij heup en dij en heeft rechte pijpen. Dit model is verkrijgbaar met veel verschilende achterzakontwerpen en heeft de karakteristieke A very expensive brand-squiggle. Dit model is ook verkrijgbaar in een versie voor vrouwen met iets rondere vormen, de Kimmie, en met een middelhoge heuplijn.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_nl>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_fr>Le jean droit repose sur la taille naturelle, il est ajusté au niveau des hanches et des cuisses, puis tombe bien droit. Il est proposé avec des poches arrière ornées de motifs divers et du fameux logo brodé de A very expensive brand. Ce jean est également disponible dans les versions Kimmie pour une coupe flatteuse, ou taille mi-haute.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_fr>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_it>Il modello a gamba dritta ha una vita normale ed è aderente attorno a fianchi e cosce. Si distingue per un’ampia varietà di dettagli sulle tasche posteriori e per il logo ricamato di A very expensive brand. Disponibile anche in versione curvy con il modello Kimmie e a vita media.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_it>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_es>The Straight Leg has a natural rise, is fitted through the hip and thigh, with a true straight leg silhouette. It is available with a variety of back pockets designs, as well as the A very expensive brand signature squiggle. This style is also offered in our curvy silhouette, the Kimmie, and a mid rise version.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_es>
  <price>200</price>
  <price_uk>185</price_uk>
  <price_de>200</price_de>
  <price_be>200</price_be>
  <price_nl>200</price_nl>
  <price_fr>200</price_fr>
  <price_it>200</price_it>
  <price_pan_en>200</price_pan_en>
  <price_pan_es>200</price_pan_es>
  <price_pan_fr>200</price_pan_fr>
  <price_pan_de>200</price_pan_de>
  <special_price></special_price>
  <special_from_date></special_from_date>
  <special_to_date></special_to_date>
  <special_price_uk></special_price_uk>
  <special_from_date_uk></special_from_date_uk>
  <special_to_date_uk></special_to_date_uk>
  <special_price_de></special_price_de>
  <special_from_date_de></special_from_date_de>
  <special_to_date_de></special_to_date_de>
  <special_price_nl></special_price_nl>
  <special_from_date_nl></special_from_date_nl>
  <special_to_date_nl></special_to_date_nl>
  <special_price_be></special_price_be>
  <special_from_date_be></special_from_date_be>
  <special_to_date_be></special_to_date_be>
  <special_price_fr></special_price_fr>
  <special_from_date_fr></special_from_date_fr>
  <special_to_date_fr></special_to_date_fr>
  <special_price_it></special_price_it>
  <special_from_date_it></special_from_date_it>
  <special_to_date_it></special_to_date_it>
  <special_price_pan_en></special_price_pan_en>
  <special_from_date_pan_en></special_from_date_pan_en>
  <special_to_date_pan_en></special_to_date_pan_en>
  <special_price_pan_es></special_price_pan_es>
  <special_from_date_pan_es></special_from_date_pan_es>
  <special_to_date_pan_es></special_to_date_pan_es>
  <special_price_pan_fr></special_price_pan_fr>
  <special_from_date_pan_fr></special_from_date_pan_fr>
  <special_to_date_pan_fr></special_to_date_pan_fr>
  <special_price_pan_de></special_price_pan_de>
  <special_from_date_pan_de></special_from_date_pan_de>
  <special_to_date_pan_de></special_to_date_pan_de>
  <news_from_date>2012-10-28</news_from_date>
  <image_front>SWS7790PD_front.jpg</image_front>
  <image_back>SWS7790PD_back.jpg</image_back>
  <image_pocket>SWS7790PD_pocket.jpg</image_pocket>
  <image_wash>SWS7790PD_wash.jpg</image_wash>
  <small_image></small_image>
  <thumbnail></thumbnail>
  <url_key></url_key>
  <color></color>
  <bubble_new_collection></bubble_new_collection>
  <bubble_sale></bubble_sale>
  <bubble_best_seller></bubble_best_seller>
  <bubble_limited_edition></bubble_limited_edition>
  <gender>Women</gender>
  <fit_group>STRAIGHT</fit_group>
  <fit_code>STRAIGHT LEG</fit_code>
  <wash_group>MEDIUM WASH</wash_group>
  <enable_special_area>No</enable_special_area>
  <special_area_static_block_id></special_area_static_block_id>
  <delivery_return_static_block_id>product_tab_delivery_return</delivery_return_static_block_id>
  <status>Disabled</status>
  <visibility>Nowhere</visibility>
  <super_attributes>Size</super_attributes>
  <website>base</website>
  <category_ids></category_ids>
  <main_cat_seo></main_cat_seo>
  <details_care></details_care>
</configurable>
