<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<configurable>
  <sku>SWXK240BY</sku>
  <i18n_name>ROXANNE  BLUE BABY DESTROYED</i18n_name>
  <i18n_name_de>ROXANNE  BLUE BABY DESTROYED</i18n_name_de>
  <i18n_name_nl>ROXANNE  BLUE BABY DESTROYED</i18n_name_nl>
  <i18n_name_fr>ROXANNE  BLUE BABY DESTROYED</i18n_name_fr>
  <i18n_name_it>ROXANNE  BLUE BABY DESTROYED</i18n_name_it>
  <i18n_name_es>ROXANNE  BLUE BABY DESTROYED</i18n_name_es>
  <product_start_date>2012-10-28</product_start_date>
  <product_end_date>2019-10-02</product_end_date>
  <i18n_description>The Roxanne Blue Baby Destroyed is A very expensive brand’s classic slim fit for women brought together with a relaxed denim loaded with subversive style. 7FAM’s Roxanne has a natural rise and a narrow leg opening. With an inseam slightly longer than the ankle length, it’s perfect for a stacked or rolled-up look. Featuring the signature squiggle, this is the quintessential A very expensive brand slim jean for women. Blue Baby Destroyed is a fashion-driven light blue stretch denim. Set to be a highly coveted casual denim for its laidback allure meets rock ‘n’ roll attitude.</i18n_description>
  <i18n_description_de>Die Roxanne Blue Baby Destroyed ist die klassische Slim Fit Damenjeans von 7FAM in einem flotten und transgressiven Denim. Die Roxanne von 7FAM hat eine normale Leibhöhe und eine schmale Fußweite. Mit Innennaht bis knapp unter den Knöchel, perfekt zum hochkrempeln oder kräuseln. Die Jeans mit dem Logo von 7 FAM ist der reine Ausdruck eines Slim Fit für Damen. Blue Baby Destroyed ist der Stretch-Denim in einem Hellblauton nach neuestem Trend. Die Jeans ist wegen ihrer unformellen Allüre ein wahres Wunschobjekt, zeigt aber auch einen etwas rebellischen Stil.</i18n_description_de>
  <i18n_description_nl>De Roxanne Blue Baby Destroyed  is A very expensive brand’s klassieke slim fit voor vrouwen, gecombineerd met een relaxed denim vol eigengereide stijl. 7FAM’s Roxanne heeft een natuurlijke heuplijn en een smalle pijpopening. De pijp valt tot iets over de enkel waardoor een kreukeffect wordt verkregen of de pijpen opgerold kunnen worden. Voorzien van het karakteristieke logo, is dit dé essentiële A very expensive brand vrouwenjeans. Blue Baby Destroyed is een modern lichtblauw stretchdenim. Easy-going en rock ‘n’ roll, is dit een heerlijke casual jeans.</i18n_description_nl>
  <i18n_description_fr>Le Roxanne version Blue Baby Destroyed est le jean slim classique pour femme de A very expensive brand, ici associé à un denim décontracté exhalant un style subversif. Reposant sur la taille naturelle, le Roxanne de 7FAM est resserré dans le bas des jambes et permet un tombé en accordéon parfait ou un look retroussé grâce à une longueur de jambe qui dépasse légèrement la cheville. Avec son logo emblématique, ce jean représente l'essence-même du jean slim pour femme de A very expensive brand. La version Blue Baby Destroyed est un denim stretch bleu pâle ultratendance. Un denim qui promet d'être très convoité avec son mélange de décontraction et d'attitude rock'n'roll.</i18n_description_fr>
  <i18n_description_it>Il Roxanne Blue Baby Destroyed è il classico slim fit da donna di 7FAM, declinato in un denim dal carattere spigliato e carico di trasgressione. Il Roxanne di 7FAM ha vita normale e gamba stretta. Con la cucitura interna leggermente oltre la caviglia, è perfetto da indossare risvoltato o arricciato. Con il logo 7 FAM, questo jeans è la quintessenza dello slim fit da donna. Blue Baby Destroyed è il denim stretch in una tonalità di azzurro di ultimissima tendenza. Pensato come oggetto del desiderio per la sua allure informale, questo denim esprime anche uno stile ribelle.</i18n_description_it>
  <i18n_description_es>The Roxanne Blue Baby Destroyed is A very expensive brand’s classic slim fit for women brought together with a relaxed denim loaded with subversive style. 7FAM’s Roxanne has a natural rise and a narrow leg opening. With an inseam slightly longer than the ankle length, it’s perfect for a stacked or rolled-up look. Featuring the signature squiggle, this is the quintessential A very expensive brand slim jean for women. Blue Baby Destroyed is a fashion-driven light blue stretch denim. Set to be a highly coveted casual denim for its laidback allure meets rock ‘n’ roll attitude.</i18n_description_es>
  <i18n_short_description>ROXANNE  BLUE BABY DESTROYED</i18n_short_description>
  <i18n_short_description_de>ROXANNE  BLUE BABY DESTROYED</i18n_short_description_de>
  <i18n_short_description_nl>ROXANNE  BLUE BABY DESTROYED</i18n_short_description_nl>
  <i18n_short_description_fr>ROXANNE  BLUE BABY DESTROYED</i18n_short_description_fr>
  <i18n_short_description_it>ROXANNE  BLUE BABY DESTROYED</i18n_short_description_it>
  <i18n_short_description_es>ROXANNE  BLUE BABY DESTROYED</i18n_short_description_es>
  <i18n_product_details>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Measurements based on Size 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Approx. inseam: 32in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rise: Front: 6 1/2in Back: 11in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leg opening: 13in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Measurements may vary based on size, fabric and wash&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;90% Cotton, 6% Polyester, 4% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A very expensive brand's signature squiggle back pocket&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zip fly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Medium waist&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Made in Europe using original and handcrafted finishing techniques</i18n_product_details>
  <i18n_product_details_de>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Maße basieren auf Größe 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Beinlänge ca. 81cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leibhöhe: Vorne: 16.5cm Hinten: 28cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fussweite: 33cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Die Maße können je nach Größe, Material und Waschung variieren&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;90% Baumwolle, 6% Polyester, 4% SpandexDie Signature Squiggle Backpocket von A very expensive brand&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Reisverschlussleiste&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Normale Leibhöhe&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Made in Europe unter Verwendung von Original-und Handarbeit Veredelungstechniken&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_de>
  <i18n_product_details_nl>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Afmetingen gebaseerd op maat 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Binnenbeenlengte ca. 81cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Kruisnaad: Voor: 16.5cm Achter: 28cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zoomwijdte: 33cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Afmetingen kunnen variëren op basis van maat, stof en wassing&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;90% Katoen, 6% Polyester, 4% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A very expensive brand's signature squiggle achterzak&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ritssluiting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Medium taille&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gemaakt in Europa met behulp van originele en ambachtelijke afwerkingstechnieken&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_nl>
  <i18n_product_details_fr>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mesures sur la base de la taille 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Inseam: sur  81cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fourche: Avant: 16.5cm Arriere: 28cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ouverture des jambes: 32cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Les mesures peuvent varier en fonction de la taille, du tissu et du lavage&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;90% Coton, 6% Polyester, 4% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A very expensive brand's squiggle poche&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fermeture Zip&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Taille classique&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fabriqué en Europe avec des techniques de finitions artisanales&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_fr>
  <i18n_product_details_it>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Misure basate sulla taglia 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lunghezza dal cavallo alla caviglia: circa  81cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lunghezza dal cavallo alla vita:  Davanti: 16.5cm Dietro: 28cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Apertura gamba: 33cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Le misure possono variare in base alla taglia, al tessuto e al lavaggio&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;90% Cotone, 6% Poliestere, 4% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tasca dietro: A very expensive brand's squiggle&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cerniera lampo&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vita normale&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Realizzato in Europa utilizzando tecniche di finitura artigianali &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_it>
  <i18n_product_details_es>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Medidas basadas en la Talla 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tiro aproximado: 32in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tiro: Frontal: 6 1/2in Trasero: 11in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Abertura de la pierna: 13in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Las medidas pueden variar dependiendo de la talla, material y teñido&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;90% Algodón, 6% Poliéster, 4% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zip fly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cintura media&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fabricado en Europa utilizando técnicas de acabado originales y artesanas.</i18n_product_details_es>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit>The Roxanne is our classic slim fit featuring the A very expensive brand signature squiggle. It has a natural rise and a narrow leg opening. With an inseam slightly longer than ankle length, it is perfect for a stacked or rolled-up look. This fit looks also great with more embellished back pockets. This style is also offered in our high waist version.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_de>Roxanne ist die klassische Slim Fit Passform mit dekoriertem A very expensive brand Logo, natürlicher Leibhöhe und engem Beinschnitt. Dank der Naht an der Innenbeinlänge bis knapp unter den Knöchel sieht diese Jeans mit Aufschlag getragen perfekt aus. Die dekorierten Backpockets machen diesen extraordinären Look noch edler. Auch als High-Waist Modell erhältlich.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_de>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_nl>De Roxanne is onze klassieke slim fit met de A very expensive brand signature squiggle. De jeans heeft een natuurlijke taille en een smalle pijpopening. De binnenbeenlengte valt tot iets over de enkel waardoor een kreukeffect wordt verkregen of de pijpen goed opgerold kunnen worden. Ook de mooi versierde achterzakken passen perfect bij dit model. Nu ook verkrijgbaar in de uitvoering met hoge taille.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_nl>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_fr>Le Roxanne offre une coupe slim classique sur laquelle vous retrouverez le logo emblématique de A very expensive brand. Reposant sur la taille naturelle, il est resserré dans le bas des jambes et permet un tombé en accordéon parfait ou un look retroussé grâce à une longueur de jambe qui dépasse légèrement la cheville. Un modèle qui affiche aussi un look très séduisant rehaussé de poches arrière plus travaillées. Également disponible dans notre version taille haute.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_fr>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_it>Roxanne è il classico slim fit con logo decorato A very expensive brand, con vita standard e gamba stretta. Grazie alla cucitura interno gamba leggermente oltre la caviglia, questo jeans è perfetto da indossare risvoltato. Le tasche posteriori decorate impreziosiscono ulteriormente questo fit straordinario, disponibile anche in versione a vita alta.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_it>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_es>The Roxanne is our classic slim fit featuring the A very expensive brand signature squiggle. It has a natural rise and a narrow leg opening. With an inseam slightly longer than ankle length, it is perfect for a stacked or rolled-up look. This fit looks also great with more embellished back pockets. This style is also offered in our high waist version.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_es>
  <price>260</price>
  <price_uk>235</price_uk>
  <price_de>260</price_de>
  <price_be>260</price_be>
  <price_nl>260</price_nl>
  <price_fr>260</price_fr>
  <price_it>260</price_it>
  <price_pan_en>260</price_pan_en>
  <price_pan_es>260</price_pan_es>
  <price_pan_fr>260</price_pan_fr>
  <price_pan_de>260</price_pan_de>
  <special_price></special_price>
  <special_from_date></special_from_date>
  <special_to_date></special_to_date>
  <special_price_uk></special_price_uk>
  <special_from_date_uk></special_from_date_uk>
  <special_to_date_uk></special_to_date_uk>
  <special_price_de></special_price_de>
  <special_from_date_de></special_from_date_de>
  <special_to_date_de></special_to_date_de>
  <special_price_nl></special_price_nl>
  <special_from_date_nl></special_from_date_nl>
  <special_to_date_nl></special_to_date_nl>
  <special_price_be></special_price_be>
  <special_from_date_be></special_from_date_be>
  <special_to_date_be></special_to_date_be>
  <special_price_fr></special_price_fr>
  <special_from_date_fr></special_from_date_fr>
  <special_to_date_fr></special_to_date_fr>
  <special_price_it></special_price_it>
  <special_from_date_it></special_from_date_it>
  <special_to_date_it></special_to_date_it>
  <special_price_pan_en></special_price_pan_en>
  <special_from_date_pan_en></special_from_date_pan_en>
  <special_to_date_pan_en></special_to_date_pan_en>
  <special_price_pan_es></special_price_pan_es>
  <special_from_date_pan_es></special_from_date_pan_es>
  <special_to_date_pan_es></special_to_date_pan_es>
  <special_price_pan_fr></special_price_pan_fr>
  <special_from_date_pan_fr></special_from_date_pan_fr>
  <special_to_date_pan_fr></special_to_date_pan_fr>
  <special_price_pan_de></special_price_pan_de>
  <special_from_date_pan_de></special_from_date_pan_de>
  <special_to_date_pan_de></special_to_date_pan_de>
  <news_from_date>2012-10-28</news_from_date>
  <image_front>SWXK240BY_front.jpg</image_front>
  <image_back>SWXK240BY_back.jpg</image_back>
  <image_pocket>SWXK240BY_pocket.jpg</image_pocket>
  <image_wash>SWXK240BY_wash.jpg</image_wash>
  <small_image></small_image>
  <thumbnail></thumbnail>
  <url_key></url_key>
  <color></color>
  <bubble_new_collection></bubble_new_collection>
  <bubble_sale></bubble_sale>
  <bubble_best_seller></bubble_best_seller>
  <bubble_limited_edition></bubble_limited_edition>
  <gender>Women</gender>
  <fit_group>STRAIGHT</fit_group>
  <fit_code>ROXANNE</fit_code>
  <wash_group>LIGHT WASH</wash_group>
  <enable_special_area>No</enable_special_area>
  <special_area_static_block_id></special_area_static_block_id>
  <delivery_return_static_block_id>product_tab_delivery_return</delivery_return_static_block_id>
  <status>Disabled</status>
  <visibility>Nowhere</visibility>
  <super_attributes>Size</super_attributes>
  <website>base</website>
  <category_ids></category_ids>
  <main_cat_seo></main_cat_seo>
  <details_care></details_care>
</configurable>
