<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<configurable>
  <sku>SW5J05CHS</sku>
  <i18n_name>KIMMIE BOOTCUT WITH SQUIGGLE AND SWAROVSKI EARTHSOUL</i18n_name>
  <i18n_name_de>KIMMIE BOOTCUT WITH SQUIGGLE AND SWAROVSKI EARTHSOUL</i18n_name_de>
  <i18n_name_nl>KIMMIE BOOTCUT WITH SQUIGGLE AND SWAROVSKI EARTHSOUL</i18n_name_nl>
  <i18n_name_fr>KIMMIE BOOTCUT WITH SQUIGGLE AND SWAROVSKI EARTHSOUL</i18n_name_fr>
  <i18n_name_it>KIMMIE BOOTCUT WITH SQUIGGLE AND SWAROVSKI EARTHSOUL</i18n_name_it>
  <i18n_name_es>KIMMIE BOOTCUT WITH SQUIGGLE AND SWAROVSKI EARTHSOUL</i18n_name_es>
  <product_start_date>2012-04-01</product_start_date>
  <product_end_date>2017-05-02</product_end_date>
  <i18n_description>The new Kimmie Bootcut Self Lasered Squiggle and Swarovski Earthsoul is 7FAM’s sexy curvy women’s jean and a wardrobe hero. Designed especially for curvy girls, the Kimmie Bootcut has a contoured waistband and a slightly higher rise to hug your waist all round. The classic bootcut leg opening enhances the dramatic silhouette. Earthsoul is the perfect laidback denim to match this fit. A warm sand cast creates a slightly dirty appearance to the loveworn vintage-look wash while the fabric boasts outstanding softness, thanks to a new generation fibre that gives smoothness and high durability in equal measure. Swarovski crystals embellish our signature squiggle to complete the flirtatious allure of this easy women’s jean. Why not have luxury everyday?</i18n_description>
  <i18n_description_de>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Die neue Kimmie Bootcut Self Lasered Squiggle and Swarovski Earthsoul ist 7FAMs sexy kurvige Damenjeans und eine Heldin aller Garderoben&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;speziell für Ladys mit Formen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;die Kimmie Bootcut hat einen konturierten Bund und eine leicht höhere Leibhöhe&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;setzt Ihre Taille perfekt in Szene&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;die klassische Bootcut-Passform verstärkt die dramatische Silhouette&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Earthsoul ist der perfekte lässige Denim für diese Passform&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;ein warmer Sandschimmer erzeugt einen leicht verwegenen Effekt für den liebevollen Used-Look im Vintage-Design&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;das Material ist herrlich weich dank einer neuen Faser, die für Weichheit und hohe Langlebigkeit sorgt&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Swarovski-Kristalle verzieren unser Signature Squiggle und verleihen der koketten Ausstrahlung dieser unkomplizierten Damenjeans den letzten Schliff&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;warum sollten Sie sich nicht jeden Tag etwas Luxus gönnen?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_description_de>
  <i18n_description_nl>De nieuwe Kimmie Bootcut Self Lasered Squiggle and Swarovski Earthsoul is de sexy vrouwenjeans van 7FAM voor vrouwen met iets rondere vormen en een echte garderobehit. De Kimmie Bootcut is speciaal ontworpen voor meisjes met rondingen en heeft een bredere broeksband en een iets hogere taille om je middel volledig te stroomlijnen. Deze klassieke bootcut die uitwaaiert aan de onderpijpen, biedt een opvallend silhouet. Earthsoul is de perfecte relaxte denim voor dit model. De warme zandkleur geeft deze mooi afgedragen vintage wassing een ietwat vuile look, terwijl de stof bijzonder zacht is dankzij de vezel van de nieuwe generatie die even soepel als duurzaam is. Swarovski-kristallen verfraaien onze signature squiggle en vervolmaken de elegante uitstraling van deze uitzonderlijke vrouwenjeans. Waarom niet elke dag in luxe baden?</i18n_description_nl>
  <i18n_description_fr>Le nouveau Kimmie Bootcut version Earthsoul avec logo travaillé au laser rehaussé de strass Swarovski est le jean à la coupe flatteuse incontournable de 7FAM. Conçu pour les femmes aux courbes généreuses, il est doté d’une ceinture et d’une taille légèrement plus haute qui galbent bien la silhouette. Il se termine en bas par une coupe semi-évasée classique qui allonge la silhouette et se marie parfaitement avec le denim Earthsoul : la teinte sable chaud de ce lavage usé et vintage offre un look grunge adouci par la texture du tissu, incroyablement souple et très résistant grâce à ses fibres nouvelle génération. Les strass Swarovski qui ornent le fameux logo brodé de 7FAM apportent la touche finale à ce jean sexy et facile à porter. Pourquoi se priver de luxe quand il est à porter de la main ?</i18n_description_fr>
  <i18n_description_it>Il nuovo jeans da donna super sexy Kimmie Bootcut Self Lasered Squiggle and Swarovski Earthsoul ha tutte le carte in tavola per diventare un pezzo cult del vostro guardaroba. Questo modello a vita leggermente più alta, dedicato alle donne tutte curve, ha una cintura particolarmente avvolgente per abbracciare la vita. Il classico taglio bootcut slancia la silhouette. Earthsoul è un denim casual davvero perfetto. Il caldo color sabbia crea un effetto leggermente “sporco”, ideale per chi ama un look vintage effetto used. Il tessuto, invece, rivela una morbidezza straordinaria grazie a una fibra di nuova generazione che garantisce al contempo massima resistenza. Infine, i cristalli Swarovski decorano il logo ricamato per completare l’allure seducente di questo modello easy. Perché rinunciare al lusso?</i18n_description_it>
  <i18n_description_es>The new Kimmie Bootcut Self Lasered Squiggle and Swarovski Earthsoul is 7FAM’s sexy curvy women’s jean and a wardrobe hero. Designed especially for curvy girls, the Kimmie Bootcut has a contoured waistband and a slightly higher rise to hug your waist all round. The classic bootcut leg opening enhances the dramatic silhouette. Earthsoul is the perfect laidback denim to match this fit. A warm sand cast creates a slightly dirty appearance to the loveworn vintage-look wash while the fabric boasts outstanding softness, thanks to a new generation fibre that gives smoothness and high durability in equal measure. Swarovski crystals embellish our signature squiggle to complete the flirtatious allure of this easy women’s jean. Why not have luxury everyday?</i18n_description_es>
  <i18n_short_description>KIMMIE BOOTCUT WITH SQUIGGLE AND SWAROVSKI EARTHSOUL</i18n_short_description>
  <i18n_short_description_de>KIMMIE BOOTCUT WITH SQUIGGLE AND SWAROVSKI EARTHSOUL</i18n_short_description_de>
  <i18n_short_description_nl>KIMMIE BOOTCUT WITH SQUIGGLE AND SWAROVSKI EARTHSOUL</i18n_short_description_nl>
  <i18n_short_description_fr>KIMMIE BOOTCUT WITH SQUIGGLE AND SWAROVSKI EARTHSOUL</i18n_short_description_fr>
  <i18n_short_description_it>KIMMIE BOOTCUT WITH SQUIGGLE AND SWAROVSKI EARTHSOUL</i18n_short_description_it>
  <i18n_short_description_es>KIMMIE BOOTCUT WITH SQUIGGLE AND SWAROVSKI EARTHSOUL</i18n_short_description_es>
  <i18n_product_details>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Approx. inseam: 35in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rise: Front: 6 3/4in Back: 11 3/4in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leg opening: 18in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;89% Cotton 11% Elastomultiester&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A very expensive brand's signature squiggle back pocket&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zip fly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Made in Europe using original and handcrafted finishing techniques&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details>
  <i18n_product_details_de>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Beinlänge ca.  89cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leibhöhe: Vorne: 17cm Hinten: 30cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fussweite: 46cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;89% Baumwolle 11% Elastomultiester&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Die Signature Squiggle Backpocket von A very expensive brand&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Reisverschlussleiste&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Made in Europe unter Verwendung von Original-und Handarbeit Veredelungstechniken&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_de>
  <i18n_product_details_nl>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Binnenbeenlengte ca.  89cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Kruisnaad: Voor: 17cm Achter: 30cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zoomwijdte: 46cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;89% Katoen 11% Elastomultiester&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A very expensive brand's signature squiggle achterzak&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ritssluiting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gemaakt in Europa met behulp van originele en ambachtelijke afwerkingstechnieken&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_nl>
  <i18n_product_details_fr>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Inseam: sur  89cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fourche: Avant: 17cm Arrière: 30cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ouverture des jambes: 46cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;89% Coton 11% Élastomultiester&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A very expensive brand's squiggle poche&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fermeture Zip&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fabriqué en Europe avec des techniques de finitions artisanales&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_fr>
  <i18n_product_details_it>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lunghezza dal cavallo alla caviglia: circa  89cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lunghezza dal cavallo alla vita: Davanti: 17cm Dietro: 30cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Apertura gamba: 46cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;89% Cotone 11% Elastomultiestere&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tasca Dietro: A very expensive brand's squiggle&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cerniera lampo&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Realizzato in Europa utilizzando tecniche di finitura artigianali&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_it>
  <i18n_product_details_es>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tiro aproximado: 35in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tiro: Frontal: 6 3/4in Trasero: 11 3/4in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Abertura de la pierna: 18in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;89% Algodón 11% Elastomultiéster&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zip fly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fabricado en Europa utilizando técnicas de acabado originales y artesanas.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_es>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit>Kimmie is our sexy curvy jean. Designed especially for the curvy girl, it has a contoured waistband and a slightly higher rise to hug your waist all around. The classic bootcut silhouette features our signature squiggle or a variety of back pocket designs.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_de>Kimmie ist unsere sexy curvy Passform, speziell designt für Frauen mit weiblicherer Figur. Sie besitzt einen konturformenden Bund mit etwas höherer Leibhöhe und passt sich dadurch perfekt Ihrer Figur an. Die klassische Bootcut-Silhouette ist mit unserem "Squiggle"-Logo und verschiedenen anderen Taschendesigns erhältlich.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_de>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_nl>Kimmie is onze sexy jeans voor het maatje meer. Speciaal bestemd voor meisjes met rondingen, met een bredere broeksband en een iets hogere taille om je middel volledig te stroomlijnen. Het klassieke bootcut-silhouet is uitgevoerd met onze signature squiggle of een van de vele andere ontwerpen op de achterzak.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_nl>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_fr>Le Kimmie est le jean qui met en valeur les courbes de façon très sexy. Conçu pour les femmes aux courbes généreuses, la ceinture et la taille légèrement plus haute galbent bien la silhouette. Ce modèle à la coupe bootcut classique est orné du logo brodé ou de divers motifs sur les poches arrière.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_fr>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_it>Kimmie è il nostro jeans super sexy. Questo modello a vita leggermente più alta, dedicato alle donne tutte curve, ha una cintura particolarmente avvolgente per abbracciare la vita. Il suo classico taglio bootcut sfoggia il logo ricamato o numerosi dettagli sulla tasca posteriore.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_it>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_es>Kimmie is our sexy curvy jean. Designed especially for the curvy girl, it has a contoured waistband and a slightly higher rise to hug your waist all around. The classic bootcut silhouette features our signature squiggle or a variety of back pocket designs.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_es>
  <price>279</price>
  <price_uk>255</price_uk>
  <price_de>279</price_de>
  <price_be>279</price_be>
  <price_nl>279</price_nl>
  <price_fr>279</price_fr>
  <price_it>279</price_it>
  <price_pan_en>279</price_pan_en>
  <price_pan_es>279</price_pan_es>
  <price_pan_fr>279</price_pan_fr>
  <price_pan_de>279</price_pan_de>
  <special_price></special_price>
  <special_from_date></special_from_date>
  <special_to_date></special_to_date>
  <special_price_uk></special_price_uk>
  <special_from_date_uk></special_from_date_uk>
  <special_to_date_uk></special_to_date_uk>
  <special_price_de></special_price_de>
  <special_from_date_de></special_from_date_de>
  <special_to_date_de></special_to_date_de>
  <special_price_nl></special_price_nl>
  <special_from_date_nl></special_from_date_nl>
  <special_to_date_nl></special_to_date_nl>
  <special_price_be></special_price_be>
  <special_from_date_be></special_from_date_be>
  <special_to_date_be></special_to_date_be>
  <special_price_fr></special_price_fr>
  <special_from_date_fr></special_from_date_fr>
  <special_to_date_fr></special_to_date_fr>
  <special_price_it></special_price_it>
  <special_from_date_it></special_from_date_it>
  <special_to_date_it></special_to_date_it>
  <special_price_pan_en></special_price_pan_en>
  <special_from_date_pan_en></special_from_date_pan_en>
  <special_to_date_pan_en></special_to_date_pan_en>
  <special_price_pan_es></special_price_pan_es>
  <special_from_date_pan_es></special_from_date_pan_es>
  <special_to_date_pan_es></special_to_date_pan_es>
  <special_price_pan_fr></special_price_pan_fr>
  <special_from_date_pan_fr></special_from_date_pan_fr>
  <special_to_date_pan_fr></special_to_date_pan_fr>
  <special_price_pan_de></special_price_pan_de>
  <special_from_date_pan_de></special_from_date_pan_de>
  <special_to_date_pan_de></special_to_date_pan_de>
  <news_from_date>2012-04-01</news_from_date>
  <image_front>SW5J05CHS_front.jpg</image_front>
  <image_back>SW5J05CHS_back.jpg</image_back>
  <image_pocket>SW5J05CHS_pocket.jpg</image_pocket>
  <image_wash>SW5J05CHS_wash.jpg</image_wash>
  <small_image></small_image>
  <thumbnail></thumbnail>
  <url_key></url_key>
  <color></color>
  <bubble_new_collection></bubble_new_collection>
  <bubble_sale></bubble_sale>
  <bubble_best_seller></bubble_best_seller>
  <bubble_limited_edition></bubble_limited_edition>
  <gender>Women</gender>
  <fit_group>BOOTCUT</fit_group>
  <fit_code>KIMMIE</fit_code>
  <wash_group>MEDIUM WASH</wash_group>
  <enable_special_area>No</enable_special_area>
  <special_area_static_block_id></special_area_static_block_id>
  <delivery_return_static_block_id>product_tab_delivery_return</delivery_return_static_block_id>
  <status>Disabled</status>
  <visibility>Nowhere</visibility>
  <super_attributes>size</super_attributes>
  <website>base</website>
  <category_ids></category_ids>
  <main_cat_seo></main_cat_seo>
  <details_care></details_care>
</configurable>
