<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<configurable>
  <sku>SWTK240BY</sku>
  <i18n_name>THE SKINNY  BLUE BABY</i18n_name>
  <i18n_name_de>THE SKINNY  BLUE BABY</i18n_name_de>
  <i18n_name_nl>THE SKINNY  BLUE BABY</i18n_name_nl>
  <i18n_name_fr>THE SKINNY  BLUE BABY</i18n_name_fr>
  <i18n_name_it>THE SKINNY  BLUE BABY</i18n_name_it>
  <i18n_name_es>THE SKINNY  BLUE BABY</i18n_name_es>
  <product_start_date>2012-10-28</product_start_date>
  <product_end_date>2019-10-02</product_end_date>
  <i18n_description>The Skinny Baby Blue is A very expensive brand’s body-sculpting women’s jean in a fashion-savvy light blue wash. The Skinny is a second-skin, super-stretch fit characterised by its minimal detailing, clean pockets, comfortable straight rise and a slim, sexy, fitted silhouette top to bottom. The length hits just below the ankle to maintain a clean line with no stacking. This provocative, street-savvy fit is loaded with seductive power in Blue Baby, 7FAM’s individualistic light blue stretch denim. Blue Baby is a trend-leader of pale denim, set apart by its fresh and youthful mood. The living is definitely easy with the perfect dose of stretch and laidback attitude.</i18n_description>
  <i18n_description_de>Die Skinny Baby Blue ist die figurbetonende Damenjeans von A very expensive brand in einer hochaktuellen hellblauen Waschung.  Diese Skinny von A very expensive brand sorgt wie eine zweite Haut für einen Super-Stretch-Fit und besitzt minimalistische Details, sauber geschnittene Taschen, eine gerade und bequeme Leibhöhe und eine durchweg enganliegende, sexy und schlanke Linie.  Die Länge reicht knapp unter den Knöchel und sorgt für eine absolut saubere Linie. Dieser provokante, sehr metropolitane Fit ist in der Waschung Blue Baby, dem einzigartig hellblauen Stretch-Denim von 7FAM, höchst verführerisch. Blue Baby ist eine helle Jeans, die einen Trend setzt und sich durch ihren jungen und frischen Charakter auszeichnet.   Mit dem richtigen Stretchanteil und einem unformellen Charakter wird alles viel einfacher.</i18n_description_de>
  <i18n_description_nl>De Skinny Baby Blue is A very expensive brand’s nauwsluitende vrouwenjeans in een moderne lichtblauwe wassing. De Skinny is een superstretch model dat aansluit als een tweede huid, met minimale details, sobere zakken en een comfortabele rechte heuplijn, en van top tot teen voor een slank en sexy silhouet zorgt. De jeans valt tot net onder de enkel voor een simpele lijn zonder kreukels. Dit uitdagende streetwise model is enorm verleidelijk in Blue Baby, 7FAM’s individualistische lichtblauwe stretchdenim. Blue Baby is leider in de trend van lichtgekleurd denim en heeft een frisse en jeugdige uitstraling. Met de perfecte dosis stretch en een relaxte stijl is het leven een stuk eenvoudiger.</i18n_description_nl>
  <i18n_description_fr>Le Skinny version Baby Blue est le jean moulant pour femme de A very expensive brand, ici présenté dans un lavage bleu pâle très tendance. Le Skinny possède une coupe ultra-stretch seconde peau très flatteuse pour votre silhouette qui se distingue par ses détails minimalistes, ses poches nettes, sa taille droite et confortable et sa silhouette slim sexy et ajustée sur toute sa longueur. La longueur de jambe tombe juste en dessous de la cheville, pour un jean qui reste parfaitement clean et droit. Le denim Baby Blue, du nom de ce denim stretch bleu pâle très particulier créé par 7FAM, insuffle à cette coupe provocante et tendance un pouvoir résolument séducteur. Véritable tête de file de la tendance denim pâle, ce Baby Blue se distingue par son côté frais et plein de jeunesse. Et avec juste ce qu'il faut de stretch et de décontraction, voilà un jean résolument facile à vivre.</i18n_description_fr>
  <i18n_description_it>Lo Skinny Baby Blue è il jeans da donna di A very expensive brand che modella il fisico con il suo lavaggio  azzurro di gran tendenza.  Lo Skinny di A very expensive brand è un fit super stretch, quasi una seconda pelle, caratterizzato da dettagli minimal e tasche di linea pulita, vita dritta e confortevole e una linea aderente, sexy e asciutta dall’alto al basso.  La lunghezza appena sotto la caviglia regala una linea decisamente pulita e senza arricciature. Questo fit provocante, estremamente metropolitano, esprime grande seduzione nella versione Blue Baby, l’originalissimo strech denim azzurro di 7FAM. Blue Baby è un jeans chiaro che fa tendenza e si distingue per il suo carattere giovane e fresco.   Con la giusta percentuale di stretch e un tono informale, tutto diventa più facile.</i18n_description_it>
  <i18n_description_es>The Skinny Baby Blue is A very expensive brand’s body-sculpting women’s jean in a fashion-savvy light blue wash. The Skinny is a second-skin, super-stretch fit characterised by its minimal detailing, clean pockets, comfortable straight rise and a slim, sexy, fitted silhouette top to bottom. The length hits just below the ankle to maintain a clean line with no stacking. This provocative, street-savvy fit is loaded with seductive power in Blue Baby, 7FAM’s individualistic light blue stretch denim. Blue Baby is a trend-leader of pale denim, set apart by its fresh and youthful mood. The living is definitely easy with the perfect dose of stretch and laidback attitude.</i18n_description_es>
  <i18n_short_description>THE SKINNY  BLUE BABY</i18n_short_description>
  <i18n_short_description_de>THE SKINNY  BLUE BABY</i18n_short_description_de>
  <i18n_short_description_nl>THE SKINNY  BLUE BABY</i18n_short_description_nl>
  <i18n_short_description_fr>THE SKINNY  BLUE BABY</i18n_short_description_fr>
  <i18n_short_description_it>THE SKINNY  BLUE BABY</i18n_short_description_it>
  <i18n_short_description_es>THE SKINNY  BLUE BABY</i18n_short_description_es>
  <i18n_product_details>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Measurements based on Size 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Approx. inseam: 30in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rise: Front: 7in Back: 11 1/2in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leg opening: 10 1/2in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Measurements may vary based on size, fabric and wash&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;90% Cotton, 6% Polyester, 4% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A very expensive brand's signature squiggle back pocket&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zip fly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Medium waist&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Made in Europe using original and handcrafted finishing techniques</i18n_product_details>
  <i18n_product_details_de>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Maße basieren auf Größe 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Beinlänge ca. 76cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leibhöhe: Vorne: 18cm Hinten: 29cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fussweite: 26.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Die Maße können je nach Größe, Material und Waschung variieren&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;90% Baumwolle, 6% Polyester, 4% SpandexDie Signature Squiggle Backpocket von A very expensive brand&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Reisverschlussleiste&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Normale Leibhöhe&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Made in Europe unter Verwendung von Original-und Handarbeit Veredelungstechniken&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_de>
  <i18n_product_details_nl>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Afmetingen gebaseerd op maat 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Binnenbeenlengte ca. 76cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Kruisnaad: Voor: 18cm Achter: 29cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zoomwijdte: 26.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Afmetingen kunnen variëren op basis van maat, stof en wassing&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;90% Katoen, 6% Polyester, 4% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A very expensive brand's signature squiggle achterzak&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ritssluiting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Medium taille&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gemaakt in Europa met behulp van originele en ambachtelijke afwerkingstechnieken&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_nl>
  <i18n_product_details_fr>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mesures sur la base de la taille 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Inseam: sur  76cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fourche: Avant: 18cm Arriere: 29cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ouverture des jambes: 26.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Les mesures peuvent varier en fonction de la taille, du tissu et du lavage&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;90% Coton, 6% Polyester, 4% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A very expensive brand's squiggle poche&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fermeture Zip&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Taille classique&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fabriqué en Europe avec des techniques de finitions artisanales&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_fr>
  <i18n_product_details_it>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Misure basate sulla taglia 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lunghezza dal cavallo alla caviglia: circa  76cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lunghezza dal cavallo alla vita:  Davanti: 18cm Dietro: 29cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Apertura gamba: 26.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Le misure possono variare in base alla taglia, al tessuto e al lavaggio&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;90% Cotone, 6% Poliestere, 4% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tasca dietro: A very expensive brand's squiggle&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cerniera lampo&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vita normale&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Realizzato in Europa utilizzando tecniche di finitura artigianali &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_it>
  <i18n_product_details_es>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Medidas basadas en la Talla 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tiro aproximado: 30in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tiro: Frontal: 7in Trasero: 11 1/2in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Abertura de la pierna: 10 1/2in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Las medidas pueden variar dependiendo de la talla, material y teñido&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;90% Algodón, 6% Poliéster, 4% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zip fly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cintura media&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fabricado en Europa utilizando técnicas de acabado originales y artesanas.</i18n_product_details_es>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit>Characterised by its minimal detailing, The Skinny has a comfortable rise with a slim, sexy, and fitted silhouette top to bottom. The length hits at the ankle to maintain a clean line with no stacking.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_de>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimalistische Verzierungen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;die Skinny hat eine bequeme Leibhöhe und eine durchweg schmale, sexy und eng anliegende Silhouette&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;endet kurz über dem Knöchel und garantiert einen cleanen Look mit schmaler Silhouette&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_de>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_nl>De Skinny wordt gekenmerkt door minimale details en heeft een comfortabele heuplijn met een slank, sexy en aansluitend silhouet van top tot teen. De lengte gaat mooi tot de enkel voor een pure lijn zonder kreuken.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_nl>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_fr>Orné de détails raffinés, le Skinny est confortable à la taille avec une coupe plus ajustée très sexy qui épouse à merveille l’ensemble de la silhouette. Son tombé bien ajusté jusqu’à la cheville lui confère une ligne impeccable et sans plis.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_fr>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_it>Il modello Skinny, con dettagli minimal e vita confortevole, disegna una figura sexy e sottile da capo a piedi! L’orlo arriva alla caviglia per un taglio deciso senza arricciature.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_it>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_es>Characterised by its minimal detailing, The Skinny has a comfortable rise with a slim, sexy, and fitted silhouette top to bottom. The length hits at the ankle to maintain a clean line with no stacking.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_es>
  <price>240</price>
  <price_uk>220</price_uk>
  <price_de>240</price_de>
  <price_be>240</price_be>
  <price_nl>240</price_nl>
  <price_fr>240</price_fr>
  <price_it>240</price_it>
  <price_pan_en>240</price_pan_en>
  <price_pan_es>240</price_pan_es>
  <price_pan_fr>240</price_pan_fr>
  <price_pan_de>240</price_pan_de>
  <special_price></special_price>
  <special_from_date></special_from_date>
  <special_to_date></special_to_date>
  <special_price_uk></special_price_uk>
  <special_from_date_uk></special_from_date_uk>
  <special_to_date_uk></special_to_date_uk>
  <special_price_de></special_price_de>
  <special_from_date_de></special_from_date_de>
  <special_to_date_de></special_to_date_de>
  <special_price_nl></special_price_nl>
  <special_from_date_nl></special_from_date_nl>
  <special_to_date_nl></special_to_date_nl>
  <special_price_be></special_price_be>
  <special_from_date_be></special_from_date_be>
  <special_to_date_be></special_to_date_be>
  <special_price_fr></special_price_fr>
  <special_from_date_fr></special_from_date_fr>
  <special_to_date_fr></special_to_date_fr>
  <special_price_it></special_price_it>
  <special_from_date_it></special_from_date_it>
  <special_to_date_it></special_to_date_it>
  <special_price_pan_en></special_price_pan_en>
  <special_from_date_pan_en></special_from_date_pan_en>
  <special_to_date_pan_en></special_to_date_pan_en>
  <special_price_pan_es></special_price_pan_es>
  <special_from_date_pan_es></special_from_date_pan_es>
  <special_to_date_pan_es></special_to_date_pan_es>
  <special_price_pan_fr></special_price_pan_fr>
  <special_from_date_pan_fr></special_from_date_pan_fr>
  <special_to_date_pan_fr></special_to_date_pan_fr>
  <special_price_pan_de></special_price_pan_de>
  <special_from_date_pan_de></special_from_date_pan_de>
  <special_to_date_pan_de></special_to_date_pan_de>
  <news_from_date>2012-10-28</news_from_date>
  <image_front>SWTK240BY_front.jpg</image_front>
  <image_back>SWTK240BY_back.jpg</image_back>
  <image_pocket>SWTK240BY_pocket.jpg</image_pocket>
  <image_wash>SWTK240BY_wash.jpg</image_wash>
  <small_image></small_image>
  <thumbnail></thumbnail>
  <url_key></url_key>
  <color></color>
  <bubble_new_collection></bubble_new_collection>
  <bubble_sale></bubble_sale>
  <bubble_best_seller></bubble_best_seller>
  <bubble_limited_edition></bubble_limited_edition>
  <gender>Women</gender>
  <fit_group>SKINNY</fit_group>
  <fit_code>THE SKINNY</fit_code>
  <wash_group>LIGHT WASH</wash_group>
  <enable_special_area>No</enable_special_area>
  <special_area_static_block_id></special_area_static_block_id>
  <delivery_return_static_block_id>product_tab_delivery_return</delivery_return_static_block_id>
  <status>Disabled</status>
  <visibility>Nowhere</visibility>
  <super_attributes>Size</super_attributes>
  <website>base</website>
  <category_ids></category_ids>
  <main_cat_seo></main_cat_seo>
  <details_care></details_care>
</configurable>
