<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<configurable>
  <sku>SWTK110EB</sku>
  <i18n_name>THE SKINNY  GEOMETRIC BLUE DENIM DEEP BLUE</i18n_name>
  <i18n_name_de>THE SKINNY  GEOMETRIC BLUE DENIM DEEP BLUE</i18n_name_de>
  <i18n_name_nl>THE SKINNY  GEOMETRIC BLUE DENIM DEEP BLUE</i18n_name_nl>
  <i18n_name_fr>THE SKINNY  GEOMETRIC BLUE DENIM DEEP BLUE</i18n_name_fr>
  <i18n_name_it>THE SKINNY  GEOMETRIC BLUE DENIM DEEP BLUE</i18n_name_it>
  <i18n_name_es>THE SKINNY  GEOMETRIC BLUE DENIM DEEP BLUE</i18n_name_es>
  <product_start_date>2012-10-28</product_start_date>
  <product_end_date>2019-10-02</product_end_date>
  <i18n_description>The Skinny Geometric Blue Denim Deep Blue is a head-turning women’s jean to lead the future of geometric prints. A very expensive brand’s The Skinny is a body-sculpting, super-stretch fit characterised by its minimal detailing, clean pockets, comfortable straight rise and a slim, sexy, fitted silhouette top to bottom. The length hits just below the ankle to maintain a clean line with no stacking. This provocative, street-savvy fit is beautiful blended with 7FAM’s geometric printed denim in Deep Blue. The directional design takes its fashion cue from city textures and geometrics. The lasered geometric print is overcoated, giving a cityscape sheen while the perfect amount of stretch makes this trophy women’s jean blissfully easywearing too. For an edgy evening statement, shape up in graphic jeans.</i18n_description>
  <i18n_description_de>Die Skinny Geometric Blue Denim Deep Blue ist eine Damenjeans, die nicht gerne unbemerkt bleibt und den neuesten Trends der geometrischen Druckmuster vorgreift.   Diese Skinny von A very expensive brand formt die Silhouette mit ihrem Super-Stretch-Gewebe und besitzt minimalistische Details, sauber geschnittene Taschen, eine gerade und bequeme Leibhöhe und eine durchweg enganliegende, sexy und schlanke Linie.  Die Länge reicht knapp unter den Knöchel und sorgt für eine absolut saubere Linie ohne Kräuselungen. Dieser kecke  metropolitane Fit ist wunderschön in dem Stretch-Denim mit geometrischem Druckmuster in Deep Blue von 7FAM.   Das hochaktuelle Design inspiriert sich an metropolitanen Geometrien und Texturen.   Der geometrische Laserdruck bildet urban wirkende Reflexe, während das richtige Ausmaß an Stretch für einen sublimen Tragkomfort dieser prestigereichen Damenjeans sorgt.  Tragen Sie diese schöne grafische Jeans und der Abend wird intrigant.</i18n_description_de>
  <i18n_description_nl>De Skinny Geometric Blue Denim Deep Blue is een opvallende vrouwenjeans die hoog scoort in de trend van geometrische prints. A very expensive brand's Skinny is een nauwsluitend superstretch model met minimale details, sobere zakken en een comfortabele rechte heuplijn dat van top tot teen voor een slank en sexy silhouet zorgt. De jeans valt tot net onder de enkel voor een simpele lijn zonder kreukels. Dit uitdagende streetwise model is mooi gecombineerd met 7FAM’s denim met geometrische prints in Deep Blue. Het toonaangevende design vindt zijn inspiratie in stadse texturen en geometrische vormen. De gelaserde geometrische print krijgt door een coating een cityscape glans terwijl het perfecte stretchgehalte deze topjeans heerlijk draagbaar maakt. Draag deze grafische jeans voor een originele avondlook.</i18n_description_nl>
  <i18n_description_fr>Le Skinny version Geometric Blue Denim Deep Blue est un jean femme bien décidé à mener la danse dans le domaine des imprimés géométriques. Avec lui, vous ferez tourner les têtes ! Le Skinny de A very expensive brand possède une coupe ultra-stretch très flatteuse pour votre silhouette qui se distingue par ses détails minimalistes, ses poches nettes, sa taille droite et confortable et sa silhouette slim sexy et ajustée sur toute sa longueur. La longueur de jambe tombe juste en dessous de la cheville, pour un jean qui reste parfaitement clean et droit. Cette coupe provocante et ultratendance forme une association de toute beauté avec le denim à imprimé géométrique de 7FAM, ici présenté en version Deep Blue. Ce modèle très mode s'inspire des textures et formes géométriques urbaines. L'imprimé géométrique réalisé au laser est recouvert d'une enduction offrant un moiré résolument urbain, tandis que son élasticité justement dosée fait de ce jean-trophée pour femme une pièce merveilleusement agréable à porter. Pour afficher un look résolument pointu en soirée, parez votre silhouette de ce jean graphique.</i18n_description_fr>
  <i18n_description_it>Lo Skinny Geometric Blue Denim Deep Blue è il jeans da donna che non ama passare inosservato e che anticipa le nuovissime tendenze delle stampe geometriche.  Lo Skinny di A very expensive brand modella la silhouette con il suo super-stretch; è caratterizzato da dettagli minimal, tasche di linea pulita, vita dritta e confortevole e una linea aderente, sexy e asciutta dall’altro in basso.  La lunghezza appena sotto la caviglia regala una linea decisamente pulita e senza arricciature. Questo fit metropolitano e audace è bellissimo declinato nel denim stretch a stampa geometrica in Deep Blue di 7FAM.   Il design attualissimo prende spunto da geometrie e texture metropolitane. La stampa geometrica laserata manda riflessi di gusto urban, mentre la giusta percentuale di stretch regala a questo prestigioso jeans  una vestibilità sublime.  Per una serata intrigante, sfoggiate questo bel jeans grafico.</i18n_description_it>
  <i18n_description_es>The Skinny Geometric Blue Denim Deep Blue is a head-turning women’s jean to lead the future of geometric prints. A very expensive brand’s The Skinny is a body-sculpting, super-stretch fit characterised by its minimal detailing, clean pockets, comfortable straight rise and a slim, sexy, fitted silhouette top to bottom. The length hits just below the ankle to maintain a clean line with no stacking. This provocative, street-savvy fit is beautiful blended with 7FAM’s geometric printed denim in Deep Blue. The directional design takes its fashion cue from city textures and geometrics. The lasered geometric print is overcoated, giving a cityscape sheen while the perfect amount of stretch makes this trophy women’s jean blissfully easywearing too. For an edgy evening statement, shape up in graphic jeans.</i18n_description_es>
  <i18n_short_description>THE SKINNY  GEOMETRIC BLUE DENIM DEEP BLUE</i18n_short_description>
  <i18n_short_description_de>THE SKINNY  GEOMETRIC BLUE DENIM DEEP BLUE</i18n_short_description_de>
  <i18n_short_description_nl>THE SKINNY  GEOMETRIC BLUE DENIM DEEP BLUE</i18n_short_description_nl>
  <i18n_short_description_fr>THE SKINNY  GEOMETRIC BLUE DENIM DEEP BLUE</i18n_short_description_fr>
  <i18n_short_description_it>THE SKINNY  GEOMETRIC BLUE DENIM DEEP BLUE</i18n_short_description_it>
  <i18n_short_description_es>THE SKINNY  GEOMETRIC BLUE DENIM DEEP BLUE</i18n_short_description_es>
  <i18n_product_details>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Measurements based on Size 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Approx. inseam: 30in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rise: Front: 7in Back: 11 1/2in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leg opening: 10 1/2in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Measurements may vary based on size, fabric and wash&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;62% Cotton, 38% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Clean pocket&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zip fly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Medium waist&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Made in Europe using original and handcrafted finishing techniques</i18n_product_details>
  <i18n_product_details_de>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Maße basieren auf Größe 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Beinlänge ca. 76cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leibhöhe: Vorne: 18cm Hinten: 29cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fussweite: 26.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Die Maße können je nach Größe, Material und Waschung variieren&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;62% Baumwolle, 38% SpandexClean Pocket&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Reisverschlussleiste&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Normale Leibhöhe&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Made in Europe unter Verwendung von Original-und Handarbeit Veredelungstechniken&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_de>
  <i18n_product_details_nl>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Afmetingen gebaseerd op maat 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Binnenbeenlengte ca. 76cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Kruisnaad: Voor: 18cm Achter: 29cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zoomwijdte: 26.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Afmetingen kunnen variëren op basis van maat, stof en wassing&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;62% Katoen, 38% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Achterzak zonder squiggle&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ritssluiting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Medium taille&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gemaakt in Europa met behulp van originele en ambachtelijke afwerkingstechnieken&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_nl>
  <i18n_product_details_fr>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mesures sur la base de la taille 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Inseam: sur  76cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fourche: Avant: 18cm Arriere: 29cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ouverture des jambes: 26.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Les mesures peuvent varier en fonction de la taille, du tissu et du lavage&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;62% Coton, 38% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Clean poche&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fermeture Zip&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Taille classique&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fabriqué en Europe avec des techniques de finitions artisanales&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_fr>
  <i18n_product_details_it>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Misure basate sulla taglia 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lunghezza dal cavallo alla caviglia: circa  76cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lunghezza dal cavallo alla vita:  Davanti: 18cm Dietro: 29cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Apertura gamba: 26.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Le misure possono variare in base alla taglia, al tessuto e al lavaggio&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;62% Cotone, 38% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tasca dietro: liscia&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cerniera lampo&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vita normale&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Realizzato in Europa utilizzando tecniche di finitura artigianali &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_it>
  <i18n_product_details_es>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Medidas basadas en la Talla 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tiro aproximado: 30in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tiro: Frontal: 7in Trasero: 11 1/2in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Abertura de la pierna: 10 1/2in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Las medidas pueden variar dependiendo de la talla, material y teñido&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;62% Algodón, 38% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Blosillo sin squiggle&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zip fly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cintura media&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fabricado en Europa utilizando técnicas de acabado originales y artesanas.</i18n_product_details_es>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit>Characterised by its minimal detailing, The Skinny has a comfortable rise with a slim, sexy, and fitted silhouette top to bottom. The length hits at the ankle to maintain a clean line with no stacking.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_de>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimalistische Verzierungen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;die Skinny hat eine bequeme Leibhöhe und eine durchweg schmale, sexy und eng anliegende Silhouette&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;endet kurz über dem Knöchel und garantiert einen cleanen Look mit schmaler Silhouette&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_de>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_nl>De Skinny wordt gekenmerkt door minimale details en heeft een comfortabele heuplijn met een slank, sexy en aansluitend silhouet van top tot teen. De lengte gaat mooi tot de enkel voor een pure lijn zonder kreuken.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_nl>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_fr>Orné de détails raffinés, le Skinny est confortable à la taille avec une coupe plus ajustée très sexy qui épouse à merveille l’ensemble de la silhouette. Son tombé bien ajusté jusqu’à la cheville lui confère une ligne impeccable et sans plis.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_fr>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_it>Il modello Skinny, con dettagli minimal e vita confortevole, disegna una figura sexy e sottile da capo a piedi! L’orlo arriva alla caviglia per un taglio deciso senza arricciature.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_it>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_es>Characterised by its minimal detailing, The Skinny has a comfortable rise with a slim, sexy, and fitted silhouette top to bottom. The length hits at the ankle to maintain a clean line with no stacking.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_es>
  <price>260</price>
  <price_uk>235</price_uk>
  <price_de>260</price_de>
  <price_be>260</price_be>
  <price_nl>260</price_nl>
  <price_fr>260</price_fr>
  <price_it>260</price_it>
  <price_pan_en>260</price_pan_en>
  <price_pan_es>260</price_pan_es>
  <price_pan_fr>260</price_pan_fr>
  <price_pan_de>260</price_pan_de>
  <special_price></special_price>
  <special_from_date></special_from_date>
  <special_to_date></special_to_date>
  <special_price_uk></special_price_uk>
  <special_from_date_uk></special_from_date_uk>
  <special_to_date_uk></special_to_date_uk>
  <special_price_de></special_price_de>
  <special_from_date_de></special_from_date_de>
  <special_to_date_de></special_to_date_de>
  <special_price_nl></special_price_nl>
  <special_from_date_nl></special_from_date_nl>
  <special_to_date_nl></special_to_date_nl>
  <special_price_be></special_price_be>
  <special_from_date_be></special_from_date_be>
  <special_to_date_be></special_to_date_be>
  <special_price_fr></special_price_fr>
  <special_from_date_fr></special_from_date_fr>
  <special_to_date_fr></special_to_date_fr>
  <special_price_it></special_price_it>
  <special_from_date_it></special_from_date_it>
  <special_to_date_it></special_to_date_it>
  <special_price_pan_en></special_price_pan_en>
  <special_from_date_pan_en></special_from_date_pan_en>
  <special_to_date_pan_en></special_to_date_pan_en>
  <special_price_pan_es></special_price_pan_es>
  <special_from_date_pan_es></special_from_date_pan_es>
  <special_to_date_pan_es></special_to_date_pan_es>
  <special_price_pan_fr></special_price_pan_fr>
  <special_from_date_pan_fr></special_from_date_pan_fr>
  <special_to_date_pan_fr></special_to_date_pan_fr>
  <special_price_pan_de></special_price_pan_de>
  <special_from_date_pan_de></special_from_date_pan_de>
  <special_to_date_pan_de></special_to_date_pan_de>
  <news_from_date>2012-10-28</news_from_date>
  <image_front>SWTK110EB_front.jpg</image_front>
  <image_back>SWTK110EB_back.jpg</image_back>
  <image_pocket>SWTK110EB_pocket.jpg</image_pocket>
  <image_wash>SWTK110EB_wash.jpg</image_wash>
  <small_image></small_image>
  <thumbnail></thumbnail>
  <url_key></url_key>
  <color></color>
  <bubble_new_collection></bubble_new_collection>
  <bubble_sale></bubble_sale>
  <bubble_best_seller></bubble_best_seller>
  <bubble_limited_edition></bubble_limited_edition>
  <gender>Women</gender>
  <fit_group>SKINNY</fit_group>
  <fit_code>THE SKINNY</fit_code>
  <wash_group>DARK WASH</wash_group>
  <enable_special_area>No</enable_special_area>
  <special_area_static_block_id></special_area_static_block_id>
  <delivery_return_static_block_id>product_tab_delivery_return</delivery_return_static_block_id>
  <status>Disabled</status>
  <visibility>Nowhere</visibility>
  <super_attributes>Size</super_attributes>
  <website>base</website>
  <category_ids></category_ids>
  <main_cat_seo></main_cat_seo>
  <details_care></details_care>
</configurable>
