<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<configurable>
  <sku>SWTM700RE</sku>
  <i18n_name>THE SKINNY HIGH SHINE GUMMY LIPSTICK RED</i18n_name>
  <i18n_name_de>THE SKINNY HIGH SHINE GUMMY LIPSTICK RED</i18n_name_de>
  <i18n_name_nl>THE SKINNY HIGH SHINE GUMMY LIPSTICK RED</i18n_name_nl>
  <i18n_name_fr>THE SKINNY HIGH SHINE GUMMY LIPSTICK RED</i18n_name_fr>
  <i18n_name_it>THE SKINNY HIGH SHINE GUMMY LIPSTICK RED</i18n_name_it>
  <i18n_name_es>THE SKINNY HIGH SHINE GUMMY LIPSTICK RED</i18n_name_es>
  <product_start_date>2012-09-28</product_start_date>
  <product_end_date>2018-10-02</product_end_date>
  <i18n_description>The Skinny High Shine Gummy Lipstick Red raises the bar in super-sexy women’s trousers. A very expensive brand’s The Skinny is a body-sculpting, super-stretch fit set apart by its minimal detailing, clean pockets and slim and seductive, fitted silhouette top to bottom. It has a comfortable rise while the length hits just below the ankle to maintain a clean line with no stacking. This provocative fit is the ultimate backdrop to showcase 7FAM’s High Shine Gummy, a breath-takingly sexy leather-look fabric that delivers amazing comfort and stretch thanks to the lightweight, high-performance construction. With the new season seeing red, parade your passion for fashion in this confident, sassy hue.</i18n_description>
  <i18n_description_de>Die Skinny High Shine Gummy Lipstick Red legt die Messlatte für super-sexy Damenhosen eine Stufe höher. Die Skinny von A very expensive brand hat einen figurformenden Effekt mit Super-Stretch und besticht durch das minimalistische Design der Details, klare Linien der Taschen und eine von oben bis unten schmale, verführerische und figurbetonte Silhouette. Sie hat eine bequeme Leibhöhe, die Beine enden direkt unter dem Knöchel, damit die klare Linie nicht durch Falten am Saum gebrochen wird. Die provozierende Passform ist der ultimative Schaukasten für das High Shine Gummy von 7FAM, ein umwerfendes Gewebe im Lederlook, das aufgrund seines leichten, hoch leistungsfähigen Aufbaus herausragenden Tragekomfort in Stretch-Qualität bietet. Die neue Saison sieht rot - tragen Sie Ihre Leidenschaft für Mode in diesem selbstbewusst-frechen Farbton zur Schau.</i18n_description_de>
  <i18n_description_nl>De Skinny High Shine Gummy Lipstick Red legt de lat een stukje hoger op het gebied van super-sexy damesbroeken. A very expensive brand's The Skinny is een nauwsluitend superstretch model met minimale details, sobere zakken en een verleidelijk en strak silhouet van top tot teen. Het model heeft een comfortabele heuplijn en valt tot net onder de enkel voor een simpele lijn zonder kreukels. Dit uitdagende model is de perfecte basis voor 7FAM's High Shine Gummy, een adembenemend sexy leerachtig materiaal dat enorme comfort en stretch biedt dankzij zijn lichtgewicht, hoogwaardige samenstelling. Nu het nieuwe seizoen de kleur rood omarmt, laat je met deze uitgesproken pittige kleur je passie voor mode zien.</i18n_description_nl>
  <i18n_description_fr>Le Skinny High Shine Gummy Lipstick Red est l'expression la plus sublime des pantalons femme supersexy. Le Skinny A very expensive brand sculpte votre corps grâce à son matériau super-stretch et se distingue par des finitions minimalistes, des poches nettes et une silhouette mince et sexy sur toute la longueur. Sa taille basse est très confortable, et sa longueur juste sous la cheville garantit une ligne nette et fluide. Cette coupe provocante est la dernière interprétation du High Shine Gummy 7FAM, un tissu aspect cuir d'un sexy éblouissant, qui offre un confort et une élasticité exceptionnels grâce à sa grande légèreté et à sa construction d'avant-garde. La nouvelle saison s'adonne au rouge, exprimez votre passion pour la mode avec cette couleur pleine d'assurance et d'impertinence.</i18n_description_fr>
  <i18n_description_it>Lo Skinny High Shine Gummy Lipstick Red è l'espressione più irresistibile del pantalone superfemminile. Lo Skinny di A very expensive brand scolpisce il fisico con il suo fit super-stretch e si distingue per i  dettagli  minimal, le tasche di taglio pulito e la linea slim, seducente e attillata in tutta la lunghezza. Ha una vita confortevole mentre la lunghezza, appena sotto la caviglia, regala una linea pulita ed impeccabile. Questo fit provocante è interpretato al meglio da High Shine Gummy di 7FAM, un tessuto effetto pelle assolutamente mozzafiato, che assicura stretch e comfort impareggiabili grazie alla sua leggerezza e alle caratteristiche performarti. In questa nuova stagione votata al rosso, mostrate la vostra passione per la moda, scegliendo questo colore deciso ed energetico.</i18n_description_it>
  <i18n_description_es>The Skinny High Shine Gummy Lipstick Red raises the bar in super-sexy women’s trousers. A very expensive brand’s The Skinny is a body-sculpting, super-stretch fit set apart by its minimal detailing, clean pockets and slim and seductive, fitted silhouette top to bottom. It has a comfortable rise while the length hits just below the ankle to maintain a clean line with no stacking. This provocative fit is the ultimate backdrop to showcase 7FAM’s High Shine Gummy, a breath-takingly sexy leather-look fabric that delivers amazing comfort and stretch thanks to the lightweight, high-performance construction. With the new season seeing red, parade your passion for fashion in this confident, sassy hue.</i18n_description_es>
  <i18n_short_description>THE SKINNY HIGH SHINE GUMMY LIPSTICK RED</i18n_short_description>
  <i18n_short_description_de>THE SKINNY HIGH SHINE GUMMY LIPSTICK RED</i18n_short_description_de>
  <i18n_short_description_nl>THE SKINNY HIGH SHINE GUMMY LIPSTICK RED</i18n_short_description_nl>
  <i18n_short_description_fr>THE SKINNY HIGH SHINE GUMMY LIPSTICK RED</i18n_short_description_fr>
  <i18n_short_description_it>THE SKINNY HIGH SHINE GUMMY LIPSTICK RED</i18n_short_description_it>
  <i18n_short_description_es>THE SKINNY HIGH SHINE GUMMY LIPSTICK RED</i18n_short_description_es>
  <i18n_product_details>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Approx. inseam: 30in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rise: Front: 6 3/4in Back: 11 1/4in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leg opening: 10in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Cotton, 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A very expensive brand's signature squiggle back pocket&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zip fly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Made in Europe using original and handcrafted finishing techniques&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details>
  <i18n_product_details_de>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Beinlänge ca. 76cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leibhöhe: Vorne: 17cm Hinten: 28.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fussweite: 25.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Baumwolle, 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Die Signature Squiggle Backpocket von A very expensive brand&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Reisverschlussleiste&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Made in Europe unter Verwendung von Original-und Handarbeit Veredelungstechniken&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_de>
  <i18n_product_details_nl>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Binnenbeenlengte ca. 76cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Kruisnaad: Voor: 17cm Achter: 28.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zoomwijdte: 25.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Katoen, 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A very expensive brand's signature squiggle achterzak&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ritssluiting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gemaakt in Europa met behulp van originele en ambachtelijke afwerkingstechnieken&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_nl>
  <i18n_product_details_fr>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Inseam: sur 76cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fourche: Avant: 17cm Arrière: 28.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ouverture des jambes: 25.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Coton, 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A very expensive brand's squiggle poche&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fermeture Zip&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fabriqué en Europe avec des techniques de finitions artisanales&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_fr>
  <i18n_product_details_it>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lunghezza dal cavallo alla caviglia: circa 76cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lunghezza dal cavallo alla vita: Davanti: 17cm Dietro: 28.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Apertura gamba: 25.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Cotone, 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tasca dietro: A very expensive brand's squiggle&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cerniera lampo&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Realizzato in Europa utilizzando tecniche di finitura artigianali  &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_it>
  <i18n_product_details_es>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tiro aproximado: 30in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tiro: Frontal: 6 3/4in Trasero: 11 1/4in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Abertura de la pierna: 10in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Algodón, 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zip fly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fabricado en Europa utilizando técnicas de acabado originales y artesanas.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_es>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit>Characterised by its minimal detailing, The Skinny has a comfortable rise with a slim, sexy, and fitted silhouette top to bottom. The length hits at the ankle to maintain a clean line with no stacking.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_de>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimalistische Verzierungen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;die Skinny hat eine bequeme Leibhöhe und eine durchweg schmale, sexy und eng anliegende Silhouette&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;endet kurz über dem Knöchel und garantiert einen cleanen Look mit schmaler Silhouette&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_de>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_nl>De Skinny wordt gekenmerkt door minimale details en heeft een comfortabele heuplijn met een slank, sexy en aansluitend silhouet van top tot teen. De lengte gaat mooi tot de enkel voor een pure lijn zonder kreuken.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_nl>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_fr>Orné de détails raffinés, le Skinny est confortable à la taille avec une coupe plus ajustée très sexy qui épouse à merveille l’ensemble de la silhouette. Son tombé bien ajusté jusqu’à la cheville lui confère une ligne impeccable et sans plis.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_fr>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_it>Il modello Skinny, con dettagli minimal e vita confortevole, disegna una figura sexy e sottile da capo a piedi! L’orlo arriva alla caviglia per un taglio deciso senza arricciature.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_it>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_es>Characterised by its minimal detailing, The Skinny has a comfortable rise with a slim, sexy, and fitted silhouette top to bottom. The length hits at the ankle to maintain a clean line with no stacking.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_es>
  <price>240</price>
  <price_uk>220</price_uk>
  <price_de>240</price_de>
  <price_be>240</price_be>
  <price_nl>240</price_nl>
  <price_fr>240</price_fr>
  <price_it>240</price_it>
  <price_pan_en>240</price_pan_en>
  <price_pan_es>240</price_pan_es>
  <price_pan_fr>240</price_pan_fr>
  <price_pan_de>240</price_pan_de>
  <special_price></special_price>
  <special_from_date></special_from_date>
  <special_to_date></special_to_date>
  <special_price_uk></special_price_uk>
  <special_from_date_uk></special_from_date_uk>
  <special_to_date_uk></special_to_date_uk>
  <special_price_de></special_price_de>
  <special_from_date_de></special_from_date_de>
  <special_to_date_de></special_to_date_de>
  <special_price_nl></special_price_nl>
  <special_from_date_nl></special_from_date_nl>
  <special_to_date_nl></special_to_date_nl>
  <special_price_be></special_price_be>
  <special_from_date_be></special_from_date_be>
  <special_to_date_be></special_to_date_be>
  <special_price_fr></special_price_fr>
  <special_from_date_fr></special_from_date_fr>
  <special_to_date_fr></special_to_date_fr>
  <special_price_it></special_price_it>
  <special_from_date_it></special_from_date_it>
  <special_to_date_it></special_to_date_it>
  <special_price_pan_en></special_price_pan_en>
  <special_from_date_pan_en></special_from_date_pan_en>
  <special_to_date_pan_en></special_to_date_pan_en>
  <special_price_pan_es></special_price_pan_es>
  <special_from_date_pan_es></special_from_date_pan_es>
  <special_to_date_pan_es></special_to_date_pan_es>
  <special_price_pan_fr></special_price_pan_fr>
  <special_from_date_pan_fr></special_from_date_pan_fr>
  <special_to_date_pan_fr></special_to_date_pan_fr>
  <special_price_pan_de></special_price_pan_de>
  <special_from_date_pan_de></special_from_date_pan_de>
  <special_to_date_pan_de></special_to_date_pan_de>
  <news_from_date>2012-09-28</news_from_date>
  <image_front>SWTM700RE_front.jpg</image_front>
  <image_back>SWTM700RE_back.jpg</image_back>
  <image_pocket>SWTM700RE_pocket.jpg</image_pocket>
  <image_wash>SWTM700RE_wash.jpg</image_wash>
  <small_image></small_image>
  <thumbnail></thumbnail>
  <url_key></url_key>
  <color></color>
  <bubble_new_collection></bubble_new_collection>
  <bubble_sale></bubble_sale>
  <bubble_best_seller></bubble_best_seller>
  <bubble_limited_edition></bubble_limited_edition>
  <gender>Women</gender>
  <fit_group>SKINNY</fit_group>
  <fit_code>THE SKINNY</fit_code>
  <wash_group>COLOUR</wash_group>
  <enable_special_area>No</enable_special_area>
  <special_area_static_block_id></special_area_static_block_id>
  <delivery_return_static_block_id>product_tab_delivery_return</delivery_return_static_block_id>
  <status>Disabled</status>
  <visibility>Nowhere</visibility>
  <super_attributes>size</super_attributes>
  <website>base</website>
  <category_ids></category_ids>
  <main_cat_seo></main_cat_seo>
  <details_care></details_care>
</configurable>
