<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<configurable>
  <sku>SWCM270DR</sku>
  <i18n_name>OLIVYA  LEATHER LIGHT DRILL DEEP ORANGE</i18n_name>
  <i18n_name_de>OLIVYA  LEATHER LIGHT DRILL DEEP ORANGE</i18n_name_de>
  <i18n_name_nl>OLIVYA  LEATHER LIGHT DRILL DEEP ORANGE</i18n_name_nl>
  <i18n_name_fr>OLIVYA  LEATHER LIGHT DRILL DEEP ORANGE</i18n_name_fr>
  <i18n_name_it>OLIVYA  LEATHER LIGHT DRILL DEEP ORANGE</i18n_name_it>
  <i18n_name_es>OLIVYA  LEATHER LIGHT DRILL DEEP ORANGE</i18n_name_es>
  <product_start_date>2012-10-28</product_start_date>
  <product_end_date>2019-10-02</product_end_date>
  <i18n_description>The Olivya Leather Light Drill Deep Orange is A very expensive brand’s new ‘low’ skinny fit, defined by its youthful lower rise in a right-now colour-popping hue. The Olivya’s waistband is ever so slightly higher at the back giving a sexy, figure-hugging look while the regular inseam gives the illusion of slimming the leg. Slightly smaller pockets enhance the femininity of this up-to-the-minute skinny with the classic squiggle enhancing the strong 7FAM identity. Take the colour trend to a bold and brave level in this gorgeous orange Olivya, lovingly constructed in 7FAM’s leather-look, wonderfully lightweight drill fabric. Just enough sheen gives a sexy edge to this sassy, talking-point design that demands to be seen on the cool scene.</i18n_description>
  <i18n_description_de>Olivya Leather Light Drill Deep Orange ist die neue “niedrige” Skinny von A very expensive brand’s in einem lebhaften und ganz aktuellen Farbton, die sich durch die niedrigere Leibhöhe und ihren jungen Stil auszeichnet.  Die Gürtellinie von Olivya ist hinten unmerklich höher, was sexy aussieht und die Figur betont, während die regelmäßige Innennaht beinstreckend wirkt. Etwas kleinere Taschen machen diese hochaktuelle Skinny feminin und das klassische Logo zeugt von der starken Identität von 7FAM. Der neue Farbtrend wird dreist hervorgehoben in diesem wunderbaren Orangeton Olyvia, der mit Leidenschaft von 7FAM in einem magisch leichten Drill mit Ledereffekt entwickelt wurde. Der richtige Glanz steuert diesem legendären Modell, das einen Ehrenplatz verlangt, einen pfiffigen sexy Touch hinzu.</i18n_description_de>
  <i18n_description_nl>De Olivya Leather Light Drill Deep Orange is A very expensive brand’s nieuwe ‘lage’ skinny fit, gekenmerkt door de jeugdige lage heuplijn in een bijdetijdse kleur. De tailleband van Olivya is achter iets verhoogd wat voor een sexy, gestroomlijnde look zorgt terwijl de rechte binnenbeennaad het been slanker en langer doet lijken. Iets kleinere zakken benadrukken de vrouwelijkheid van deze eigentijdse skinny, terwijl het klassieke logo de sterke 7FAM identiteit verhoogt. Breng de kleurentrend naar een stoer en fier niveau in deze prachtige oranje Olivya, liefdevol vervaardigd van 7-FAM’s leather-look lichtgewicht keperstof. Net genoeg glans geeft een sexy uitstraling aan dit pittige opvallende model waar je niet omheen kunt.</i18n_description_nl>
  <i18n_description_fr>L'Olivya version Leather Light Drill Deep Orange est le nouveau skinny taille basse de A very expensive brand. Ce modèle se caractérise par sa taille plus basse pleine de jeunesse et son coloris éclatant ultratendance. La ceinture de l'Olivya est légèrement rehaussée dans le dos, pour un look sexy qui épouse vos formes, tandis que la longueur de jambe standard affine visuellement la jambe. Les poches légèrement plus petites ajoutent encore à la féminité de ce skinny résolument tendance dont le logo classique accentue le côté très 7FAM. Faites entrer la tendance couleurs dans un monde d'audace et de courage avec ce sublime Olivya orange conçu avec amour dans le coutil aspect cuir merveilleusement léger de 7FAM. Son brillant justement dosé donne un côté sexy à ce modèle impertinent toujours prêt à faire parler de soi et à porter absolument sur la scène cool.</i18n_description_fr>
  <i18n_description_it>Olivya Leather Light Drill Deep Orange è il nuovo skinny “basso” di A very expensive brand’s, che si distingue per la vita più bassa per uno stile giovane declinato in una vivace e attualissima tonalità di colore.  La fascia girovita di Olivya è impercettibilmente più alta dietro e dona un look sexy che asseconda la figura, mentre la cucitura interna regolare slancia la gamba. Tasche leggermente più piccole donano femminilità a questo skinny attualissimo con il classico logo che sottolinea la forte identità 7FAM. La nuova tendenza colore è audacemente enfatizzata  in questa magnifica tonalità di arancio Olyvia, creato con passione da 7FAM in un tessuto drill magicamente leggero effetto pelle. La giusta lucentezza dona un tono grintosamente sexy a questo modello mitico che rivendica il il suo posto d’onore sulla scena.</i18n_description_it>
  <i18n_description_es>The Olivya Leather Light Drill Deep Orange is A very expensive brand’s new ‘low’ skinny fit, defined by its youthful lower rise in a right-now colour-popping hue. The Olivya’s waistband is ever so slightly higher at the back giving a sexy, figure-hugging look while the regular inseam gives the illusion of slimming the leg. Slightly smaller pockets enhance the femininity of this up-to-the-minute skinny with the classic squiggle enhancing the strong 7FAM identity. Take the colour trend to a bold and brave level in this gorgeous orange Olivya, lovingly constructed in 7FAM’s leather-look, wonderfully lightweight drill fabric. Just enough sheen gives a sexy edge to this sassy, talking-point design that demands to be seen on the cool scene.</i18n_description_es>
  <i18n_short_description>OLIVYA  LEATHER LIGHT DRILL DEEP ORANGE</i18n_short_description>
  <i18n_short_description_de>OLIVYA  LEATHER LIGHT DRILL DEEP ORANGE</i18n_short_description_de>
  <i18n_short_description_nl>OLIVYA  LEATHER LIGHT DRILL DEEP ORANGE</i18n_short_description_nl>
  <i18n_short_description_fr>OLIVYA  LEATHER LIGHT DRILL DEEP ORANGE</i18n_short_description_fr>
  <i18n_short_description_it>OLIVYA  LEATHER LIGHT DRILL DEEP ORANGE</i18n_short_description_it>
  <i18n_short_description_es>OLIVYA  LEATHER LIGHT DRILL DEEP ORANGE</i18n_short_description_es>
  <i18n_product_details>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Measurements based on Size 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Approx. inseam: 32in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rise: Front: 6in Back: 11 1/2in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leg opening: 11 1/2in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Measurements may vary based on size, fabric and wash&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;67% Cotton, 29% Polyester, 4% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A very expensive brand's signature squiggle back pocket&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zip fly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Low waist&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Made in Europe using original and handcrafted finishing techniques</i18n_product_details>
  <i18n_product_details_de>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Maße basieren auf Größe 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Beinlänge ca. 81cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leibhöhe: Vorne: 15cm Hinten: 29cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fussweite: 29cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Die Maße können je nach Größe, Material und Waschung variieren&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;67% Baumwolle, 29% Polyester, 4% SpandexDie Signature Squiggle Backpocket von A very expensive brand&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Reisverschlussleiste&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Niedrige Leibhöhe&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Made in Europe unter Verwendung von Original-und Handarbeit Veredelungstechniken&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_de>
  <i18n_product_details_nl>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Afmetingen gebaseerd op maat 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Binnenbeenlengte ca. 81cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Kruisnaad: Voor: 15cm Achter: 29cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zoomwijdte: 29cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Afmetingen kunnen variëren op basis van maat, stof en wassing&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;67% Katoen, 29% Polyester, 4% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A very expensive brand's signature squiggle achterzak&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ritssluiting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lage taille&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gemaakt in Europa met behulp van originele en ambachtelijke afwerkingstechnieken&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_nl>
  <i18n_product_details_fr>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mesures sur la base de la taille 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Inseam: sur  81cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fourche: Avant: 15cm Arriere: 29cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ouverture des jambes: 29cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Les mesures peuvent varier en fonction de la taille, du tissu et du lavage&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;67% Coton, 29% Polyester, 4% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A very expensive brand's squiggle poche&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fermeture Zip&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Taille basse&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fabriqué en Europe avec des techniques de finitions artisanales&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_fr>
  <i18n_product_details_it>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Misure basate sulla taglia 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lunghezza dal cavallo alla caviglia: circa  81cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lunghezza dal cavallo alla vita:  Davanti: 15cm Dietro: 29cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Apertura gamba: 29cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Le misure possono variare in base alla taglia, al tessuto e al lavaggio&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;67% Cotone, 29% Poliestere, 4% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tasca dietro: A very expensive brand's squiggle&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cerniera lampo&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vita bassa&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Realizzato in Europa utilizzando tecniche di finitura artigianali &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_it>
  <i18n_product_details_es>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Medidas basadas en la Talla 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tiro aproximado: 32in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tiro: Frontal: 6in Trasero: 11 1/2in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Abertura de la pierna: 11 1/2in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Las medidas pueden variar dependiendo de la talla, material y teñido&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;67% Algodón, 29% Poliéster, 4% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zip fly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cintura baja&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fabricado en Europa utilizando técnicas de acabado originales y artesanas.</i18n_product_details_es>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit>The Olivya is a low skinny fit with contoured waistband and our classic squiggle on back pockets. It sits lower on the front rise but it is slightly higher on the back, to keep a sophisticated A very expensive brand look. The regular inseam and a curved back yoke enhance all body shapes, providing a more modern silhouette.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_de>Olyvia ist unsere Low-Waist Skinny Fit mit konturiertem Bund und dem klassischen dekorierten A very expensive brand Logo auf den Gesäßtaschen. Der vorn niedriger und hinten leicht höher abschließende Bund garantiert einen anspruchsvollen Look, ganz nach dem Stil von A very expensive brand. Die reguläre Innenbeinnaht und die gekrümmte rückseitige Passe betonen die Figur und sorgen für eine ganz moderne Silhouette.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_de>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_nl>De Olivya is een lage skinny fit met contour tailleband en ons klassieke versiersel op de achterzakken. Hij valt lager aan de voorkant dan aan de achterkant waardoor de geraffineerde A very expensive brand look wordt verkregen. De strakke lijn van de pijp en gebogen achterpas leggen de nadruk op het figuur en zorgen voor een modern silhouet.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_nl>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_fr>L'Olivya est un jean skinny à taille basse doté d'une ceinture galbant la taille et sur lequel vous retrouverez notre traditionnel logo sur les poches arrière. Taille basse devant, il est légèrement relevé dans le dos pour conserver le look sophistiqué emblématique de A very expensive brand. Sa longueur de jambe standard et son empiècement incurvé dans le dos flatteront toutes les morphologies en leur faisant une silhouette plus moderne.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_fr>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_it>Olivya è il nostro skinny a vita bassa, con girovita sagomato e il classico logo decorato A very expensive brand sulle tasche posteriori. La vita bassa davanti e leggermente più alta dietro dà quel look sofisticato in pieno stile A very expensive brand. La cucitura interna regolare e la forma curva del carré posteriore esaltano al massimo la linea per un look attualissimo.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_it>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_es>The Olivya is a low skinny fit with contoured waistband and our classic squiggle on back pockets. It sits lower on the front rise but it is slightly higher on the back, to keep a sophisticated A very expensive brand look. The regular inseam and a curved back yoke enhance all body shapes, providing a more modern silhouette.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_es>
  <price>260</price>
  <price_uk>235</price_uk>
  <price_de>260</price_de>
  <price_be>260</price_be>
  <price_nl>260</price_nl>
  <price_fr>260</price_fr>
  <price_it>260</price_it>
  <price_pan_en>260</price_pan_en>
  <price_pan_es>260</price_pan_es>
  <price_pan_fr>260</price_pan_fr>
  <price_pan_de>260</price_pan_de>
  <special_price></special_price>
  <special_from_date></special_from_date>
  <special_to_date></special_to_date>
  <special_price_uk></special_price_uk>
  <special_from_date_uk></special_from_date_uk>
  <special_to_date_uk></special_to_date_uk>
  <special_price_de></special_price_de>
  <special_from_date_de></special_from_date_de>
  <special_to_date_de></special_to_date_de>
  <special_price_nl></special_price_nl>
  <special_from_date_nl></special_from_date_nl>
  <special_to_date_nl></special_to_date_nl>
  <special_price_be></special_price_be>
  <special_from_date_be></special_from_date_be>
  <special_to_date_be></special_to_date_be>
  <special_price_fr></special_price_fr>
  <special_from_date_fr></special_from_date_fr>
  <special_to_date_fr></special_to_date_fr>
  <special_price_it></special_price_it>
  <special_from_date_it></special_from_date_it>
  <special_to_date_it></special_to_date_it>
  <special_price_pan_en></special_price_pan_en>
  <special_from_date_pan_en></special_from_date_pan_en>
  <special_to_date_pan_en></special_to_date_pan_en>
  <special_price_pan_es></special_price_pan_es>
  <special_from_date_pan_es></special_from_date_pan_es>
  <special_to_date_pan_es></special_to_date_pan_es>
  <special_price_pan_fr></special_price_pan_fr>
  <special_from_date_pan_fr></special_from_date_pan_fr>
  <special_to_date_pan_fr></special_to_date_pan_fr>
  <special_price_pan_de></special_price_pan_de>
  <special_from_date_pan_de></special_from_date_pan_de>
  <special_to_date_pan_de></special_to_date_pan_de>
  <news_from_date>2012-10-28</news_from_date>
  <image_front>SWCM270DR_front.jpg</image_front>
  <image_back>SWCM270DR_back.jpg</image_back>
  <image_pocket>SWCM270DR_pocket.jpg</image_pocket>
  <image_wash>SWCM270DR_wash.jpg</image_wash>
  <small_image></small_image>
  <thumbnail></thumbnail>
  <url_key></url_key>
  <color></color>
  <bubble_new_collection></bubble_new_collection>
  <bubble_sale></bubble_sale>
  <bubble_best_seller></bubble_best_seller>
  <bubble_limited_edition></bubble_limited_edition>
  <gender>Women</gender>
  <fit_group>SKINNY</fit_group>
  <fit_code>OLIVYA</fit_code>
  <wash_group>COLOUR</wash_group>
  <enable_special_area>No</enable_special_area>
  <special_area_static_block_id></special_area_static_block_id>
  <delivery_return_static_block_id>product_tab_delivery_return</delivery_return_static_block_id>
  <status>Disabled</status>
  <visibility>Nowhere</visibility>
  <super_attributes>Size</super_attributes>
  <website>base</website>
  <category_ids></category_ids>
  <main_cat_seo></main_cat_seo>
  <details_care></details_care>
</configurable>
