<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<configurable>
  <sku>SWTM700SI</sku>
  <i18n_name>THE SKINNY ARTISAN TILE LASER</i18n_name>
  <i18n_name_de>THE SKINNY ARTISAN TILE LASER</i18n_name_de>
  <i18n_name_nl>THE SKINNY ARTISAN TILE LASER</i18n_name_nl>
  <i18n_name_fr>THE SKINNY ARTISAN TILE LASER</i18n_name_fr>
  <i18n_name_it>THE SKINNY ARTISAN TILE LASER</i18n_name_it>
  <i18n_name_es>THE SKINNY ARTISAN TILE LASER</i18n_name_es>
  <product_start_date>2012-09-28</product_start_date>
  <product_end_date>2018-10-02</product_end_date>
  <i18n_description>The Skinny Artisan Tile Laser Silver is a mesmerising women’s skinny, taking the trends for geometric prints and space-aged metallics to a new realm of edgy beauty.  Lo Skinny di A very expensive brand  is a body-sculpting, super-stretch fit set apart by its minimal detailing, clean pockets and slim and seductive, fitted silhouette top to bottom. The Skinny has a comfortable rise while the length hits just below the ankle to maintain a clean line with no stacking. This seductive fit blends beautifully with the cutting-edge sheen attained through 7FAM’s directional laser treatment. Team this high-fashion women’s trouser with suitably extravagant heels and a sexy silk shirt for a daring, directional and achingly glamorous, going-out ensemble.</i18n_description>
  <i18n_description_de>Die Skinny Artisan Tile Laser Silver hypnotisiert und bringt den Trend für geometrische Prints und spacige Metalliceffekte in neue Gefielde trendiger Schönheit. Die Skinny von A very expensive brand hat einen figurformenden Effekt mit Super-Stretch und besticht durch das minimalistische Design der Details, klare Linien der Taschen und eine von oben bis unten schmale, verführerische und figurbetonte Silhouette. Die Skinny hat eine bequeme Leibhöhe, die Beine enden direkt unter dem Knöchel, damit die klare Linie nicht durch Falten am Saum gebrochen wird. Ihr verführerischer Schnitt passt wunderbar zum topaktuellen Schimmer, den die Richtlaser-Verarbeitung von 7FAM herbeizaubert. Tragen Sie diese modische Damenhose mit passend extravaganten Heels und einem sexy Seidenshirt - ein mutiges, aussagestarkes und schmerzlich schönes Ausgehensemble.</i18n_description_de>
  <i18n_description_nl>De Skinny Artisan Tile Laser Silver is een betoverende skinny voor vrouwen, die geometrische prints en space-age metallic naar een nieuwe dimensie van schoonheid voert. A very expensive brand's The Skinny is een nauwsluitend superstretch model met minimale details, sobere zakken en een verleidelijk en strak silhouet van top tot teen. De Skinny heeft een comfortabele heuplijn en valt tot net onder de enkel voor een simpele lijn zonder kreukels. Dit uitdagende model schittert in combinatie met de ultramoderne glans, verkregen door 7FAM's speciale laserbehandeling. Draag deze modieuze vrouwenbroek met extravagant hoge hakken en een sexy zijden bloes voor een toonaangevende en waanzinnig mondaine outfit voor een avondje uit.</i18n_description_nl>
  <i18n_description_fr>Le Skinny Artisan Tile Laser Silver est un skinny femme fascinant qui reprend la tendance des imprimés géométriques et des métallisés de l'ère spatiale pour créer une esthétique contemporaine. Le Skinny A very expensive brand sculpte votre corps grâce à son matériau super-stretch et se distingue par des finitions minimalistes, des poches nettes et une silhouette mince et sexy sur toute la longueur. Sa taille basse est très confortable, et sa longueur juste sous la cheville garantit une ligne nette et fluide. Ce modèle séduisant s'adapte parfaitement au brillant obtenu grâce au traitement laser directionnel 7FAM. Associez ce pantalon femme haute  couture avec des talons extravagants et un haut en soie sexy pour une tenue audacieuse, aboutie et résolument glamour.</i18n_description_fr>
  <i18n_description_it>Lo Skinny Artisan Tile Laser Silver è uno skinny da donna assolutamente ammaliante, che trasporta il gusto per le stampe geometriche e i riflessi metallici dell'era spaziale verso nuovi orizzonti di una bellezza contemporanea. Lo Skinny di A very expensive brandscolpisce il fisico con il suo fit super-stretch e si distingue per i dettagli  minimal, le tasche di taglio pulito e la linea slim, seducente e attillata in tutta la lunghezza. Ha vita confortevole mentre la lunghezza, appena sotto la caviglia, regala una linea essenziale ed impeccabile. Questo fit seducente armonizza perfettamente con  la lucentezza ottenuta attraverso l'innovativo trattamento laser di 7FAM. Infilate un paio di scarpe con tacchi molto particolari sotto questi pantaloni da alta moda e una camicia in seta per una mise da sera audace, di gran tendenza e assolutamente glam.</i18n_description_it>
  <i18n_description_es>The Skinny Artisan Tile Laser Silver is a mesmerising women’s skinny, taking the trends for geometric prints and space-aged metallics to a new realm of edgy beauty.  Lo Skinny di A very expensive brand  is a body-sculpting, super-stretch fit set apart by its minimal detailing, clean pockets and slim and seductive, fitted silhouette top to bottom. The Skinny has a comfortable rise while the length hits just below the ankle to maintain a clean line with no stacking. This seductive fit blends beautifully with the cutting-edge sheen attained through 7FAM’s directional laser treatment. Team this high-fashion women’s trouser with suitably extravagant heels and a sexy silk shirt for a daring, directional and achingly glamorous, going-out ensemble.</i18n_description_es>
  <i18n_short_description>THE SKINNY ARTISAN TILE LASER</i18n_short_description>
  <i18n_short_description_de>THE SKINNY ARTISAN TILE LASER</i18n_short_description_de>
  <i18n_short_description_nl>THE SKINNY ARTISAN TILE LASER</i18n_short_description_nl>
  <i18n_short_description_fr>THE SKINNY ARTISAN TILE LASER</i18n_short_description_fr>
  <i18n_short_description_it>THE SKINNY ARTISAN TILE LASER</i18n_short_description_it>
  <i18n_short_description_es>THE SKINNY ARTISAN TILE LASER</i18n_short_description_es>
  <i18n_product_details>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Approx. inseam: 30in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rise: Front: 6 3/4in Back: 11 1/4in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leg opening: 10in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Cotton, 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Clean pocket&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zip fly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Made in Europe using original and handcrafted finishing techniques&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details>
  <i18n_product_details_de>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Beinlänge ca. 76cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leibhöhe: Vorne: 17cm Hinten: 28.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fussweite: 25.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Baumwolle, 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Clean Pocket&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Reisverschlussleiste&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Made in Europe unter Verwendung von Original-und Handarbeit Veredelungstechniken&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_de>
  <i18n_product_details_nl>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Binnenbeenlengte ca. 76cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Kruisnaad: Voor: 17cm Achter: 28.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zoomwijdte: 25.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Katoen, 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Achterzak zonder squiggle&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ritssluiting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gemaakt in Europa met behulp van originele en ambachtelijke afwerkingstechnieken&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_nl>
  <i18n_product_details_fr>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Inseam: sur 76cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fourche: Avant: 17cm Arrière: 28.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ouverture des jambes: 25.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Coton, 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Clean poche&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fermeture Zip&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fabriqué en Europe avec des techniques de finitions artisanales&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_fr>
  <i18n_product_details_it>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lunghezza dal cavallo alla caviglia: circa 76cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lunghezza dal cavallo alla vita: Davanti: 17cm Dietro: 28.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Apertura gamba: 25.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Cotone, 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tasca dietro: liscia&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cerniera lampo&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Realizzato in Europa utilizzando tecniche di finitura artigianali  &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_it>
  <i18n_product_details_es>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tiro aproximado: 30in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tiro: Frontal: 6 3/4in Trasero: 11 1/4in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Abertura de la pierna: 10in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Algodón, 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Blosillo sin squiggle&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zip fly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fabricado en Europa utilizando técnicas de acabado originales y artesanas.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_es>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit>Characterised by its minimal detailing, The Skinny has a comfortable rise with a slim, sexy, and fitted silhouette top to bottom. The length hits at the ankle to maintain a clean line with no stacking.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_de>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimalistische Verzierungen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;die Skinny hat eine bequeme Leibhöhe und eine durchweg schmale, sexy und eng anliegende Silhouette&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;endet kurz über dem Knöchel und garantiert einen cleanen Look mit schmaler Silhouette&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_de>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_nl>De Skinny wordt gekenmerkt door minimale details en heeft een comfortabele heuplijn met een slank, sexy en aansluitend silhouet van top tot teen. De lengte gaat mooi tot de enkel voor een pure lijn zonder kreuken.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_nl>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_fr>Orné de détails raffinés, le Skinny est confortable à la taille avec une coupe plus ajustée très sexy qui épouse à merveille l’ensemble de la silhouette. Son tombé bien ajusté jusqu’à la cheville lui confère une ligne impeccable et sans plis.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_fr>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_it>Per creare Roxanne Skinny, abbiamo abbinato il nostro classico slim Roxanne a un denim super sexy e ultra stretch. Questo modello, con vita normale e gamba stretta che arriva appena sotto la caviglia, è l’ideale per un look all’ultimo grido. Roxanne Skinn</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_it>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_es>Characterised by its minimal detailing, The Skinny has a comfortable rise with a slim, sexy, and fitted silhouette top to bottom. The length hits at the ankle to maintain a clean line with no stacking.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_es>
  <price>260</price>
  <price_uk>235</price_uk>
  <price_de>260</price_de>
  <price_be>260</price_be>
  <price_nl>260</price_nl>
  <price_fr>260</price_fr>
  <price_it>260</price_it>
  <price_pan_en>260</price_pan_en>
  <price_pan_es>260</price_pan_es>
  <price_pan_fr>260</price_pan_fr>
  <price_pan_de>260</price_pan_de>
  <special_price></special_price>
  <special_from_date></special_from_date>
  <special_to_date></special_to_date>
  <special_price_uk></special_price_uk>
  <special_from_date_uk></special_from_date_uk>
  <special_to_date_uk></special_to_date_uk>
  <special_price_de></special_price_de>
  <special_from_date_de></special_from_date_de>
  <special_to_date_de></special_to_date_de>
  <special_price_nl></special_price_nl>
  <special_from_date_nl></special_from_date_nl>
  <special_to_date_nl></special_to_date_nl>
  <special_price_be></special_price_be>
  <special_from_date_be></special_from_date_be>
  <special_to_date_be></special_to_date_be>
  <special_price_fr></special_price_fr>
  <special_from_date_fr></special_from_date_fr>
  <special_to_date_fr></special_to_date_fr>
  <special_price_it></special_price_it>
  <special_from_date_it></special_from_date_it>
  <special_to_date_it></special_to_date_it>
  <special_price_pan_en></special_price_pan_en>
  <special_from_date_pan_en></special_from_date_pan_en>
  <special_to_date_pan_en></special_to_date_pan_en>
  <special_price_pan_es></special_price_pan_es>
  <special_from_date_pan_es></special_from_date_pan_es>
  <special_to_date_pan_es></special_to_date_pan_es>
  <special_price_pan_fr></special_price_pan_fr>
  <special_from_date_pan_fr></special_from_date_pan_fr>
  <special_to_date_pan_fr></special_to_date_pan_fr>
  <special_price_pan_de></special_price_pan_de>
  <special_from_date_pan_de></special_from_date_pan_de>
  <special_to_date_pan_de></special_to_date_pan_de>
  <news_from_date>2012-09-28</news_from_date>
  <image_front>SWTM700SI_front.jpg</image_front>
  <image_back>SWTM700SI_back.jpg</image_back>
  <image_pocket>SWTM700SI_pocket.jpg</image_pocket>
  <image_wash>SWTM700SI_wash.jpg</image_wash>
  <small_image></small_image>
  <thumbnail></thumbnail>
  <url_key></url_key>
  <color></color>
  <bubble_new_collection></bubble_new_collection>
  <bubble_sale></bubble_sale>
  <bubble_best_seller></bubble_best_seller>
  <bubble_limited_edition></bubble_limited_edition>
  <gender>Women</gender>
  <fit_group>SKINNY</fit_group>
  <fit_code>THE SKINNY</fit_code>
  <wash_group>COLOUR</wash_group>
  <enable_special_area>No</enable_special_area>
  <special_area_static_block_id></special_area_static_block_id>
  <delivery_return_static_block_id>product_tab_delivery_return</delivery_return_static_block_id>
  <status>Disabled</status>
  <visibility>Nowhere</visibility>
  <super_attributes>size</super_attributes>
  <website>base</website>
  <category_ids></category_ids>
  <main_cat_seo></main_cat_seo>
  <details_care></details_care>
</configurable>
