<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<configurable>
  <sku>SWA7790LB</sku>
  <i18n_name>"A" POCKET WITH GOLD STUDS LONG BEACH WAVE</i18n_name>
  <i18n_name_de>"A" POCKET WITH GOLD STUDS LONG BEACH WAVE</i18n_name_de>
  <i18n_name_nl>"A" POCKET WITH GOLD STUDS LONG BEACH WAVE</i18n_name_nl>
  <i18n_name_fr>"A" POCKET WITH GOLD STUDS LONG BEACH WAVE</i18n_name_fr>
  <i18n_name_it>"A" POCKET WITH GOLD STUDS LONG BEACH WAVE</i18n_name_it>
  <i18n_name_es>"A" POCKET WITH GOLD STUDS LONG BEACH WAVE</i18n_name_es>
  <product_start_date>2012-10-28</product_start_date>
  <product_end_date>2019-10-02</product_end_date>
  <i18n_description>The A Pocket with Gold Studs Long Beach Wave is a second-glance women’s jean to epitomise new vintage glamour. A very expensive brand’s ‘A’ Pocket fit sits comfortably on the hips and features a contoured waistband that hugs you all around. It fits slim through the thigh and extends into a wide boot leg. The stand-out ‘A’ Pocket design on the back pocket completes the look-at-me legs. Long Beach Wave is a gorgeous dark blue stretch denim that has been subtly worn in and faded, making it a cornerstone piece to put your own stamp on the glamour vintage aesthetic.</i18n_description>
  <i18n_description_de>A Pocket with Gold Studs Long Beach Wave ist eine Damenjeans, die Blicke anzieht und dem Vintage-Look neuen Charme verleiht. Der ‘A’ Pocket Fit von 7FAM ist um die Hüfte bequem und hat einen konturierten Bund, der sich den Körperformen perfekt anpasst.  An den Oberschenkeln schmal und nach unten weit ausgestellt. Das außergewöhnliche Design ‘A’ Pocket  auf dem Backpocket macht die Beine definitiv zum Blickfang. Long Beach Wave ist ein wunderbar dunkelblauer Stretch-Denim mit gut studierten Abriebstellen und Abfärbungen: Eine unverzichtbare Jeans, wenn Sie sich für Ihren Vintage-Look einen ganz persönlichen Charme wünschen.</i18n_description_de>
  <i18n_description_nl>De A Pocket with Gold Studs Long Beach Wave is een opvallende vrouwenjeans die nieuwe vintage glamour uitstraalt. De ‘A' Pocket van A very expensive brand zit comfortabel bij de heupen en heeft een aansluitende tailleband die je lichaam omhult. Hij sluit goed aan om het dijbeen en loopt in een wijde bootleg uit. Het opvallende ‘A’ Pocket design op de achterzak voltooit de ‘look-at-me’ beenlijn. Long Beach Wave is een prachtig donkerblauw stretchdenim dat subtiel is afgedragen en gebleekt, waardoor het een basic wordt waarmee je je eigen stempel op glamour vintage drukt.</i18n_description_nl>
  <i18n_description_fr>Le jean A Pocket version Long Beach Wave avec clous dorés est un jean femme qui incarne l'essence-même du nouveau glamour vintage. Un jean qui attirera les regards !  La coupe A Pocket de A very expensive brand repose confortablement sur les hanches et comporte une ceinture galbant la taille qui épouse les contours de votre corps. Slim au niveau des cuisses, il s'élargit ensuite pour former un bas de jambe largement évasé. Le design A Pocket distinctif sur les poches arrière complète à merveille des jambes qui accrocheront les regards. Le lavage Long Beach Wave est un superbe denim stretch bleu foncé subtilement usé et délavé qui fait de ce jean une pièce incontournable pour marquer de votre empreinte l'esthétique glamour vintage.</i18n_description_fr>
  <i18n_description_it>A Pocket with Gold Studs Long Beach Wave è un jeans da donna che richiama lo sguardo imprimendo nuovo fascino al look vintage. Il fit ‘A’ Pocket di 7FAM ha una seduta confortevole e una fascia girovita sagomata che asseconda perfettamente le forme.  Veste slim sulla coscia e scende svasato. Lo straordinario design ‘A’ Pocket  sulla tasca posteriore completa l’effetto irresistibile sulla gamba. Long Beach Wave è un magnifico denim blu scuro in stretch con abrasioni e scoloriture ben studiate: un pezzo irrinunciabile per imprimere un fascino tutto personale al look vintage.</i18n_description_it>
  <i18n_description_es>The A Pocket with Gold Studs Long Beach Wave is a second-glance women’s jean to epitomise new vintage glamour. A very expensive brand’s ‘A’ Pocket fit sits comfortably on the hips and features a contoured waistband that hugs you all around. It fits slim through the thigh and extends into a wide boot leg. The stand-out ‘A’ Pocket design on the back pocket completes the look-at-me legs. Long Beach Wave is a gorgeous dark blue stretch denim that has been subtly worn in and faded, making it a cornerstone piece to put your own stamp on the glamour vintage aesthetic.</i18n_description_es>
  <i18n_short_description>"A" POCKET WITH GOLD STUDS LONG BEACH WAVE</i18n_short_description>
  <i18n_short_description_de>"A" POCKET WITH GOLD STUDS LONG BEACH WAVE</i18n_short_description_de>
  <i18n_short_description_nl>"A" POCKET WITH GOLD STUDS LONG BEACH WAVE</i18n_short_description_nl>
  <i18n_short_description_fr>"A" POCKET WITH GOLD STUDS LONG BEACH WAVE</i18n_short_description_fr>
  <i18n_short_description_it>"A" POCKET WITH GOLD STUDS LONG BEACH WAVE</i18n_short_description_it>
  <i18n_short_description_es>"A" POCKET WITH GOLD STUDS LONG BEACH WAVE</i18n_short_description_es>
  <i18n_product_details>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Approx. inseam: 34 1/2in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rise: Front: 6 1/4in Back: 11 1/4in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leg opening: 19 1/2in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Measurements may vary based on size, fabric and wash&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Cotton, 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A very expensive brand's signature squiggle back pocket&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zip fly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Made in Europe using original and handcrafted finishing techniques</i18n_product_details>
  <i18n_product_details_de>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Maße basieren auf Größe 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Beinlänge ca. 88cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leibhöhe: Vorne: 16cm Hinten: 28.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fussweite: 49.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Die Maße können je nach Größe, Material und Waschung variieren&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Baumwolle, 2% SpandexDie Signature Squiggle Backpocket von A very expensive brand&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Reisverschlussleiste&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Made in Europe unter Verwendung von Original-und Handarbeit Veredelungstechniken&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_de>
  <i18n_product_details_nl>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Afmetingen gebaseerd op maat 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Binnenbeenlengte ca. 88cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Kruisnaad: Voor: 16cm Achter: 28.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zoomwijdte: 49.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Afmetingen kunnen variëren op basis van maat, stof en wassing&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Katoen, 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A very expensive brand's signature squiggle achterzak&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ritssluiting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gemaakt in Europa met behulp van originele en ambachtelijke afwerkingstechnieken&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_nl>
  <i18n_product_details_fr>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mesures sur la base de la taille 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Inseam: sur  88cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fourche: Avant: 16cm Arriere: 28.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ouverture des jambes: 49.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Les mesures peuvent varier en fonction de la taille, du tissu et du lavage&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Coton, 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A very expensive brand's squiggle poche&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fermeture Zip&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fabriqué en Europe avec des techniques de finitions artisanales&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_fr>
  <i18n_product_details_it>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Misure basate sulla taglia 28&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lunghezza dal cavallo alla caviglia: circa  88cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lunghezza dal cavallo alla vita:  Davanti: 16cm Dietro: 28.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Apertura gamba: 49.5cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Le misure possono variare in base alla taglia, al tessuto e al lavaggio&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Cotone, 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tasca dietro: A very expensive brand's squiggle&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cerniera lampo&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Realizzato in Europa utilizzando tecniche di finitura artigianali &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_it>
  <i18n_product_details_es>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tiro aproximado: 34 1/2in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tiro: Frontal: 6 1/4in Trasero: 11 1/4in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Abertura de la pierna: 19 1/2in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Las medidas pueden variar dependiendo de la talla, material y teñido&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Algodón, 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zip fly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fabricado en Europa utilizando técnicas de acabado originales y artesanas.</i18n_product_details_es>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit>The "A" Pocket sits comfortably on the hips and features a contoured waistband that hugs you all around. It's slim through the thigh and extends into a wide boot leg, and features the signature "A" Pocket design on the back pockets. This fit is offered in a variety of novelty "A" Pocket designs.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_de>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Die "A" Pocket sitzt bequem auf den Hüften und hat einen konturierten, figurumschmeichelnden Bund&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;der an den Oberschenkeln schmale Schnitt endet in einem weiten Bootleg&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;die Backpockets ziert das „A“-Design von 7FAM Passform erhältlich mit verschiedenen neuen „A“-Pocket-Designs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_de>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_nl>De "A" Pocket zit comfortabel bij de heupen en heeft een bredere broeksband om je middel volledig te stroomlijnen. De broek oogt smal dankzij de strakke pijp die uitloopt in een wijde bootleg en heeft een opvallend "A"-design op de achterzakken. Dit model is verkrijgbaar in een hele reeks vernieuwende "A" Pocket-designs.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_nl>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_fr>Le "A" Pocket de A very expensive brand repose confortablement sur les hanches avec sa ceinture qui galbe joliment la silhouette. Slim au niveau des cuisses, il s’évase pour finir en bootcut, avec en prime sur ses poches arrière les toutes dernières déclinaisons du fameux logo « A » brodé.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_fr>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_it>Il modello “A” Pocket è confortevole attorno ai fianchi e presenta una cintura particolarmente avvolgente per abbracciare la vita. Ha una vestibilità aderente attorno alle cosce, per poi allargarsi come un bootcut. Sulle tasche posteriori spicca la lettera “A”. Disponibile con nuovi e numerosi dettagli.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_it>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_es>The "A" Pocket sits comfortably on the hips and features a contoured waistband that hugs you all around. It's slim through the thigh and extends into a wide boot leg, and features the signature "A" Pocket design on the back pockets. This fit is offered in a variety of novelty "A" Pocket designs.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_es>
  <price>280</price>
  <price_uk>255</price_uk>
  <price_de>280</price_de>
  <price_be>280</price_be>
  <price_nl>280</price_nl>
  <price_fr>280</price_fr>
  <price_it>280</price_it>
  <price_pan_en>280</price_pan_en>
  <price_pan_es>280</price_pan_es>
  <price_pan_fr>280</price_pan_fr>
  <price_pan_de>280</price_pan_de>
  <special_price></special_price>
  <special_from_date></special_from_date>
  <special_to_date></special_to_date>
  <special_price_uk></special_price_uk>
  <special_from_date_uk></special_from_date_uk>
  <special_to_date_uk></special_to_date_uk>
  <special_price_de></special_price_de>
  <special_from_date_de></special_from_date_de>
  <special_to_date_de></special_to_date_de>
  <special_price_nl></special_price_nl>
  <special_from_date_nl></special_from_date_nl>
  <special_to_date_nl></special_to_date_nl>
  <special_price_be></special_price_be>
  <special_from_date_be></special_from_date_be>
  <special_to_date_be></special_to_date_be>
  <special_price_fr></special_price_fr>
  <special_from_date_fr></special_from_date_fr>
  <special_to_date_fr></special_to_date_fr>
  <special_price_it></special_price_it>
  <special_from_date_it></special_from_date_it>
  <special_to_date_it></special_to_date_it>
  <special_price_pan_en></special_price_pan_en>
  <special_from_date_pan_en></special_from_date_pan_en>
  <special_to_date_pan_en></special_to_date_pan_en>
  <special_price_pan_es></special_price_pan_es>
  <special_from_date_pan_es></special_from_date_pan_es>
  <special_to_date_pan_es></special_to_date_pan_es>
  <special_price_pan_fr></special_price_pan_fr>
  <special_from_date_pan_fr></special_from_date_pan_fr>
  <special_to_date_pan_fr></special_to_date_pan_fr>
  <special_price_pan_de></special_price_pan_de>
  <special_from_date_pan_de></special_from_date_pan_de>
  <special_to_date_pan_de></special_to_date_pan_de>
  <news_from_date>2012-10-28</news_from_date>
  <image_front>SWA7790LB_front.jpg</image_front>
  <image_back>SWA7790LB_back.jpg</image_back>
  <image_pocket>SWA7790LB_pocket.jpg</image_pocket>
  <image_wash>SWA7790LB_wash.jpg</image_wash>
  <small_image></small_image>
  <thumbnail></thumbnail>
  <url_key></url_key>
  <color></color>
  <bubble_new_collection></bubble_new_collection>
  <bubble_sale></bubble_sale>
  <bubble_best_seller></bubble_best_seller>
  <bubble_limited_edition></bubble_limited_edition>
  <gender>Women</gender>
  <fit_group>BOOTCUT</fit_group>
  <fit_code>"A" POCKET</fit_code>
  <wash_group>DARK WASH</wash_group>
  <enable_special_area>No</enable_special_area>
  <special_area_static_block_id></special_area_static_block_id>
  <delivery_return_static_block_id>product_tab_delivery_return</delivery_return_static_block_id>
  <status>Disabled</status>
  <visibility>Nowhere</visibility>
  <super_attributes>Size</super_attributes>
  <website>base</website>
  <category_ids></category_ids>
  <main_cat_seo></main_cat_seo>
  <details_care></details_care>
</configurable>
