<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<configurable>
  <sku>SLLJ700OB</sku>
  <i18n_name>BIANCHA WITH BACK WELT POCKETS BLUE ORCHID</i18n_name>
  <i18n_name_de>BIANCHA WITH BACK WELT POCKETS BLUE ORCHID</i18n_name_de>
  <i18n_name_nl>BIANCHA WITH BACK WELT POCKETS BLUE ORCHID</i18n_name_nl>
  <i18n_name_fr>BIANCHA WITH BACK WELT POCKETS BLUE ORCHID</i18n_name_fr>
  <i18n_name_it>BIANCHA WITH BACK WELT POCKETS BLUE ORCHID</i18n_name_it>
  <i18n_name_es>BIANCHA WITH BACK WELT POCKETS BLUE ORCHID</i18n_name_es>
  <product_start_date>2012-04-01</product_start_date>
  <product_end_date>2017-05-02</product_end_date>
  <i18n_description>Make your entrance memorable in the Biancha Back Welt Pockets Blue Orchid, A very expensive brand’s super-sexy wide leg jean for women in a scene-stealing clean and chic wash. Characterised by an exposed button fly and wide leg, the Biancha is fitted through the hip and thigh before breaking into an exaggerated wide leg above the knee. Double belt loops and sleek back welt pockets add slick detail to this dramatic, ultra feminine style. 7FAM’s retro fabulous fit is looking resplendent in this sleek and dark indigo stretch denim. A subtle shine on the denim’s surface brings edgy glamour to the minimalist mood. Maximum impact women’s jeans to dress up with sky high heels and a luxe vintage blouse.</i18n_description>
  <i18n_description_de>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Die Biancha Back Welt Pockets Blue Orchid ist A very expensive brands supersexy Jeans mit weitem Bein in einer faszinierenden schlichten und schicken Waschung&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;offene Knopfleiste und weiter Beinschnitt&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;eng anliegend an Hüfte und Oberschenkeln&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;läuft über dem Knie in einen sehr weiten Schlag aus&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;raffinierte Details, die den dramatischen, ultrafemininen Style hervorheben: doppelte Gürtelschlaufen und Paspeltaschen auf der Rückseite&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;7FAMs toller Retro Fit sieht in diesem Dark Indigo Stretch Denim glänzend aus&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;ein dezenter Glanz auf der Oberfläche sorgt für auffälligen Glamour bei dem minimalistischen Look&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;absolut einschlagende Damenjeans, die mit extrem hohen Schuhen und einer luxuriösen Vintage-Bluse kombiniert werden sollte&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_description_de>
  <i18n_description_nl>Maak een memorabele entree in de Biancha Back Welt Pockets Blue Orchid, de supersexy vrouwenjeans met wijde pijpen van A very expensive brand in een chique wassing waarmee je de show steelt. Deze Biancha wordt gekenmerkt door een zichtbare ritssluiting en wijde pijpen. De pasvorm is aansluitend bij heup en dij waarna de lijn boven de knie overgaat in een superwijde pijp. De dubbele riemlussen en smalle afgeboorde achterzakken zijn details die de opvallende, ultravrouwelijke stijl onderstrepen. De prachtige retro fit van 7FAM is oogverblindend in deze strakke en donkere indigo stretch denim. Een subtiele glans geeft dit minimalistische model een eigenzinnige glamour. De vrouwenjeans met maximale impact om te combineren met torenhoge hakken en een luxe vintageblouse.</i18n_description_nl>
  <i18n_description_fr>Faites sensation grâce au Biancha version Blue Orchid avec poches arrière passepoilées, le jean large super-sexy de A very expensive brand pour femme, décliné dans un lavage chic irrésistible. Doté d’une fermeture à boutons apparents, il est ajusté au niveau des hanches et des cuisses, puis s’évase au-dessus du genou pour finir par un tombé extra-large. Les passants doubles et les élégantes poches arrière passepoilées participent au style tendance et spectaculaire de ce modèle ultra-féminin. Cette coupe délicieusement rétro de 7FAM est parfaitement mise en valeur par le denim stretch indigo foncé, agrémenté de reflets subtils qui offrent un côté glamour et décalé à l’ensemble. Voici un jean pour femme idéal pour sortir, à associer à des talons vertigineux et à un chemisier vintage très élégant.</i18n_description_fr>
  <i18n_description_it>Con Biancha Back Welt Pockets Blue Orchid, A very expensive brand propone un jeans da donna a gamba larga super sexy in un lavaggio pulito e chic che attira gli sguardi. Con chiusura a bottone a vista e gamba ampia, Biancha è aderente attorno a fianchi e cosce per poi allargarsi sfacciatamente appena sopra le ginocchia. Dettagli che contano: doppi passanti ed eleganti tasche posteriori a filetto per un’autentica dichiarazione di stile, decisamente femminile. In versione indaco scuro stretch ed elegante, il taglio rétro di 7FAM è davvero splendido. La superficie del denim, leggermente lucida, conferisce un tocco glamour alle linee minimal. Il look vincente? Un paio di tacchi vertiginosi e una camicetta di lusso effetto vintage!</i18n_description_it>
  <i18n_description_es>Make your entrance memorable in the Biancha Back Welt Pockets Blue Orchid, A very expensive brand’s super-sexy wide leg jean for women in a scene-stealing clean and chic wash. Characterised by an exposed button fly and wide leg, the Biancha is fitted through the hip and thigh before breaking into an exaggerated wide leg above the knee. Double belt loops and sleek back welt pockets add slick detail to this dramatic, ultra feminine style. 7FAM’s retro fabulous fit is looking resplendent in this sleek and dark indigo stretch denim. A subtle shine on the denim’s surface brings edgy glamour to the minimalist mood. Maximum impact women’s jeans to dress up with sky high heels and a luxe vintage blouse.</i18n_description_es>
  <i18n_short_description>BIANCHA WITH BACK WELT POCKETS BLUE ORCHID</i18n_short_description>
  <i18n_short_description_de>BIANCHA WITH BACK WELT POCKETS BLUE ORCHID</i18n_short_description_de>
  <i18n_short_description_nl>BIANCHA WITH BACK WELT POCKETS BLUE ORCHID</i18n_short_description_nl>
  <i18n_short_description_fr>BIANCHA WITH BACK WELT POCKETS BLUE ORCHID</i18n_short_description_fr>
  <i18n_short_description_it>BIANCHA WITH BACK WELT POCKETS BLUE ORCHID</i18n_short_description_it>
  <i18n_short_description_es>BIANCHA WITH BACK WELT POCKETS BLUE ORCHID</i18n_short_description_es>
  <i18n_product_details>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Approx. inseam: 34in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rise: Front: 7 1/4in Back: 11 3/4in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leg opening: 24 1/2in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Cotton 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Clean pocket&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Button fly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Made in Europe using original and handcrafted finishing techniques&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details>
  <i18n_product_details_de>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Beinlänge ca.  86cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leibhöhe: Vorne: 18cm Hinten: 30cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fussweite: 63cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Baumwolle 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Clean Pocket&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Knopfleiste&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Made in Europe unter Verwendung von Original-und Handarbeit Veredelungstechniken&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_de>
  <i18n_product_details_nl>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Binnenbeenlengte ca.  86cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Kruisnaad: Voor: 18cm Achter: 30cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zoomwijdte: 63cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Katoen 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Achterzak zonder squiggle&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Knoopsluiting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gemaakt in Europa met behulp van originele en ambachtelijke afwerkingstechnieken&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_nl>
  <i18n_product_details_fr>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Inseam: sur  86cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fourche: Avant: 18cm Arrière: 30cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ouverture des jambes: 63cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Coton 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Clean poche&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fermeture boutons&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fabriqué en Europe avec des techniques de finitions artisanales&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_fr>
  <i18n_product_details_it>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lunghezza dal cavallo alla caviglia: circa  86cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lunghezza dal cavallo alla vita: Davanti: 18cm Dietro: 30cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Apertura gamba: 63cm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Cotone 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tasca Dietro: liscia&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Chiusura a bottoni&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Realizzato in Europa utilizzando tecniche di finitura artigianali&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_it>
  <i18n_product_details_es>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tiro aproximado: 34in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tiro: Frontal: 7 1/4in Trasero: 11 3/4in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Abertura de la pierna: 24 1/2in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;98% Algodón 2% Spandex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Blosillo sin squiggle&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Botones&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fabricado en Europa utilizando técnicas de acabado originales y artesanas.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_details_es>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit>The Biancha is A very expensive brand’s new, super sexy wide leg jean that features an exposed button fly, doubled belt loops, and coin welt pocket details. It is fitted through the hip and thigh and breaks above the knee into an exaggerated wide leg, creating flirty drama that is sophisticated, yet sexy.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_de>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Die Biancha ist A very expensive brands neue, super-sexy Jeans mit weitem Bein, auffälliger Knopfleiste, doppelten Gürtelschlaufen und gepaspelten Coinpockets&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;die an Hüften und Oberschenkeln körperbetonte Passform geht knapp unter dem Knie in einen extrem weiten Schlag über&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;eine absolut kokette Drama-Queen für einen sexy-eleganten Auftritt&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_de>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_nl>De Biancha is de nieuwe, supersexy jeans van A very expensive brand met uitlopende pijp, zichtbare knoopsluiting, dubbele ceintuurlussen en een muntzak. De broek sluit nauw aan rond de heup en dij en loopt net boven de knie superwijd uit, voor een flirterig dramatisch, sexy maar toch verfijnd resultaat.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_nl>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_fr>Le Biancha est le nouveau jean large super sexy de A very expensive brand, doté d’une fermeture à boutons apparents, de passants doubles et de poches passepoilées. Ajustée au niveau des hanches et des cuisses, la coupe s’évase au-dessus du genou en une jambe extra-large pour un style à la fois sophistiqué et très sexy.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_fr>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_it>Biancha è il nuovo jeans a gamba larga super sexy, firmato A very expensive brand. Si distingue per la chiusura a bottone a vista, i doppi passanti e le tasche a filetto portamonete. È aderente attorno a fianchi e cosce per poi allargarsi sfacciatamente appena sopra il ginocchio, disegnando una splendida silhouette dal look sofisticato, ma sexy.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_it>
  <i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_es>The Biancha is A very expensive brand’s new, super sexy wide leg jean that features an exposed button fly, doubled belt loops, and coin welt pocket details. It is fitted through the hip and thigh and breaks above the knee into an exaggerated wide leg, creating flirty drama that is sophisticated, yet sexy.</i18n_product_moreaboutthefit_es>
  <price>239</price>
  <price_uk>220</price_uk>
  <price_de>239</price_de>
  <price_be>239</price_be>
  <price_nl>239</price_nl>
  <price_fr>81.83</price_fr>
  <price_it>239</price_it>
  <price_pan_en>239</price_pan_en>
  <price_pan_es>239</price_pan_es>
  <price_pan_fr>239</price_pan_fr>
  <price_pan_de>239</price_pan_de>
  <special_price></special_price>
  <special_from_date></special_from_date>
  <special_to_date></special_to_date>
  <special_price_uk></special_price_uk>
  <special_from_date_uk></special_from_date_uk>
  <special_to_date_uk></special_to_date_uk>
  <special_price_de></special_price_de>
  <special_from_date_de></special_from_date_de>
  <special_to_date_de></special_to_date_de>
  <special_price_nl></special_price_nl>
  <special_from_date_nl></special_from_date_nl>
  <special_to_date_nl></special_to_date_nl>
  <special_price_be></special_price_be>
  <special_from_date_be></special_from_date_be>
  <special_to_date_be></special_to_date_be>
  <special_price_fr></special_price_fr>
  <special_from_date_fr></special_from_date_fr>
  <special_to_date_fr></special_to_date_fr>
  <special_price_it></special_price_it>
  <special_from_date_it></special_from_date_it>
  <special_to_date_it></special_to_date_it>
  <special_price_pan_en></special_price_pan_en>
  <special_from_date_pan_en></special_from_date_pan_en>
  <special_to_date_pan_en></special_to_date_pan_en>
  <special_price_pan_es></special_price_pan_es>
  <special_from_date_pan_es></special_from_date_pan_es>
  <special_to_date_pan_es></special_to_date_pan_es>
  <special_price_pan_fr></special_price_pan_fr>
  <special_from_date_pan_fr></special_from_date_pan_fr>
  <special_to_date_pan_fr></special_to_date_pan_fr>
  <special_price_pan_de></special_price_pan_de>
  <special_from_date_pan_de></special_from_date_pan_de>
  <special_to_date_pan_de></special_to_date_pan_de>
  <news_from_date>2012-04-01</news_from_date>
  <image_front>SLLJ700OB_front.jpg</image_front>
  <image_back>SLLJ700OB_back.jpg</image_back>
  <image_pocket>SLLJ700OB_pocket.jpg</image_pocket>
  <image_wash>SLLJ700OB_wash.jpg</image_wash>
  <small_image></small_image>
  <thumbnail></thumbnail>
  <url_key></url_key>
  <color></color>
  <bubble_new_collection></bubble_new_collection>
  <bubble_sale></bubble_sale>
  <bubble_best_seller></bubble_best_seller>
  <bubble_limited_edition></bubble_limited_edition>
  <gender>Women</gender>
  <fit_group>FLARED</fit_group>
  <fit_code>BIANCHA</fit_code>
  <wash_group>DARK WASH</wash_group>
  <enable_special_area>No</enable_special_area>
  <special_area_static_block_id></special_area_static_block_id>
  <delivery_return_static_block_id>product_tab_delivery_return</delivery_return_static_block_id>
  <status>Disabled</status>
  <visibility>Nowhere</visibility>
  <super_attributes>size</super_attributes>
  <website>base</website>
  <category_ids></category_ids>
  <main_cat_seo></main_cat_seo>
  <details_care></details_care>
</configurable>
